We interrupt with breaking news.
Premier Medical Hall in Chinatown
suffered a tragedy yesterday.
Mom, Dad...
For generations, we healed in peace.
Then disaster struck and my parents were murdered.
I was framed by my fiancée and jailed.
Luckily, Young Master Gu watched over my sister.
That gave me some peace of mind in prison.
And uncovered clues to my parents' murder.
Boss, we've got a new guy today.
Really? Then let's lay down the rules.
Sorry, sorry.
Watch where you're going!
Are you blind, you fat piece of trash?
I was just looking for a punching bag.
You fat bastard.
And you delivered yourself right to me.
Stop!
1580, I'm warning you, stay out of this.
Around here,
I call the shots.
And what if I insist on butting in?
Then I'll teach you the rules here.
Get him!
Boss!
No more bullying newcomers.
That's my rule.
Stop calling me 1580.
My name is Ren Feifan.
Dad
Mom
Don't worry
I won't let any of them get away
Welcome back, Master
Did you find Ren Ran?
She's at Zhao Biao's club
They played dirty with Young Master Gu away
Let's go
To get her
Right
Time to settle all scores with Zhao Biao
Where are they?
Who's there?
Where the hell did they go?
Get out here!
Beat him to death!
Who the hell are you people?
Do you know where this is?
You'll be in big trouble soon.
Behave yourself!
My boss is Ma Dongxi!
Cut the crap.
Ren Ran.
It's all right now.
Ren Feifan.
Shut up.
Take Ren Ran home first.
Ren Feifan, what are you trying to do?
Answer one question for me.
I...
Who's there?
Boss.
Who is it?
Who's there?
Boss.
Who is it?
Ren Feifan, you're dead!
I...
Your name is Ren Feifan?
Yeah.
Were you in North City Prison?
Just got out today?
Yes.
Benefactor!
I finally get to meet you!
Back when you were inside,
you saved our family's only heir in three generations!
Look here.
Come on.
The situation isn't looking good.
Ma.
Yes.
He's wanted to thank you for saving him inside.
We were supposed to pick you up today.
But we missed you. Look at this.
Boss Feifan.
From now on, your word is my word.
My turf is your turf.
Just say the word,
and we'll go through fire and water for you.
Go through fire and water,
without hesitation.
Four years ago,
why did you kill my parents?
I...
I know someone took the fall for you.
A prescription.
You don't know medicine or healing.
What did you want the prescription for?
I...
Well...
Someone else sent me to do it.
Who?
Talk, now!
No, Boss.
I...
This matter...
Speak!
It was the Wang heir, Wang Wenhao.
Not bad. Ten minutes longer than last time.
If watching me do it didn't give you an adrenaline rush,
you probably wouldn't even get excited, right?
Useless man.
So boring.
President Wang.
Ren Feifan is back.
And Ma Dongxi has become his underling.
Who could have seen this coming?
He nearly beat me to death.
President Wang, only you can protect me now.
So you're saying,
you told him everything, didn't you?
No, President Wang.
Look at me.
He would've killed me if I didn't talk.
President Wang! President Wang!
Four years ago, you botched my job.
I told you never to appear before me again.
Don't ruin things for me again!
Understood?
Ren Feifan!
Feeding your sister random meds again?
Stop right there!
Recite it from the beginning.
Ying Zhi Zhuan Ren, Wang Li...
What do you mean, Wang Leehom?
It's Li Fanghong.
Don't just make things up.
You got it wrong again! You...
And now you're running?
Feifan,
you're finally back.
Brother Hui.
Yeah.
After Master and his wife passed away,
Premier Medical Hall was liquidated.
Nothing was left behind.
Over the years, the Wangs won over the Li Group,
and joined with distributor Xu...
Joined with the Xu Family.
These three are now in cahoots.
Through hostile takeovers,
they control almost 80% of North City's pharma market.
Other clinics that refused to pick a side
were all pushed out.
North City today
is no longer the North City we knew.
I'll make the Wang family
pay blood for blood.
Lu Jianqi just became president of the Northern City Medical Association.
We've got to get him on our side.
Cut the useless crap.
You think I don't know that?
I've sent gifts twice already.
And they were all sent back.
Dad, just hear me out.
I've already found a way in.
It'll definitely work.
I've done my research.
Lu Jianqi's father has a severe cataract.
I've gathered top experts from home and abroad
to take turns treating him.
There's no way we can't cure him.
Will this actually work?
Of course it will.
You're finally using your head this time.
Fine.
Go handle it.
Don't worry, Dad.
I heard Ren Feifan is back.
That small fry won't last long.
Once I've dealt with Lu Jianqi,
I'll take my time playing with him.
The project is at a critical stage right now.
We absolutely can't afford any slip-ups.
If you spot any potential threats,
best to eliminate them in advance.
Don't worry, Dad.
I know what I'm doing.
Master.
Ren Ran has been admitted to the South City sanatorium.
How is she?
Is she adjusting well?
Don't worry, I've arranged everything there.
Rest assured, Master.
Also, Master, I've delivered what you asked me to.
Lu Jianqi wants to meet you tomorrow to discuss it.
All of you, get away!
Back, back, back!
Get away, all of you!
Is that so!
You want to cut into this old man's eyes?
Not in this lifetime!
Mr. Lu, please calm down.
These doctors I invited for you
are all top cataract surgery specialists from home and abroad.
It took great effort to bring them here.
Let me ask you just one thing.
Can it be cured without surgery?
I'm Dr. Alexander.
I have extensive experience in cataract surgery.
You can trust me.
Get out! What nonsense is this?
Go, go, all of you, leave!
Everyone out!
Out, out, out!
All of you, leave!
Get out, now!
Just grab him and do the surgery.
Are you leaving or not?
Once his eyes are healed, he'll thank us.
All of you, get away!
Step back!
Who dares?
Dad, Dad, don't get worked up.
Please calm down.
I'll handle it.
President.
I know you're a devoted son,
but if we keep delaying his eye treatment,
it really won't be curable.
Cutting into the eyes is no small matter.
Here's what we'll do.
If any of you
can carve the word 'Healer' on a single grain of rice,
that person will be qualified to operate on the old man.
Rice? How is that possible?
That's indeed asking too much.
If none of you can do it,
then please leave.
I can do it.