‎SPOOKY IN LOVE
‎They parked by Haedam Reservoir
‎for two hours,
‎then drove seven kilometers
‎past the tollgate.
‎At 1 a.m.,
‎the missing person's phone
‎was turned off
‎somewhere around Sanggok-myeon, so…
‎Yes?
‎Where?
‎Who's there?
‎It was a woman?
‎So it's you.
‎They say the culprit
‎always returns to the scene.
‎No woman could dump a corpse here alone.
‎An accomplice?
‎Are you here for this?
‎The victim's phone? Put it down.
‎Put it down.
‎That's…
‎Damn it.
‎People like you exhaust me.
‎People like you are the reason
‎I have no time to be exhausted.
‎The law is a luxury for the likes of you.
‎You're lecturing me about the law?
‎-What a joke.
‎-Let me go.
‎-What do you think--
‎-Freeze.
‎Don't move!
‎What are you doing here this late?
‎My gosh,
‎I get that it's dark and secluded here,
‎but aren't you being too frisky?
‎-It's not what you think!
‎Darn it.
‎Good job, guys. You can go on home now.
‎Don't touch me.
‎I'll sue you for aggravated assault.
‎If nudging you is aggravated assault,
‎what will you call your kick?
‎You appeared out of nowhere
‎and acted all weird.
‎You're the weirdest one here, okay?
‎Why were you here this late,
‎and how did you know the body was here?
‎-Well?
‎-Prosecutor Ma.
‎Hey.
‎So how did you know…
‎What the heck? Where'd she go?
‎What? Who?
‎-Where did…
‎-Who? What?
‎Didn't you see the woman
‎I was just talking to?
‎What woman?
‎Come on, you're scaring me.
‎She was in a hoodie.
‎Come on, now. You must've seen a ghost.
‎This is why I told you
‎to go to bed on time.
‎But she was standing right here
‎a minute ago.
‎Yeah, sure.
‎So how did the caller know
‎the body was here?
‎Who called in the tip-off?
‎I know you're angry
‎it took so long to find your body,
‎but the killer will pay.
‎So let it all go and move on.
‎And marry a good person in your next life.
‎Is there even a next life?
‎I think my current life
‎is royally screwed.
‎If I were told I could get a second try
‎at living again, perhaps…
‎Wait. Where'd he go?
‎You moved on already?
‎Couldn't you give me an answer first?
‎Why do they all vanish
‎whenever I ask them that?
‎Aren't we on the same side?
‎We have a camaraderie.
‎Don't we?
‎I guess we don't.
‎Yeo-ri.
‎6 YEARS AGO
‎What's the matter? You don't like it?
‎Are you really okay with this?
‎For as long as you're with me,
‎you'll live with fear and horror.
‎They'll become a part of your life.
‎I heard all about that.
‎Give me your hand.
‎It's fine.
‎Nothing will happen.
‎Next, we have some business news.
‎Cheon Yeo-ri,
‎the Reina Hotels & Resorts heiress
‎and Cha Gi-u, the eldest son
‎of Cha & Yul Law Firm's partner
‎are to be engaged today.
‎They met early in the year
‎through a mutual friend,
‎and dated with prospects of marriage.
‎The union of two prestigious business
‎and legal entities has everyone talking.
‎The engagement will be held in private
‎at Reina Hotel's Siena Hall.
‎CHEON YEO-RI & CHA GI-U
‎I'm so sorry.
‎I left home early,
‎but the traffic was insane.
‎It's okay, you're here now.
‎Everyone's waiting. We should go.
‎You look amazing today.
‎Let's go.
‎The engagement ring.
‎I must've left it in the car.
‎I'll be right back.
‎What's happening?
‎Hey. Get a hold of yourself.
‎Hello?
‎The elevator's flooding!
‎Hello? The elevator's flooded!
‎Hello?
‎Damn it.
‎Gi-u.
‎-Are you all right?
‎-Don't come closer.
‎-Gi-u.
‎-Stay right there!
‎I didn't think I'd actually become haunted
‎just by holding your hand.
‎Yeo-ri.
‎I'm sorry.
‎I don't think I can marry you. I'm sorry.
‎I won't date her.
‎I won't ever see Yeo-ri again.
‎That's when I realized…
‎that I couldn't touch anyone ever ‎again.
‎That I shouldn't rely on
‎or expect anything from anyone.
‎That's when I also decided…
‎that if I couldn't avoid the spirits
‎that came to find me,
‎then I'd learn not to let them bother me.
‎I may not be welcoming,
‎but I'd try to overcome it ‎enough
‎that I wouldn't fear
‎being around them.
‎SPOOKY IN LOVE
‎EPISODE 1
‎The whole point of this case is
‎that although the parties
‎do seem to be connected,
‎there's only circumstantial evidence
‎and no direct evidence
‎such as a corpse or murder weapon.
‎We uphold ‎the ‎principle ‎of ‎trial
‎by evidence,
‎and therefore have concluded
‎there's not enough
‎to result in a conviction.
‎Defendant, please rise.
‎Case No. 5410-Badan-1651.
‎The sentence.
‎Defendant Park Seung-jae,
‎accused of the murder of Jang Eun-ju.
‎We find him not guilty.
‎-What? Not guilty?
‎-This trial is concluded.
‎Good job. Well done, man.
‎You did great.
‎How does it feel to lose?
‎I'll appeal.
‎They say there's no hope for the stupid.
‎Did you forget what the judge said?
‎It's trial by evidence
‎and you have no body.
‎Bring material evidence,
‎not circumstantial nonsense.
‎No evidence now
‎doesn't mean no evidence forever.
‎I'll find something before the appeal
‎and lock you up.
‎-By the book.
‎-Sure, whatever.
‎Whatever helps you sleep at night.
‎You follow your dear law.
‎I'll do whatever I want.
‎Prosecutor Ma.
‎CHIEF PROSECUTOR NAM SANG-HO
‎What will you do?
‎Type out a cause for appeal.
‎Over a drop of blood on his shirt
‎when you don't have a body?
‎Please, Gang-uk…
‎You won't talk me out of appealing,
‎will you?
‎Park Seung-jae's father,
‎Assemblyman Park Jin-dong
‎is the ruling party's
‎likely presidential candidate.
‎I already have my orders from above.
‎It's time to drop it.
‎Can't you back me up even a little?
‎I don't…
‎I really don't want to be petty
‎and say this--
‎Not a word then.
‎I'll recite your usual spiel.
‎The Daebak Savings Bank corruption case.
‎The YOLO City fraudulent estate sale case.
‎That's not all.
‎The Seojin Construction
‎political bribery case.
‎Despite immense outside pressure,
‎you indicted them all and took them
‎to court without batting an eyelid.
‎On top of that,
‎you maintained your stance
‎and scored hefty penalties for them all.
‎You crazy bastard.
‎You did all that on your own.
‎You did all the work
‎and I took all the credit.
‎I admit that too.
‎But Gang-uk…
‎Forget everything else.
‎Let me work according to the law.
‎Oh, gosh…
‎Man, my eyes hurt bad.
‎CRIMINAL PROSECUTION 12,
‎CHIEF PROSECUTOR'S OFFICE
‎What will you do now?
‎Giving up…
‎is not an option. We should fight.
‎-Excuse me.
‎-Sure.
‎MADAM PANG
‎Why is Madam Pang calling?
‎Hello?
‎Oh, that's today?
‎I'm a bit busy.
‎Does the monk do remote prayers…
‎Could you go instead?
‎You see, I'm considering going to church.
‎I think it's best if you go.
‎Grandma.
‎Do it properly, with all your heart.
‎How much longer do I have to keep this up?
‎Hello, Venerable.
‎You just do as you're told.
‎I'm not saying I won't attend the service.
‎At least tell me who I'm praying for
‎so I can--
‎Enough.
‎Madam Pang, I have a hunch.
‎-Is the person I'm praying for--
‎-Right.
‎I spoke to the chief monk already,
‎-so pay the temple office.
‎-Yes, ma'am.
‎Oh, right.
‎I'll say it again, for your sake.
‎You must stay well away from women
‎born in the year of the Black Monkey.
‎All right?
‎Black Monkey or White Monkey,
‎I don't have the time to meet anyone.
‎What zodiac signs
‎are you incompatible with?
‎Why do you ask?
‎Just so I know.
‎We can't have you meeting your soulmate
‎only to find out you're incompatible.
‎You darn fool.
‎You can't talk like that at a temple.
‎-We're leaving.
‎-Come on, it's harmless fun.
‎You're too cheeky for your own good.
‎What happened to the old man from before?
‎-Who?
‎-It seemed to be going well.
‎You crazy fool.
‎Oh, welcome.
‎Where to, sir?
‎Sir?
‎Aren't you going home?
‎You won't stay on the Jang Eun-ju case,
‎will you?
‎Not you too, Investigator Ko.
‎I mean, it's raining hard.
‎It's the perfect night for a nice drink.
‎It's raining hard,
‎so why don't you just go home?
‎Have some quality time with your wife.
‎My wife says all she wants from me
‎is confirmation that I'm alive.
‎Oh, dear. Is that why you're sulking?
‎Will you keep me company then?
‎I'm willing if you're buying.
‎I'm always free.
‎You never even suggest you'll buy.
‎Let's split the bill today. 50-50.
‎-Who pays 50?
‎-What?
‎I pay 50, of course.
‎With our prosecutor's card.
‎You really won't join us, sir?
‎Oh, right.
‎The bathroom light is out.
‎Oh, that's right.
‎Don't use the last stall.
‎-They say a ghost appears on rainy days--
‎-Get out of here already.
‎-Watch out.
‎-The ghost harasses people.
‎-Don't drink too much!
‎-I'm serious.
‎KEEP THE TOILET CLEAN
‎TAKE ALL YOUR BELONGINGS!
‎This happens whenever it rains.
‎Damn it.
‎Who's there?
‎Don't use the last stall.
‎They say a ghost appears on rainy days.
‎Show yourself!
‎OUT OF ORDER, DO NOT USE
‎Where are we on the Jane Müller deal?
‎Yes, ma'am.
‎Jane Müller's a world-famous florist,
‎and we had some scheduling difficulties.
‎We were finally able to arrange a meeting.
‎-I'll organize your trip--
‎-Stop.
‎Maintain your distance.
‎I apologize, Ms. Cheon.
‎-I got carried away with the brief.
‎-Catch me if you can.
‎Sweetie, are you all right?
‎Let's get you up.
‎I'm so sorry.
‎Let's go.
‎Ms. Cheon.
‎The chairwoman is asking for you.
‎-Here he comes.
‎-How do you feel right now?
‎-Any comments?
‎-What do you have to say?
‎-How do you feel?
‎-Anything to say?
‎-Look at the cameras.
‎-Pose for some photos.
‎First of all, I respect
‎the judiciary's sensible decision.
‎I'm pleased the truth came out
‎before it was too late.
‎I thank everyone who believed in me
‎and waited for the verdict.
‎I'll do a full interview at a later date.
‎Are you satisfied with the verdict?
‎How will your career--
‎He was found not guilty.
‎Can I go ahead and marry him?
‎Negligence and embezzlement
‎come with the territory
‎when you're in business,
‎but aren't you concerned
‎he was charged with murder?
‎No, Chairwoman.
‎Come on, Grandma.
‎That brat clung to him like superglue,
‎then went into hiding
‎when she couldn't get her way.
‎If you think about it,
‎Seung-jae's a victim too.
‎It's not just about marriage.
‎It involves business interests too.
‎Our new resort needs building approval
‎and it's in his father's constituency.
‎Postponing the wedding
‎might only delay our business plans.
‎We were discussing Ha-ri's marriage.
‎I asked you to join
‎because we haven't met in a while.
‎What do you think
‎about Assemblyman Park's son?
‎Does it matter what I think?
‎Ha-ri's the one getting married.
‎Of course your opinion matters.
‎Our family is an economic unit.
‎If we're an economic unit,
‎the wedding should happen.
‎That's your stance as an older cousin.
‎What do you think as a big sister?
‎If you want my opinion as a big sister…
‎I'll never accept a parasite like him.
‎You called him a parasite?
‎Isn't that a bit too harsh?
‎If Mr. Park's a parasite,
‎do you think his father is a host?
‎I don't like the sound of that.
‎I know you're just cousins,
‎but you grew up together.
‎I say that because we grew up together.
‎To be honest,
‎without his assemblyman father,
‎Mr. Park has nothing to offer.
‎How do you feel about him
‎in relation to the ruling?
‎Frankly, the whole thing started
‎because Park Seung-jae
‎dumped Jang Eun-ju for Ha-ri.
‎Ha-ri.
‎What's your charm?
‎Yeo-ri, what kind of question is that?
‎Our Ha-ri…
‎has her beauty.
‎Yes, I was born with a noble elegance.
‎I stand to inherit loads too.
‎Once a cheater, always a cheater.
‎If he were to come across
‎an heiress with more pull,
‎Park Seung-jae will dump you for her.
‎Are you trying to keep me in check
‎in case Seung-jae helps us
‎secure the resort license
‎and boost my equity?
‎Ha-ri.
‎Let's see how things play out.
‎We'll wait and see.
‎Give me a moment, Yeo-ri.
‎The occupation rates
‎are holding up pretty well
‎considering it's off-season.
‎The restaurants and banquet halls
‎are fully booked every day.
‎Siena Hall is the real problem.
‎Siena Hall…
‎It's not just a problem.
‎It makes zero sales.
‎It's as good as a disaster.
‎It's not that bad.
‎It was every couple's dream venue
‎before the renovation.
‎It was.
‎Until Cheon Yeo-ri wanted to be the first
‎to get engaged after the reopening,
‎and ruined everything.
‎She ruined everything? How?
‎Her fiancé ran off
‎right before the engagement.
‎Who'd want to marry there
‎after the first couple broke up?
‎They say no couple
‎that got engaged or married there
‎lasted more than two years.
‎That's how Siena Hall became
‎Cheon Yeo-ri's most painful weakness.
‎It can't be great all the time.
‎Apart from Siena Hall,
‎our sales are the highest in the area.
‎We couldn't have done that
‎without Ms. Cheon.
‎That's true.
‎I must admit, she's a great businesswoman.
‎If only she were nicer
‎to the people around her…
‎How long do we have to wait anyway?
‎It'll be here soon.
‎You must be hungry.
‎I'm starving. Hurry up.
‎By the way,
‎what happens to Siena Hall now?
‎I don't know.
‎I guess the chairwoman
‎will make a call soon.
‎How about we use this building
‎as something else entirely?
‎As an art gallery.
‎Siena Hall, you mean?
‎I was going to mention it
‎at the strategy meeting in two days.
‎A gallery is a great idea.
‎As expected, Grandma…
‎Chairwoman,
‎I applaud your thought process.
‎Mom, it's what you always wanted.
‎-If you were to do that for me…
‎-I can't accept that.
‎You know what this hall means to me.
‎My dad designed and built this place
‎for my mom.
‎It can never be used for anything else.
‎In any case,
‎Siena Hall is still part of the hotel.
‎A building that doesn't make money
‎is just an eyesore.
‎That's what I still think and believe.
‎How about we have dinner together
‎since it's been a while?
‎I'm sorry,
‎but my routine is to get home before dusk.
‎I didn't think
‎I'd actually become haunted
‎because ‎of ‎you.
‎Siena Hall is the real problem.
‎How about we use this building
‎as something else entirely?
‎As an art gallery.
‎Cheers.
‎Oh, gosh. Give me those.
‎We need a steady flow of cooked meat.
‎How many times did I tell you so?
‎Can't we eat raw fish too,
‎every once in a while?
‎We're always eating pork skin and offal.
‎I can't take it anymore.
‎You don't know what you're talking about.
‎The internal organs taste best,
‎Hyeong-min.
‎It's not good to eat too much food
‎that's high in fat.
‎You need to watch your health.
‎Speaking of which,
‎how many supplements do you take a day?
‎I used to take 12.
‎But I started taking spirulina,
‎so it's 14 now.
‎If we civil servants
‎want to live long enough
‎to claim a pension,
‎we need to watch our health.
‎Exactly. To stay healthy,
‎we must eat food that's good for us.
‎-…pro golfer Park Seung-jae
‎-Mr. Ma. The omakase nearby…
‎will compete
‎in the Astra Championship this week.
‎He was named as a suspect
‎in ‎the ‎murder ‎of his late girlfriend,
‎-but was found not guilty,
‎-What?
‎-thereby clearing his name.
‎-He went right back to playing golf?
‎He resumed training
‎as soon as the verdict was announced,
‎-and is determined to return to…
‎-Championship, my ass.
‎Be it a witness or an informant,
‎I wish someone would come forward.
‎…focusing on improving his score.
‎As a likely winner of the tournament,
‎Park Seung-jae--
‎ROUND 8
‎5 SONGS WITH LOCATIONS IN THE TITLE
‎You're hurting my eyes!
‎If you want to fiddle with the zipper,
‎just do it all in one go.
‎You scared me by going bit by bit.
‎Even better, just knock.
‎I put up a wall because I was tired.
‎I'm not discriminating between ghosts.
‎Okay, fine.
‎I'll go. I'm going.
‎See? I'm off.
‎You went to death's door and back.
‎Do as they ask, if you can.
‎Help the ghosts.
‎Doing as they ask and helping them
‎is the only thing
‎that will keep you alive.
‎It doesn't feel right to ignore her,
‎but helping them would be a hassle.
‎Let's go already.
‎-Can we please go home?
‎-Wait.
‎Let's have one more drink.
‎Just for another hour.
‎-Your wife will kill me.
‎-Just another hour.
‎She won't kill you. I said I'd be late,
‎and she texted back saying she understood.
‎No way! Your wife's not like that!
‎Why don't you believe me?
‎I'll show you the text.
‎-No, that's fine.
‎-Don't bother.
‎No, why don't you both come to my place?
‎You haven't seen my wife in a while.
‎I'll say, "Honey, cook us something."
‎-We saw her not that long ago.
‎-Oh, taxi!
‎-Let's go for a third round.
‎-You need to go home.
‎-Get in quick.
‎-Wait, I…
‎-I got slapped for coming alone.
‎-Fine.
‎-No, you won't get slapped.
‎-Just get in.
‎-Watch your head as you get in.
‎-You might never see me again.
‎-Watch your head.
‎-But I…
‎Go on home already.
‎-Take him home.
‎-Wait!
‎-Here's the taxi fare.
‎-Get in.
‎-Get home safely.
‎-No, wait!
‎Oh, gosh…
‎He never knows when to stop.
‎Man, I'm exhausted.
‎-Where are you going?
‎-I need to take a leak.
‎Come right back. We're leaving right away.
‎What should I get?
‎Give me a pack of those red cigarettes.
‎Hey, can you move your head?
‎I'm trying to park
‎and you're blocking my view.
‎Is that the car?
‎I'm not the police.
‎I can't exactly do anything.
‎What was that?
‎Damn it.
‎Oh, come on.
‎-Are you all right?
‎-Yes.
‎Those crazy bastards.
‎Step on it.
‎Who are you?
‎-Why did you jump into my car?
‎-That was a hit-and-run.
‎I can help. Don't worry.
‎What makes you think I'm worried?
‎Huh?
‎What?
‎What are you doing here?
‎You're the one who jumped in.
‎That was forced entry.
‎Start the car first. I'll help you.
‎Why do you keep saying you'll help?
‎I'll take care of it,
‎so get out of my car.
‎Those two looked suspicious, okay?
‎They didn't just smell of alcohol.
‎If they're that suspicious,
‎follow them in your own car.
‎I would if I could. I can't drive drunk!
‎I'm not some weirdo. Here.
‎Take a look. I'm a prosecutor.
‎Pretend you're assisting in a case
‎and start the car.
‎Hurry! We might lose them!
‎They're stuck at a red light
‎at the intersection up ahead!
‎Says who?
‎Darn it.
‎Hey, isn't that the car I reversed into?
‎You were right.
‎-Step on the gas.
‎-Damn it.
‎See if you can turn left from here.
‎-I know a shortcut.
‎-Okay.
‎Turning right from here.
‎What?
‎Why did you turn right?
‎I told you to turn left.
‎Okay, then turn right up there.
‎-Where do I go now? Left?
‎-What?
‎Don't you hear me?
‎You're sure, right?
‎A right turn, then left turn?
‎Are you serious?
‎When did I say turn right then left?
‎I told you to turn left then right,
‎or right then right again.
‎Be quiet, both of you!
‎I can't concentrate
‎with you both shouting!
‎We lost them.
‎There's no teamwork here, just sabotage.
‎We're not a team.
‎We haven't lost them completely.
‎It's a straight road from here on out,
‎and there are shortcuts
‎on the way, he says.
‎I say, I mean.
‎Who is she talking to?
‎This road…
‎You must stay well away from women
‎born in the year of the Black Monkey.
‎All right?
‎This feels more like a shortcut to hell.
‎Hey, could you be a bit more careful?
‎Your driving…
‎The punk's a pretty good tail.
‎Get ahead of them.
‎Get into the other lane.
‎Step on it.
‎-How much?
‎-Until I say stop.
‎Now!
‎That crazy…
‎Nice, we did it. High-five.
‎Damn it.
‎Stay in the car with the doors locked.
‎Hey, be careful.
‎Being a thug is all about the gear.
‎You don't just do hit-and-runs, do you?
‎You look like you rob people,
‎at the very least.
‎Let's have you pay
‎for what you did right away.
‎Prison is the place for you.
‎That's right.
‎Fights are all about the gear.
‎Lend me a hand?
‎Well…
‎Call me if you need a witness
‎to the hit-and-run.
‎Why don't you finish
‎your official business first?
‎What…
‎Please, no!
‎Goodbye,
‎to a better place.
‎So it wasn't about the hit-and-run?
‎That's impossible.
‎What was that?
‎Who is she really?
‎She's no ghost,
‎but she appears wherever I go.
‎What's wrong with this?
‎Huh?
‎What the heck?
‎What's going on?
‎Hey, Mr. Ma.
‎What was that?
‎Why am I even dreaming about her?
‎-Morning.
‎-Hey.
‎-Mr. Ma.
‎-Yes?
‎For the missing taxi driver case,
‎the suspects were indicted for murder.
‎How did you catch them?
‎Well…
‎-Huh?
‎-What? What are you doing here?
‎-Turn left.
‎-Turning right.
‎-Turn right up there.
‎-Left?
‎What?
‎We caught them and that's what matters.
‎Do we have surveillance footage
‎for the Mt. Haewang body disposal case?
‎Something about that
‎has been bothering me.
‎Do we have it yet?
‎About 30 minutes
‎before the victim's phone was turned on,
‎someone placed a call
‎from a nearby payphone.
‎Oh, they sent it over.
‎There.
‎-We only have a back profile.
‎-Wait.
‎What is it?
‎The sneakers. Can you zoom in on them?
‎I'd recognize them anywhere.
‎How did they get a pair?
‎-What pair?
‎-You don't know the brand?
‎Those cost a fortune.
‎How expensive could a pair of sneakers be?
‎-They cost at least ten million won.
‎-What?
‎This model is a collaboration
‎between Blenciaga and Nice.
‎Let me see.
‎F&F Black and White.
‎It's the limited edition.
‎Only three pairs were sold in Korea.
‎I think I've seen these somewhere.
‎You can't have.
‎You don't know anyone
‎who could afford those.
‎Then again,
‎there are lots of knockoffs too.
‎Your top looks like a knockoff.
‎What?
‎Gosh, what a flashy building.
‎I looked into the three people
‎who bought those sneakers.
‎One flew to the US last month.
‎Another one was locked up
‎six months ago for fraud.
‎The third and last one's a bit…
‎A bit what?
‎There's no point
‎in even checking them out.
‎Heiress to Reina Group,
‎the nation's fifth-largest ‎conglomerate,
‎and CEO of the most luxurious hotel
‎in the country, Cheon Yeo-ri.
‎She has a strong aversion
‎to meeting people,
‎so she rarely sits in meetings
‎or does media interviews.
‎Only a few core hotel executives
‎know what she looks like.
‎So Mr. Ma,
‎if you go there without a warrant,
‎you'll get turned away
‎before you set eyes on her.
‎Hello.
‎I'm Prosecutor Ma Gang-uk from Seoul
‎Central District Prosecutors' Office.
‎I'd like to meet the CEO.
‎You can't request
‎a private meeting with her.
‎What do I have to do then?
‎If you send an official request
‎to the secretary's office,
‎they'll review it and get back to you.
‎Thank you.
‎We extend a warm welcome from Reina.
‎-Hello.
‎Did you see a woman in a checkered outfit?
‎No?
‎Why is he coming after me?
‎What is this about?
‎She's so darn fast. Jeez.
‎Excuse me?
‎Hello?
‎Wait up!
‎Will you just…
‎What the… Are you serious?
‎Why is this hotel so massive?
‎Hey, wait. Can we just talk?
‎Why are there so many stairs?
‎Where'd she go?
‎He won't follow me in here, will he?
‎What's going on?
‎Why does he keep appearing wherever I go?
‎Is he stalking me?
‎Where did she go?
‎Why were you out so late?
‎I'm just asking.
‎I envy you for having plans after work.
‎Oh, don't worry. It wasn't a guy, okay?
‎You should date someone.
‎Will you set me up?
‎What? He didn't leave?
‎Did you see Cheon Yeo-ri yesterday?
‎"Stop. Maintain your distance."
‎-You sound just like her.
‎-Don't I?
‎Was she always so hard to be around?
‎Yeah, I've been here for five years
‎and she was like that then too.
‎She ignored a kid
‎who fell right in front of her.
‎She ignores everything and everyone.
‎Is she a germaphobe?
‎She's always wearing gloves.
‎Wasn't she pretending to be
‎a European crown princess?
‎She's the worst.
‎I wish ghosts would drag away
‎entitled people like her--
‎My gosh. Ms. Cheon.
‎"Ms. Cheon"?
‎-Oh, no.
‎-What do we do?
‎Oh, my legs.
‎What is he doing here?
‎Why do we keep crossing paths?
‎Where am I?
‎I'm pretty sure she went this way.
‎CEO'S OFFICE
‎Hello?
‎No one's here.
‎What the heck?
‎SPOOKY IN LOVE
‎Park Seung-jae sunk ‎thrilling ‎shot
‎after ‎shot ‎at the championship
‎and is now top of the leaderboard
‎in the third round.
‎We must find something
‎we might have overlooked.
‎Something to overturn the verdict
‎in the second trial.
‎A smoking gun.
‎The truth is, Jang Eun-ju
‎came to our hotel before she went missing.
‎Could this be a coincidence?
‎Let's go for a three-way encounter.
‎So you're saying
‎Jang Eun-ju is coming here?
‎Did we make contact?
‎What then? That would be a disaster.
‎Excuse me.
‎Did you and I…
‎You're not at all my type.
‎Who cares if he sees ghosts or not?
‎Subtitle translation by: Jennifer Jean Lim