[Episode 22]
Look over there.
Come on, let's unload the luggage first.
No rush. Sit steady for a moment.
- Right. Here.
- Thank you.
- All right.
- Let's take off our life jackets.
Thank you.
Just a moment.
- No rush. Sit tight, everyone.
- Come on.
When you stand up later,
one from the left, one from the right.
That keeps the boat balanced
and makes it safer.
- Okay.
- Okay. All right.
This feels amazing.
- When we go up the mountain...
- Look at that.
- Not bad. It's a bit hot, though.
- Slow down a bit.
Good.
- Is that a coconut tree?
- Yes, that's a coconut tree.
- Are there coconuts on it?
- Yes, there are.
Big ones. We can go pick one.
I'm dying of thirst.
God, are you insane?
Okay. Careful over here.
- We're almost there.
- These flowers are beautiful too.
This is nice. Time to unwind.
Yeah. We hardly ever get a break.
- Jing.
- Yeah?
Let me show you something good.
What do you think?
Put this on, and you'll turn every head.
I guarantee everyone within ten miles
will be at your feet.
Just put it on.
In that swimsuit,
you'd look like an orchid mantis.
I brought one.
Hey. I bought this push-up style
especially for you.
Look.
You have no taste.
Jing. Hurry up.
Cen won't know what hit him.
The beach sun is brutal.
Use plenty of sunscreen.
That should do it.
Looks great. It really suits your skin tone.
See? I told you.
With Cen's taste, he'll totally get your look.
Ma Yang's first move was Hawaiian shorts.
Why don't you follow the local custom?
If you like,
I can steal a pair from his closet.
Let's go.
What's this?
Just listen.
You haven't been sleeping well lately.
Don't you listen to white noise to sleep?
I recorded some on the boat here.
- Let me help you with the sunscreen.
- No, thanks.
She's right by the ocean.
She's got the real thing.
Once she's back, there won't be an ocean.
Put it by your pillow when you sleep.
It should help you sleep better.
Then I'll take it.
I'll get you something in return.
Sure.
Take me around Teng City's night market later.
Do you want to play?
Are you taking my picture,
or am I taking yours?
Take a couple of me.
Get Ma Yang here, too. The more, the merrier.
Slow down.
Ma Yang,
let's play.
Do you know what an uninvited
ex-boyfriend is like?
Like when you're beachcombing,
and a trash bag washes back onto the sand.
An uninvited ex-boyfriend...
Then what are you?
Go warm up. I'll watch your match in a bit.
Come on. Weren't you here to get moving?
Mr. Cen, you spend most days at a desk.
Don't pull something when you start moving.
No need to worry, Mr. Chen.
I can handle that much basic exercise.
Come on.
Jing, which type do you like?
What type of what?
Men.
With two handsome guys playing right there?
You don't react at all.
Look at Chen.
Every move he makes has an edge.
Just like his personality.
Cen plays so gently,
but always finds a clever way out.
And Ma?
He...
He's just an idiot.
The team match officially begins.
Away from her, your arm stops hurting,
and your legs aren't sore anymore.
Nice shot.
Trying to look tough won't always work.
You're this guarded around me.
Is it because you doubt yourself?
Or because you don't trust Miao Jing?
She's an adult.
She has her own mind.
True.
She's ambitious. She has vision.
On this project, besides me,
she's the second-in-command.
The only thing standing between her
and a senior partner is time.
Teng City is too small a stage for her.
As her boss,
you care a lot about an employee's career.
As her family,
of course, I'll give her my full support.
- Impressive.
- Nice shot.
Good!
Sorry.
- This one...
- I think this is yours.
- Is this beef?
- There's plenty for everyone.
It feels more like lamb to me.
I'll take one of these.
- Is that enough?
- Yes, plenty.
- Here.
- Look at this.
- A new way of skewering.
- Come on. These are freshly grilled.
Sandwich.
Come on, try it.
This smells amazing.
You gave it a little extra work.
How does it taste?
You can pick it up here
or at a Hai City auto service center.
See which location works better for you.
What do you mean?
You'll have more freedom with your own car.
So you don't always have to borrow one
from your coworkers.
And who are you to give me this?
Come on, just eating is boring.
- Let's do something exciting.
- Like what?
- What are we playing?
- Come on.
- Let's play a game.
- Sure.
Mr. Chen, join us for a round.
Sure, just call me by my name.
Alright, Chen.
Who's the king?
Me.
For this round, let's skip the dares.
Truth.
Jing.
What's your type? Tell us.
Why are you coming for me right away?
Respect the rules.
- Respect the rules of the game.
- Hurry up, Jing.
We all drank. Yeah.
- Right, do what the king says.
- What, too shy?
- The King's word is law.
- Right.
Passionate.
Honest.
Trusting each other.
Willing to risk everything for each other.
Sounds kind of...
Why does this person look familiar?
Who is this guy, Jing?
I don't remember you naming Cen.
Why is he blushing?
You have to say the name.
- Is he here?
Is he here?
I'll take the penalty myself, okay?
Jing, you can't do that.
That was slick, boss.
What's going on? This is juicy.
- Come on, let's drink!
- Come on, next round, next round!
I'll let you guys off the hook. Next round.
- Eat up, eat up.
- This one, this one.
- Give me one.
- I want this one.
No, let's swap it.
Jing, hurry over.
Anything?
Not yet. We're still looking.
Hurry over.
Mr. Chen, you haven't sent her the car key.
You're too invested in your employees' lives.
I just wanted to remind you.
While the project is ongoing,
you should keep a proper distance.
Otherwise, you'll just cause problems
for Miao Jing.
Jing! There must be fish in there.
Let's go take a look. Everybody, be careful.
Where are you heading?
Over here. There must be some here.
In that crack between the rocks.
- Wait.
- Ma Yang!
If there aren't any, I'll kill you.
There are. Trust me.
- One, two!
- Come on.
- It's so high.
- There's one down there.
Where?
Over here.
- I'll go down first.
- Okay.
Careful.
Come on. Give me your hand.
I can't. I'm scared. It's too high.
I can't, Jing. Hurry.
It's too slippery. I can't get down.
It's okay. I'll catch you.
The tide's coming in. Get back here.
- It's dangerous!
- Let's go.
Everyone out there, the tide's coming in.
- Come back quickly!
- Are you okay?
What happened, Xiao Yu?
I twisted my ankle.
- I can't stand up.
- Jing, she's injured.
Stay where you are.
Due to stronger winds,
the tide will keep rising.
Please leave the beach as soon as possible.
- Pull her up.
- One, two... Three!
Careful.
Can you pull her up?
Hold on tight. One, two, three.
Careful.
Jing, come on.
I can't reach.
- Jing.
- Miao Jing.
The tide's coming in fast.
What are you going to do?
Take Xiao Yu back first and go get help.
- Okay. Be careful.
- Be careful.
Go.
Hold on to me.
- We'll have an extra dish for dinner.
- I don't think this is enough.
- Where's Miao Jing?
- We can catch more if it's not enough.
She isn't back yet?
Cen.
Cen, hurry.
- Where's Miao Jing?
- Jing is trapped down by the reef.
- Oh my god! What should we do?
- We need to find help.
- Chen! Chen! Chen!
- Mr. Chen.
Someone's trapped out on the reef flats.
Send a boat over right now.
I'll pay triple.
I'll take her to the infirmary first.
You take her back first.
- I'll help you.
- Easy.
Miao Jing, you have to be okay. You have to be.
Miao Jing.
We don't need to beg anyone.
From now on,
we'll be safe, and everything will work out.
I promise.
Okay.
Miao Jing.
Chen Yi.
Come on.
Miao Jing.
Grab my hand.
Chen Yi, are you out of your mind?
You swam over when the tide was coming in.
What if you'd been swept away?
Thank God you're okay.
Thank God.
It hurts.
Now you know it hurts?
Where did all that bravado go?
I couldn't just leave Xiao Yu there alone.
- I'm not like you...
- That's different!
Miao Jing, I'm not saying loyalty is wrong.
I'm just scared.
I can be selfish.
[Infirmary]
This might hurt a little.
For the next few days,
avoid foods that could aggravate it.
Try not to get the wound wet
until it scabs over.
No tendons or bones were damaged.
It's nothing serious.
One of you, come with me to get her medicine.
Who is coming with me?
I'll go.
- No.
- You...
- Just hang in there.
- Ma Yang, can you just make it quick?
Where's that decisiveness you had
when you slung me over your back?
Do this.
Put this on yourself for now.
I'll get you some painkillers. Chen has some.
- I'll go borrow some from him.
- Okay, go ahead.
- Where are you going?
- Boss.
I'm getting painkillers from Chen.
He's not here.
- Then I'll look for Jing.
- She's not here either.
Chen Yi.
Every time you save me,
what goes through your mind?
Honestly, nothing at all.
The longer I stop to think or hesitate,
the more danger you're in.
What about me?
When I'm in danger, you worry yourself sick.
And when you risk your life,
am I supposed to feel at peace?
Sometimes I really don't know
whether you're being noble or just selfish,
whether you love me that much
or don't know how to love me at all.
You remind me of a story I read as a kid.
The Happy Prince.
I'm like the sea witch.
You keep trading pieces of yourself away
first for my future, and now for my safety.
But you never got happiness in return.
The Happy Prince and the sea witch aren't
from the same story.
Chen Yi.
I used to think
that when I came back,
I could get you out of this place.
But I was wrong.
I only put you in greater danger.
I made you suffer more.
I chose all of this.
Close your eyes.
Chen Yi.
When will you learn to love yourself?
Miao Jing.
I just want you safe.
Qiao, I'm almost done here.
Dinner should be ready in about ten minutes.
Okay. We're almost done, too.
I was going to find time to stop by your shop.
I had nothing going on today,
so I just came by.
Did you add the WeChat contact I sent you?
Not yet.
Was he not right for you or something?
Qiao.
- Can I ask you something?
- Go ahead.
Does Chen Yi have a girlfriend?
I'm not really sure.
What's wrong?
Didn't you say before that a girl like you
could take it or leave it, free and easy?
Looks like you're not over him.
It's not that.
Are you close with Miao Jing?
Miao Jing?
I've met her a few times, but we're not close.
What are you two talking about?
Gossip. Want in? Is dinner ready?
Almost.
Try these beef balls.
Give her some beef balls. They're amazing.
They're all hand-pounded.
The beef was marinated well.
Try it.
Don't just talk. Try this.
Try the soup in a bit.
You made this soup yourself?
I think it's way better
than those store-bought hot pot bases.
Of course. I fattened her up myself,
one pound at a time.
What did you think?
I really got fat?
No.
Then why did you say that?
- I made it up.
- He's just teasing you.
This thing is still alive.
- You bought some really fresh stuff.
- Look, it's still moving.
Look, it's reaching out.
- Nice.
- Bo.
- Can I ask you something?
- Go ahead.
Are Miao Jing and Chen Yi dating or not?
I don't know if they are dating.
But I think if you want to
get back together with Yi,
it might be pretty tough.
So from what you're saying,
Yi has always been into Miao Jing.
What about Miao Jing? Does she like Yi, too?
I'm not inside their heads.
I don't know that much about them.
So they like each other,
but aren't together yet.
Then I still have a chance.
Li. This may sound a little harsh.
But Miao Jing really is different.
She's Yi's whole world.
Before, she was away in Hai City.
Now, not even a typhoon could split them up,
unless Miao Jing chooses to leave.
They're too far apart.
They're not the same kind of people.
But only they know what went on between them.
We're all outsiders.
There's no place for us in it.
Bo, my dipping sauce is a little salty.
Could you swap it for a can of Coke?
Go.
Have some more.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I'm okay. Thanks, Chen.
It's fine. Let's go.
The car's over there.
Who swore he'd never get seasick or carsick?
And now you're here puking
while leaning on Mr. Chen.
It's the change in climate, okay?
- Are you okay?
- Thank you. It's fine.
- Drink a little more.
- Chen. We still have room in our car.
No, I'll take this car. Get some rest.
What, afraid I'll puke in the car?
Get in.
Isn't it cramped sitting like that, Mr. Chen?
My eyes have been really dry lately.
Too much sea breeze.
If I sit up front, the light makes me tear up.
If you think it's cramped, take the front seat.
You've had a rough couple of days with us.
The front has a visor and more room.
It's better for resting. Perfect for you.
Enough.
Move.
I'll sit up front. You two rest in the back.
Let's go.
Mr. Cen.
Your hotel isn't on our way, is it?
We'll take her home first.
Then I'll head back to the hotel.
Thanks.
Use this.
My back is killing me from sitting.
Get some rest when you get home.
You too. See you.
Okay. See you at the office.
- Okay.
- One more thing...
Let's go, sir.
Okay.
[Miao's Album, Yesterday]
[A Dream I Never Want to Wake From]
When I'm in danger, you worry yourself sick.
And when you risk your life,
am I supposed to feel at peace?
Sometimes I really don't know
if you're being noble or just selfish,
whether you love me that much
or don't know how to love me at all.
Are you not feeling well today?
You look listless.
I made soup. Have some later.
I'm fine.
What's wrong with you?
Looks like it's about to rain.
I'll go bring in the laundry.
What did I do to upset her?
According to the weather service,
Super Typhoon Mota will make landfall
on our east coast tonight.
It will bring the heaviest rainfall
of the season.
Please close all doors and windows.
Do not go outside.
[You don't understand me at all.]
[We're going to be so happy together.]
[Wen got me a little gift. I love it!
Zhou and Wen came over for New Year! So happy!]
This is just for you.
I get a present too?
What?
This is a secret between us girls.
Boys aren't allowed to see it.
Happy New Year, Jing.
Happy New Year.
He's always been that resilient.
Maybe nothing can break him.
[Receipt]
Don't worry about the tuition bill.
I've got it covered.
Go pay your tuition.
Don't worry. It's clean money.
[He was covered in injuries again today.
I want him to stay safe and never get hurt.]
Do well on your exams.
After the college entrance exam,
I'll buy you a thicker chain.
At least this thick.
[You don't understand me at all.]
Chen Yi. Do you even understand?
The future you're breaking yourself to buy me
is too painful for me to hold.
[You don't understand me at all.
The future you're breaking yourself to...]
Chen Yi.
I used to think
that when I came back,
I could get you out of this place.
But I was wrong.
I only put you in greater danger.
I made you suffer more.
I chose all of this.
If I finally decide to let go,
will you stop getting hurt?