[Episode 23]
Chen Yi.
I don't want to hold you back anymore.
Let's end this here.
Goodbye.
Chen Yi.
- How did everything get flooded?
- Let's clean it up together.
I should've checked the doors and windows.
No, I forgot to close it
when I brought in the laundry.
It's not your fault. I wasn't paying attention.
Chen Yi, I left the window open.
Stop walking on eggshells around me.
I'm not made of glass.
Leave it there. I'll do it.
The rain's letting up.
Looks like it won't stop anytime soon.
Let's get some rest tonight.
We'll make do.
[Swimwear and Lingerie World]
I meant to throw it out,
but forgot where I put it.
Why are you panicking?
It's not like I haven't seen it.
When did you ever see it?
Didn't you always ask me to hide it for you?
Don't say it.
I'll give you half.
Chen Yi.
If this were our last day together,
what would you want to do?
I don't want this rain to become our problem.
I'm sorry.
I'm happy.
After I finish my audit,
will you still stay at Haoyun?
You've got everything covered.
Why would I need to stay?
I know what you're worried about.
Don't worry.
Wherever you go, I'll go with you.
Your job is dangerous.
Then I'll be your bodyguard for life, okay?
Let's talk about it tomorrow. I'm sleepy.
What are you doing?
Resting.
Don't you think
this position is a little weird?
Enough talking.
Close your eyes and sleep.
Rainy days are actually pretty nice.
Right?
- The window is broken. How is that nice?
- You can fix it.
Just sleep.
Hello. Routine inspection.
- Open the trunk, please.
- Okay.
This way.
- Hurry.
- Okay.
It's all just toys.
[Haoyun Logistics]
No problem. It's a routine inspection.
Okay.
- They're all toys, right? Nothing else?
- Yes, they're all toys.
- How is it? Any problems?
- No problem. Let them through.
Mr. Zhang, all the trucks cleared customs.
Don't worry.
Okay. Got it.
Looks like the results are very satisfying.
I heard the addendum Tao Jiang gave you
still hasn't been finalized.
Now the route is working smoothly.
Mr. Liu.
You aren't having second thoughts, are you?
It's just a few minor issues.
I'll have Legal send the contract back to you.
Then I'll wait for good news, Mr. Liu.
Once the goods are sold,
our options will only keep opening up.
I'd better stay sharp.
Mr. Zhang.
Otherwise, I'll end up like your old friend.
How is your listing coming along?
Didn't Hongshen arrange an audit for you?
It won't cause any trouble, will it?
I was worried before,
but I feel much better lately.
We should be listed very soon.
The Teng City to Lingang route is fine now.
But as for Country Jin...
I think we should play it safe.
The young man I met last time,
the one working under Kao.
For this trial run,
he'll be there the whole time, right?
We can't do this without him.
Mr. Zhang.
Since you're in Lingang,
I have a little gift for you.
The other one is for that young man.
How are the arrangements coming along?
Don't worry. Everything is set.
Anything on the books can stand scrutiny.
Hongshen's investment will arrive on time.
We've also spoken to the metal buyer.
Handle it as you see fit.
[Fengwei BBQ Restaurant]
Oh my goodness, this one is so heavy.
Bin.
Here.
I'll go now.
Thanks.
- I'll close it.
- All right.
By the way, Tao Jiang.
Pack me an order of roast goose noodles.
I heard from the drivers around here
that there's a great roast goose place
by Lingang Harbor.
I used to just hear about it and forget it.
Now that I'm in Lingang,
I'm actually craving it.
How are things with Chen Yi?
Just as you expected.
I'm afraid he isn't on our side at Haoyun.
Ding Lei's fall was tied to him, too.
I don't see it that way.
As long as those two are still
on the same page,
I can keep him on board.
In the next few days,
set up a dinner at Haoting.
Okay. I'm on it.
These are all done.
Jing.
The files are all organized.
Check if anything's wrong.
Now we're just waiting for approval.
We're finally done.
No one has to work late tonight.
Let's go eat something nice.
- What are we eating?
After I submit this for approval.
- Go ahead and choose.
- Any ideas?
- Let's get something more local.
- How about barbecue?
[Wait for me at home. I'll be back soon.]
Let's do barbecue.
I'm in. Barbecue.
- Let's take a vote.
- Okay.
- That works.
- Let's go.
I think that place is good.
Ms. Miao, Mr. Zhang is hosting dinner tonight.
I was wondering if you're free.
Only Jing is invited?
Sorry.
Our team has dinner tonight.
Sorry. I didn't know you already had plans.
But concerning the audit report,
Mr. Zhang wants to ask her about
some details about the freight section.
Our client is Hongshen Group, not Haoyun.
If Haoyun has concerns about our report,
they can call a public meeting.
I'll answer Mr. Zhang's questions there.
Will anyone else be at Mr. Zhang's dinner?
I'm not sure about the details.
He's senior to me. I can't just refuse.
Stay safe. Call me if anything happens.
You guys go ahead and eat.
Hello.
- Miao Jing was taken away by Zhang Bin.
- What?
Eat. Why isn't anyone picking up chopsticks?
Is Jing still coming?
Let's eat first.
She probably can't make it tonight.
Why would they suddenly call her away now?
Don't worry too much.
Maybe it's just a spur-of-the-moment idea.
And they only asked Jing out for dinner?
Then why are you shaking?
This dinner is a trap.
A high-ranking executive asking a girl out
to meet at a private club?
There's no way his intentions are innocent.
I think maybe Ding's team has messed up again.
Why else call Jing away right now?
There's nothing wrong with our reports.
Cen, how can you still eat?
What about Jing?
For now, everything is moving along.
And our standards are completely fair.
There is no obvious bias.
If anything, it is good news for Haoyun.
They have no reason to target Miao Jing.
Haoting, right? I'm going to find Jing.
Sit down. Don't get worked up.
Don't worry. The boss just said so.
- Sit down. It's fine.
- Calm down.
Come on, eat.
All right.
Your audit is almost finished.
I was thinking,
we should invite you over for a family dinner.
Let's see if we can work together more closely.
I've heard a lot about you, Mr. Zhang.
I've just been tied up with the audit.
Otherwise, I would have met you sooner.
You have quite a way with words, Ms. Miao.
Haven't we met before, Ms. Miao?
You remember me, Mr. Zhang?
Chen Yi and I grew up together.
I used to wait for him at District Seven.
If I'd known you'd seen me, I would've changed.
This outfit is too formal.
You really are something, Ms. Miao.
Chen Yi is something too.
You two really are something.
I heard you studied in Hai City.
Hai City is much better than Teng City.
Why come back?
I've always thought Teng City was better.
Mr. Zhang.
Chen Yi is here.
Let him in.
Mr. Zhang.
Looks like I picked a bad time.
What are you talking about?
Your sister is sitting right here. Have a seat.
You're joking, Mr. Zhang.
We only lived together for two or three years.
That hardly makes her my sister.
Why do you start talking nonsense
the second you walk in?
Ms. Miao, don't be mad at him.
But no matter how you look at it,
after all these twists and turns,
we're all back at the same table at Haoyun.
That has to mean something.
Whether this project gets finished smoothly
depends on both of you.
That's too much, Mr. Zhang.
We're just employees.
Whether the project succeeds is up to you.
So what if you're employees?
The two of you are the most important people
to Haoyun and to me.
Ms. Miao, do you know something?
There is a new logistics chain this time.
One section of it had a missing link.
But with your brother on board,
this chain can finally close the loop.
Don't be fooled by all that modest talk.
He is genuinely good at what he does.
Oh, I almost forgot.
The tea snacks over there
are especially for you.
They made a point of saying that
since you're in charge of this route,
you should give it extra attention
and go along on the route more often.
When you get back,
I'll make up your vacation days.
Take your sister around
Teng City's new landmarks.
Mr. Zhang.
If I remember correctly,
the new logistics route you mentioned
is the one to Southeast Asia.
You've really done your homework, Ms. Miao.
Yes.
Chen Yi.
You need to step it up.
Make sure that the route runs smoothly.
If you keep dragging your feet, who knows
how long your sister will be stuck at Haoyun.
Okay.
Kao has already sent word.
Really?
That's great.
When you get over there,
you can catch up with them.
Miao.
If you're busy today, you can head back first.
Looks like this family dinner
is a bit too sudden.
I'll invite you properly another day.
Sure. I'll wait to hear from you, Mr. Zhang.
It's just not easy to get back downtown
from here tonight.
I'll wait and go with my brother.
Okay.
It's safer for siblings to go home together.
Come on. A toast to you both.
- Tea instead of wine, then.
- Okay.
Why did you come?
Don't you know what kind of man he is?
You're already in charge of auditing Haoyun.
What if he asks you
to do something out of line?
Besides, you shouldn't have
let him know we're connected.
If he could get me there,
that means he already knows about us.
There's no point hiding it from him.
Do you think, to Zhang Bin,
a junior auditor like me has any value?
After years in the real world,
you should know how it works.
He was just using me to bait you.
What are you doing?
Nothing. Just tidying up.
It's getting cold. Dry your hair.
What are you doing?
Where are you going?
Fall has come to Teng City.
Where are you going with summer clothes?
The freight department is sending me on a trip.
So where are they sending you?
Lingang. Just for two or three days.
Chen Yi. You said you'd never lie to me, right?
Did Zhang Bin send you?
Who is Kao, the man you mentioned that night?
Are you going to Country Jin?
Owen.
How did you know?
So this is what you've been hiding from me?
- Did Zhang Bin tell you?
- You're not going anywhere tomorrow.
Some things are better left unknown.
- Miao Jing, what are you doing now?
- I'm sleeping here tonight.
Chen Yi.
Whatever you went through before,
it's over now.
I don't want to keep asking about it.
But tomorrow.
- You can't go anywhere.
- It's not what you think.
I was in Country Jin those years.
- But I knew right from wrong.
- I believe you.
Then can you not go tomorrow?
I'll be back soon.
I heard that line six years ago.
My eye has been twitching all day.
Can you stay home?
I'll be back tomorrow,
before the scores come out.
Pinky swear.
Pinky swear. No changing for a hundred years.
If you do, we'll never see each other again.
You're not going anywhere.
Try me if you don't believe it.
[Chen Yi]
[Wait for me at home. I'll be back soon.]
Chen Yi.
So you're Chen?
No wonder you run border routes.
You used to work for Kao, right?
Is that because you did something big before,
and now you can't clear customs normally?
So you have to take a boat to Lingang,
and then head to Country Jin.
Otherwise, the sea route is way too rough.
Are those goods legit?
Don't put me on the spot.
How would I know what the boss is shipping?
We're just hired hands.
Biao.
Don't take it personally. Just routine.
You'll get it back when we disembark.
That boat will reach Lingang in 40 minutes.
The higher-ups told me to transport
those goods to Country Jin.
What do you mean?
The goods aren't on board?
Of course.
The goods already went to Lingang
with those trucks.
Chen.
Let's go.
This isn't what we agreed on.
Hello, I'd like to report a crime.
A group has gathered for a fight.
I don't know anything else.
I only know the plate number and names.
The plate number is Teng SFA302.
Name.
Chen Yi.
Quit stalling, Chen.
If we don't leave now, the tide will rise.
Then getting out will be tough.
Why would I leave without the goods?
No wonder you run the border waters.
You've got guts.
I don't know what you're thinking.
I have to finish the job
the higher-ups gave me.
I was told to bring you in.
In half an hour, you have to be there.
Your boss has watched too many gangster films,
thinking he can send you bastards to mouth off.
Police.
Stay right where you are.
Local police.
Don't move.
You're suspected of illegal fishing.
Show me your papers.
Identification.
You guys...
What are you doing gathered here?
I...
Officer.
They're on a cargo ship from Lingang.
I'm the freight manager at the logistics firm.
I came tonight to check the ships.
Nothing else.
Is that right?
Yes.
No one leaves.
We need full statements from everyone.
Officer.
They're on a cargo ship from Lingang.
I'm the freight manager at the logistics firm.
I'm just here to check the ships today.
So, can we leave now?
Biao, let's go.
- Get in.
- Okay.
Get in.
Their cargo isn't on the ship.
This time, they're just testing the route.
They even kept me in the dark.
They threw up a smokescreen.
We'll counter them move for move.
As for the follow-up,
leave it to the task force.
Most likely,
they'll think we've put our focus
on the waterways.
So they'll be more likely
to make their move by land.
I'm not worried about tipping them off.
I'm worried they won't take the bait.
Wasn't the operation set for 9:30?
Why did you get here early?
Someone reported that
you were involved in a fight here.
Miao Jing called it in.
She wanted me to come arrest you.
Aren't you scared?
If she'd called the police,
I wouldn't be in your car right now.
She called Zhou's private line.
She wouldn't actually want me locked up.
You're a lucky guy.
She was worried you'd get hurt.
Go back and thank her properly.
Drive.
Miao Jing.
Why is it you?
[Zhang Bin: You got investigated?]
[Zhang Bin: What's going on?]
Over here.
Where's Xiao Yu?
Disappointed to see me?
Just surprised.
I helped her with some data adjustments
in exchange for this errand to pick you up.
That's a bad trade.
Your professional instincts are slipping.
I'd call that going above and beyond.
Come in.
How long are you planning to stay here?
I'll probably stay here
until I go back to Hai City.
Everyone must be pretty happy about that.
Xiao Yu and Ma Yang are over there.
I'm staying over here.
We're all on this floor.
If anything comes up, just call.
Thanks.
Get some rest.
Chen Yi.
If this were our last day together,
what would you want to do?
I brought you some fruit.
Miao Jing isn't home?
She's away on a work trip.
I meant to come by a couple of days ago.
But Bao had a fever, so I couldn't get away.
Is the kid doing better now?
Much better.
Want some noodles?
I already ate.
Yi.
Do you remember how you used to say
you hated girls going into your kitchen?
What are you doing here?
Is something wrong at home?
No.
I just came to ask you something.
On Bo's wedding day,
you wanted to stand with Miao Jing, right?