This series is crafted for the purpose of entertainment.
All characters, behaviors, settings, and events depicted in this drama are entirely fictitious.
They are not designed to allude to any particular entity, occupation, or group of people.
Viewer discretion is advised.
[North Star Entertainment]
[7HD Channel]
[iQIYI]
[Present]
♫Where’s that love people are saying?♫
♫To always be by each other’s sides♫
♫The love that’s willing to sacrifice everything♫
♫Everything even my own life♫
♫Do they really exist? I’d rather not believe it♫
♫I don’t think I’ll ever fall for anyone♫
♫Love? I don’t find it interesting♫
♫Sorry about that♫
♫But then who are you?♫
♫To make my heart keep fluttering♫
♫Please tell me♫
♫What’s happening with my heart?♫
♫It can’t be, why am I feeling this?♫
♫Oh, my heart is pounding so fast♫
♫Time freezes whenever I see you♫
♫I wonder why every time you smile♫
♫Something in your eyes make me go weak♫
♫Oh no, this is real–it’s not a dream♫
♫Or is the love that people are saying...♫
♫Is it you?♫
[Flaming Chains of Love]
[Previously]
This is Mum’s house. You’re not allowed to bring your new lover here.
I’ve never said I’ll bring my new lover here.
If not a lover, then who the hell is she?
Long time no see, Buffalo Fai.
What if one day, she tries to seduce him for his money?
Over my dead body then.
I’m going to help you at work–but only on one condition.
You have to let Kaphrao be my assistant.
Deal.
From now on, you have to do whatever I say because I’m now officially your boss.
I can’t believe you’re really teaching me some work.
The dump truck tickets are with Uncle Yod. Can you go get them for me?
Get them from where?
Behind that mountain over there.
How do you expect me to go there?
Probably by feet.
Walk? Are you crazy? It’s freaking hot and far.
Please. Think of it as your first assignment.
But it’s hot as hell!
Slacking off right on your first day–Dad really overrated you.
So?
Make the whole ground flat so it’d be easier for us to get the stones up there
and bring them down here.
Uncle Yod!
Oh! Miss Kaphrao!
What are you doing here? It’s dangerous.
Fai told me to get the dump truck tickets from you.
I already gave them to her.
What?
But she said she doesn’t have them.
Here, look. I already sent them.
You did?
Why the heck did she tell me to come here then?
That jerk!
Oops, sorry. They’re here.
I totally forgot he already sent me.
I wanted to call but I don’t have your number.
Never mind.
But thanks anyway. Look at your face–so greasy.
Is there anything you want me to do, Miss Buffalo Fai?
Hmm, let me think.
Can you count the rocks in these two piles?
Our client wants to know the amount.
Is that how you usually do it?
Yes, if it’s not a big purchase.
You sell it by piece?
Yes, we sell in retail too.
You keep finding excuses because you don’t want to do it, don't you?
It’s just your first day and you’re getting lazy already. I’m going to tell Dad.
Fine!
Hang on, Miss Phrao. What are you doing?
I’m counting rocks.
Counting rocks? That’s not how we do it.
We sell them by tons, not by pieces.
What?
Look there. See that?
They’ll scoop up the whole pile onto the dump truck and weigh them. That’s it.
That’s it…
That’s it?
That’s how we do it if it’s not a big purchase.
We sell in retail too.
Buffalo Fai!
You must be exhausted today.
Yes, but I’ve learnt a lot of things.
Thank you so much indeed.
No problem.
Please let me drive.
You’re the boss. It’s me who should be the driver.
Come, just sit back and relax.
It’s okay, I can drive.
It’s all right. You’ve been working all day.
There, go on.
Buffalo Fai!
Can’t you go faster?
The turtle is probably biting on our tyre now.
Well, I’m sleepy.
I was out in the sun and did the labour work all day.
But don’t worry though.
I’m okay. I can drive.
Look at yourself first. Are you sure we’ll get home today?
Come and drive it yourself then.
So ungrateful.
Why is she sulking?
Hey!
I know what you’re thinking, you silly Gremlin.
You wanted to trick me to get out of the car and left me here, didn’t you?
No! All you can think of is finding a way to get back at me!
Aren’t you like that too?
No, I’m not!
How did she know?
Hey! Let me get in! Hey!
Do you hear me? Hey! Let me get in!
Unlock the door! Let me get in! Hey!
Apologise first.
For what?
For trying to trick me earlier.
Why did you pick on me–
There! You just admit it.
Stay outside then.
It’s a bit hot though.
Fine! Sorry, Fai!
Say it nicely and politely–”I’m sorry, Miss Fai.”
Are you going to say it? Fine, not saying it, huh?
Okay, okay! I’ll say it! Let me get in!
I’m sorry, Miss Fai!
Can’t hear you.
Dad said you used to take a dance class and did quite well too. Show me a bit then.
You’re going too far!
Or do you want to walk back? It’s hot though.
Boiling hot.
Come on, show me.
I’ll film it too.
The view in the background is just perfect.
I’ll save the clip to recheck later if you’re doing it right.
Just you wait.
Don’t let me wait too long then.
Hurry up. It’s hot.
Let’s go!
That’s it? Is that all they taught you?
Yeah.
Make it stronger.
Step back a little. I need a full-body view for the clip.
Just you wait!
Make it cute, can’t you? That’s not cute.
Come and do it yourself then!
Enough?
More.
Make it stronger. An old lady next door can even do better.
Geez, you!
Wanna walk back?
What? Tired already?
Yeah, that’s right. See? You can actually do it
Sorry, my dad’s probably gone to bed by now.
I don’t think you can complain about me today.
Look, I’m all grown up.
I’m not gonna waste my time doing something nonsense like that.
Don’t forget to shower when you get home.
You’re stinking so bad I almost gag.
The scent is still there.
Stinking? Smell it then!
Smell it! Go on!
- Smelly Guinea Pig!
- Eat this!
Get off me! That’s gross!
Come here, baby! Why are you running away?
Geez, stinky, huh?
Yuck! I really stink.
I’m having goosebumps, brrr!
Fai, why are you back so late, dear. I’ve been waiting to eat with you.
I’m sorry, Auntie. I forgot to call that I’d be late.
There was a little problem on our way back.
Has Kaphrao caused you any trouble?
Not at all.
If that girl ever does anything to upset you, you can always tell me. I’ll go deal with her.
It’s all right, Auntie, I can handle it. I’m a big girl now. I won’t let anyone pick on me so easily.
Actually, Ak has so many businesses.
Why does he have to send Kaphrao to work here?
And even work with you.
I really don’t know what he’s thinking.
But isn’t it better to keep her here?
How?
So that she’ll always be in our sight.
If Dad had sent her to live outside, we wouldn’t have known when he went to see her or do anything with her.
I’ve never liked this girl, from the very first moment.
When you were still under my care, I had never once raised my hand to you.
But when Ak brought this girl into the house, everyday was troublesome.
Ak always punished you, my dear.
He never once raised a hand to that Gremlin. Whatever she did just pleased him.
Unlike me, whatever I did was wrong in his eyes.
I’m always on your side, dear.
There’s only you who loves me the most.
But don’t worry, that girl won’t be here for long.
Let’s eat.
Eat up. They’re all your favourites.
Thank you.
Throw it away.
Yes, Young Master.
Hey, hold on!
Stop!
What are you doing with my bike?
Throwing it away.
Didn’t my dad give it to you?
That means you didn’t own it in the first place.
Are you nuts? It’s still in good condition, why would you throw it away?
Piak, throw it away!
But, Young Master–
Piak!
Yes, Young Master.
You!
Are you having fun?
Absolutely.
Maniac!
But if you give up and beg me nicely, I might consider giving you a ride.
You need to work at the office today, don’t you?
No need. I have legs, I can walk.
But it’s far, are you sure you can walk there?
It’s better than going with you!
These are accounting records from previous years. Young Master said you must go through all of them.
All of them–
Geez, her manners.
Young Master said you can’t go home if you don’t finish it today.
Sure, this is nothing.
I’ll definitely get it done today.
That’s not all.
Here are records of every main and subsidiary business that the Master owns.
Yes?
Young Master said if you think you can’t do it…
Then come and beg me. I’ll be waiting upstairs.
Go tell your Young Master that this is a piece of cake for me.
Bullsh*t.
Geez, just like her boss.
I heard that day when you took her to the mine, you made her count rocks and do the labour work under the sun.
I just want to help her practise patience.
Practise patience?
By throwing her bike away and letting her walk to work,
and even make her work until late at night?
Are you sure you’re not picking on her again?
Did that Gremlin rat me out again?
It doesn’t matter who told me.
I left her in your care because I wanted you to train her at work–
not to use her as your emotional dumpster.
Is that all you have to say to me?
I’m warning you, you should know when to stop.
What if anything happens to her again like that time, what will you do?
You still remember it, right?
So what? I don’t care.
Huh, Miss Phrao?
You’re still here?
I’m still not done. There’s a lot more to do.
Are you here to close up the office?
Yes. Why don’t you just leave it for tomorrow?
It’s dangerous to walk home alone this late.
I’ll give you a ride.
It’s all right. Judging from the amount of work, I guess I’ll have to pull an all-nighter.
Well then, are you sure?
Yes.
Then, please lock the back door for me when you leave.
Oh, sure.
I'm leaving now.
Goodnight.
She’s still working?
Yes, are you sure you’re going to leave her there alone?
It’s dark and deserted around there at night.
She wants to stay there herself. It’s not like I’ve forced her.
But she doesn’t have her bike with her.
And it looks like it’s going to rain too.
If you’re worried this much, why don’t you just drop her home?
I already offered but she refused to go home.
If she’s so stubborn, just leave her be.
I’m hanging up.
Fai, is everything okay? I saw you came back a while ago.
Who were you talking to on the phone?
I was discussing work with Uncle Yod.
It’s late, why aren’t you in bed yet, Auntie?
I was about to turn in but I’m waiting for you to come home first.
We might have a good dream tonight. Looks like it’s going to rain. It’s been pretty cloudy since evening.
Let’s go, dear.
I’ve been knitting all day long.
Then, let’s get some sleep.
So that we’ll have a good dream.
Okay then.
Sweet dream, Auntie.
I’ll shower and go to bed too.
Yes, dear.
[Yod]: Are you sure you’re going to leave Miss Phrao there alone, Young Master?
It’s dark and deserted around there at night.
She doesn’t have her bike with her.
And it looks like it’s going to rain too.
[Akanee]: I’m warning you, you should know when to stop.
What if anything happens to her again like that time, what will you do?
You still remember, right?
Can’t you just give in for once? You silly Gremlin.
Does she want to die buried under a pile of work for real?
Geez, why now?
Panel board…
Boo!
Sh*t!
Fai!
Damn it, I’m bleeding.
What’s so funny?
If my face is ruined, I’ll kill you.
Who told you to pull a prank on me then?
I got startled and had to protect myself.
Can’t you be more gentle? Try to behave more like a lady.
Serve you right. If you don’t like it, then just do it yourself.
No.
You’re the cause so you must take responsibility.
Stop whining.
Stay still.
Did you do that on purpose to get back at me?
Think whatever you want. I’d rather not cast my pearls before swine.
Hey! Did you just call me a pig?
You have to be the last to laugh every time, huh?
It’s you who’re like that.
You were like that when you were young, and you’ve never changed at all.
Who would be like you? You’ve grown up and become another person completely.
How?
When you were little, you were so weak and kept crying all the time.
You clung on to me all the time, it was so annoying.
Get off me.
No, I’m scared.
Don’t you want a doll? I’m taking you to get your doll.
I don’t want it anymore. I’m scared.
If you don’t stop crying, I’ll leave you here alone.
Fai, don’t leave me!
Fai!
Did you take her to play outside again? It’s late.
No, Dad. I just took her to see–
Then, why is she crying?
I told you not to pick on your sister. Haven’t I told you so many times already?
But Dad, I didn’t do anything to her!
Don’t you dare lie to my face!
If you do it again, I’ll punish you. Consider it a warning.
Are you all right, sweetie?
I’ll take you to bed. It’s okay, now.
Don’t be scared, dear.
You were a crybaby–crying over every little thing.
That’s why I got scolded off by my dad all the time.
But look at you now, kicking and punching like a thug.
And even love to use your fists to fix problems.
People do change over time.
Who would’ve been consistently awful like you?
That’s why I really want to know–what made you change this much?
It’s you.
Kaphrao.
Is it because I’m weak? Is that why Big Sis always picks on me?
From now on, I’ll be strong. I’ll never let Big Sis do that to me again.
Yes, sweetie.
You have to be strong.
You must be strong.
All the documents are correct. We’ll show you to your room in a moment.
Thank you.
You’ll be staying here from now on.
They’ll teach you to be strong and look after yourself.
But there isn’t Uncle or Big Sis here.
You must be a good girl and study hard for your future.
I’ll come visit you every weekend, I promise.
Once you graduate and are big enough to handle her, I’ll come take you home.
Be a good girl, sweetie.
Finally, I can bring you back home.
Don’t worry, I’ll take the best care of her.
Kaphrao.
I’ll go there early to finish off the work tomorrow.
Forget it, you don’t need to do it anymore.
Huh? But Miss Duangnate said it’s your order.
And I’m giving you an order now, can’t you understand human language, Guinea Pig?
Fine! I get it.
Wait.
What now? Are you going to pick on me again?
Here.
Does it have holes?
No, hurry up and get out.
Huh? No holes indeed.
Did I punch her too hard her brain has fallen out? Why so kind all of a sudden?
Yeah, yeah, I get it!
Fai.
It’s pouring outside, where did you rush off to, dear?
Oh, I left something at the office so I just went there to get it.
I thought you were already in bed, Auntie.
Well, I heard your car leaving.
Let’s go to bed then.
Hold on, what happened to your lips?
Oh, I wasn’t looking and walked into the door at the office.
But judging from the wound, it doesn’t look that way.
I really bumped into the door, Auntie.
Come on, let’s go to bed. I’m sleepy now.
Be more careful next time, dear.
Okay, I’ll be more careful.
I’ll apply some cream for you.
Was that a hand or an elephant's foot?
Boo!
Sh*t!
My lips are bleeding.
She probably ran to tell Miss Panee everything by now.
Her lips must be swollen so bad.
All right guys, I’m going to start now.
This one is a flared skirt with floral print. It’s for 50 baht only!
Oh! Mr. Kittisak just confirmed it.
Thank you so much. What? You want to buy it for your girlfriend?
Aww, so romantic! It’s yours now!
And here, I proudly present this one. They were what I wore when I got drunk with Princess Blew of Madelin.
I’ll sell them for only 300 baht.
Hang on, let’s make it 500 then–500 baht!
Sorry, Bua.
It’s all right. Guys, I’ll just take a little break first.
Miss Phrao.
What are you doing?
I’m selling my clothes on livestream for extra income.
I see.
By the way, why are you up so early today? Are you heading out to work now?
I need to walk there so I have to leave a bit early.
Why don’t you use my bike then?
I’d rather not do that. If Fai finds out, you might be in trouble.
You’re right.
Young Master is so mean to you. She’s never been this harsh to other workers.
Usually, she’s very kind–not someone unreasonable like this.
I think she’s probably misunderstood something about you.
So pretty. Is it pricey?
Only 50 baht.
I’m used to it. When we were just kids, she was always like this too.
No matter what I did was wrong. Just the fact that I’m breathing is already wrong.
But I’m sure Young Master will finally understand it one day.
Trust me.
She’s narrow-minded, self-absorbed, and pigheaded like a frog in the well. She’d never understand anything, Bua.
Who are you calling pigheaded?
I gotta go.
Okay.
Hey! Wait!
I’m back, guys. Let’s continue, shall we?
I said it’s for 500 earlier, right?
But since I’m quite moody now, let’s make it 1,000 then.
Guinea Pig, get in the car.
No need. I can walk.
We’re going to work somewhere else today.
Where then?
Don’t ask. Just get in the car.
Of course, I have to ask.
What if you plan to sell me out or murder me?
I need to be sure someone will find my body.
You’re being delulu.
And you can’t be trusted.
Get in the car! That’s an order and it’s during working hours now.
You have to do as I say, understood?
Get in!
Fine!
Uncle Yod, I’m going outside with Fai.
If I’m not back within three hours, please tell Uncle and report it to the police.
What are you looking at?
Nothing.
Why did you stare at me?
The wound is almost healed. It’s barely visible now.
It shouldn’t have been there in the first place.
You were being childish with that stupid prank first.
You still have the nerve to blame it on someone else?
Use this, so it’ll heal faster.
Hey, do we have to meet the client here?
No.
Then, why are you taking me here?
I thought you said we’ll be working out of the office today.
Can you stop asking questions, Guinea Pig?
No, not until you stop acting suspicious.
Follow me if you want to know.
Quickly!
Hello, there.
Go ahead and pick what you like. We have it from a thousand to ten thousand baht.
Are you going to use it for delivery or exercising?
Go and pick one.
A bike?
Mhm, do you think they’re oxcarts?
It’s to replace the old one that I threw away.
So that you won’t have another excuse to complain to my dad.
I don’t want it.
What’s so different whether a father or a daughter pays for it?
It is!
Uncle might be rich but he is careful with his money and knows how to spend.
But you, you threw away a bike that’s still in good condition.
And you don’t even feel guilty about it.
Are you done?
Yes! And if that’s all you want from me, then I’m going back.
Let me go.
Or else you’ll get hurt.
Don’t make a fuss.
If you want to go back, just go and pick one.
It’s not like I want to be here.
As if I begged you to take me here.
Stop complaining and hurry up.
I don’t want to stay close to you for even a minute–it’s annoying!
You’re annoying too!
You both are annoying!
Are you going to buy it or not?
So?
Hurry up!
So fussy.
Why bother? It’s not like I want it.
Thanks, girl.
Can you take it to the car for me?
Sure.
Saw! Come and take this bike to her car.
Yes, Boss.
That’s it.
So, do you want to go anywhere or buy anything else?
Hey, are you done? You should have some manners.
Why the hell would you ask me if I wanted to buy anything?
And look, I’m buying them for your office.
If you don’t want to be here, go and wait in the car.
I was just asking. What’s wrong with her?
Does she have a hole in her mouth or what?
‘Buffalo Fai, control freak’.
‘Buffalo Fai, nasty mouth’
‘Buffalo Fai, bloody Monkey’s Flea’.
Did you just curse at me?
No, just testing the pen. Don’t start it.
But I saw you writing something. Let me see.
Here, Granny.
Hey, I’m done. Didn’t you say you want to hurry home?
Did you write this for me?
‘Stealing a glance at you’.
What? I didn’t write that!
That’s not mine.
Auntie, I don’t want them anymore.
Hey, what’s the rush? Don’t you want them anymore?
[Humming] Stealing a glance at you…
See you later, Granny.
Is your butt growing roots?
Why am I doing everything when I’m the one who paid for it?
Who told you to buy it then?
Young Master!
Oh, wow! Your new bike is looking fabulous, Miss Kaphrao.
I bought it but it seems someone around here is being ungrateful.
The old one still works fine but someone lunatic just threw it away.
Oh, actually, the old one was already worn out.
Its chain often fell off. I tried to fix it many times but it didn’t work.
Young Master thought it’d be dangerous if you kept using it, so she told Piak to throw it away.
I was only afraid that if you fell off that bike, you might run to Dad and fake being a victim to get him on your side.
That’s why I bought you a new one just to get it over with.
You and your ugly thoughts!
The Master wants both of you to eat with him at the main house.
He needs to talk to you about something.
Eat up, girls.
Fai, you’ll attend the grand opening of Nam’s new resort, right?
I want you to take Kaphrao with you too.
What? Why should I take this Gremlin with me?
Well, I want her to go see things and also get to know your siblings.
Wake up, Dad. She’s not related to us.
Why should she get to know my siblings?
Isn’t it better to be acquainted? Who knows–we might find it useful in the future.
But I don’t want to take her with me–it’s a burden!
I don’t want to go with her either!
Who said I’d take you with me?
Uncle, please let me stay here to help you with work.
All right, all right. Fine.
If you don’t want to go, then let’s do that. I’m not gonna force you, okay?
Thank you.
While Fai is away, I’ll help coach you at work instead, is that good?
That’s great.
Eat up then.
Yes.
I’ve changed my mind.
I’m going to take the Guinea Pig to Hua Hin with me.
Hey, that’s all right. I won’t force you if you don’t want to do it.
But I’m happy to do it.
Good then, if you say so.
Take her with you to Hua Hin too, okay?
- Okay.
- Look after her too.
I’ll take good care of her.
Come, let’s eat then.
The crispy omelette smells so good.
Here, try it, Little One.
I was about to try it.
Thanks, Dad.
You were?
That’s fine. I’ll get you another one.
I want more.
Fine, you want more.
Take the whole plate then.
Can I?
Why not? Hey!
Really, you two.
Have a safe trip, girls.
[Next Episode]
Finally, what took you so long?
Someone’s been dawdling.
Are you two dating?
No!
I’d rather stay single for the rest of my life than have this Gremlin as my girlfriend.
Isn’t she pretty, Fai?
Yes–I mean, she’s okay but not that pretty.
Phrao! Are you Kaphrao?
Nod! Hey!
Nod, stop it. Don’t make a scene.
I’m tired. I want to go home now.
Then, let’s go talk in your room after this.
Okay, sure!
♫I still remember vividly that day when we first met♫
♫Those memories we had together never fade away from my heart♫
♫We might never say it out loud how we feel for each other♫
♫But deep down we both know how we feel♫
♫Those things in the past, I still can’t forget them♫
♫I want to know if you’re like that too–do you also feel the same?♫
♫I could never forget those eyes of yours♫
♫The warmth you used to give me, I still remember it vividly♫
♫No matter for how long, you’ll always remain in my heart♫
♫All those years I’ve been waiting, for us to finally be together again♫
[North Star Entertainment]
[Flaming Chains of Love]