This is the Lu Family estate.
Can any random nobody just waltz in here?
Someone, throw him out right now!
You've got no say in Lu Family matters.
Mr. Ren.
May I give it a try?
Please.
Done.
Impressive technique!
I couldn't even see how he made the cut.
That's incredible.
He's really skilled.
How is that possible?
Mr. Ren,
is your surgical skill a family tradition?
From the Chinese clinic, Premier Medical Hall?
Don't be ridiculous.
Chinese clinics never perform surgery.
China had cranial surgery back in the Shang and Zhou dynasties.
In the second century AD,
Hua Tuo of the Han Dynasty
performed the world's first abdominal surgery under general anesthesia.
Europe didn't adopt anesthetic surgery until the 19th century.
Chinese medicine mastered surgery a thousand years before Europe.
Well said.
However,
the Ancient Chinese Medical Arts I've studied
don't require surgery
to cure Elder Lu's eyes.
A physician mustn't speak recklessly.
If anything goes wrong,
do you know the consequences?
Of course.
Elder Lu suffers from liver and kidney deficiency,
lacking vital essence,
which has deprived the eyes of nourishment,
forming internal cataracts.
To treat cataracts with acupuncture,
needles are inserted into the Jingming, Cuanzhu, and Taiyang points.
The liver governs the eyes; the kidney governs essence.
Acupuncture regulates and restores,
using the nature of the needle
to stimulate liver and kidney energies,
thereby nourishing the liver and kidney,
clearing the ocular channels,
and restoring sight.
The final step:
from the Ancient Chinese Medical Arts,
the Golden Spatula Cataract Surgery.
How is it?
Dad,
can you see now?
I can see.
I can see now!
I can see!
Amazing.
Truly astonishing.
Incredible.
Young man,
I owe it all to you.
Thank you, thank you.
Jianqi, thank him for me.
Mr. Ren, please.
Please,
first deliver the patent license,
then treat my father.
I don't believe this is a coincidence.
Delivering the patent license,
I do have an agenda.
But in treating your father,
I have no ulterior motive.
It's simply a healer's conscience.
Good.
I like sincere, clever people.
What do you want?
What I want
is trivial for you.
I want to join Beisheng'an Hospital.
That's all?
Do you know what this license
you gave me represents?
Last year,
your proprietary Chinese respiratory medicine,
in South City,
within one year of launch,
the distributor closed three funding rounds.
The entire South City Chamber of Commerce
was commended because of this drug.
Bringing them unmatched glory.
Now you're giving it to me,
asking only to join Beisheng'an Hospital.
As chairman of North City's Medical Association,
you founded Lubei Pharmaceutical last year
out of dissatisfaction with a few oligarchs
using foreign capital to monopolize the market.
So this license of mine
shares the same purpose as yours,
to change the gloom over North City's medical industry.
Good.
Well said.
Actually, your father Ren Fanghai and I go way back.
In private, don't call me chairman anymore.
Just call me Uncle Lu.
Alright, Uncle Lu.
At Beisheng'an Hospital,
what position do you think would suit you?
Hello, Director Ren.
Thank you all for your kindness.
Everyone, get back to work.
Alright, let's go.
Not bad, kid.
Just got out and you're already my boss.
It was easier than I thought.
By the way, Senior Brother.
There's something I need your help with.
Starting today, keep a close eye on Ren Feifan.
I want to see how long he can keep this up.
Don't go easy on Ren Feifan.
Do I make myself clear?
What exactly are you trying to find?
The Wang Family stole a prescription from us back then.
But I don't know exactly which one.
A prescription.
So you spent the whole day checking
the herb usage at the new drug research center
to figure out what herbs were in that prescription?
That's right.
Isn't that like finding a needle in a haystack?
By the way, Senior Brother.
You were familiar with our family's situation back then.
Can you guess which prescription it was?
I don't know either.
Alright.
You should head back first.
I'll keep looking for a while.
Okay, but don't stay too late.
This can't be rushed.
Don't wear yourself out.
File corrupted.
Hello, is this the archives?
Hello.
Do you have the paper copy of ZXR 1158?
Oh, yes, we do.
Great, I'll come pick it up now.
Okay.
Hello?
The nurse in the archive room passed out.
But it's nothing serious.
Come up and take care of it.
Got it.
Stop right there!
Stop!
Shen Yue.
Long time no see, Feifan.
Hand over what you just stole.
Why are you being so rough?
You're hurting me.
You're accusing me of stealing?
What did I steal?
Director.
If you don't believe me,
you're welcome to search me.
Hand it over.
Feifan.
Those are just the hospital's public records.
They're of no use to you.
Shen Yue, don't make trouble for me.
Otherwise...
Otherwise what?
You're welcome.
Okay, got it.
It's all up to you then.
Mm.
The newly appointed Director Ren Feifan
I'll go feel him out
Ma-ma'am, are you all right?
I think I sprained my ankle.
Let me take a look.
That hurts!
It hurts so much!
Your ankle is fine.
Just try to wear high heels less.
But it really hurts.
Could you take me home?
I've got a fierce wife at home.
It's not very appropriate.
Why are you so boring?
I've got things to do.
You'd better ask someone else.
How dull.
So guarded... Something's definitely off.
These are the Li family's herb supply records.
But it doesn't say who the herbs were supplied to.
Sichuan Aconite Root and Pinellia Rhizome are toxic herbs containing aconitine.
Their harvest has been strictly banned.
These herbs...
only started appearing in records four years ago.
They must be linked to the prescription the Wang Family stole.
Hey, Da Zhuang.
I need you to look into something for me.