What are you doing here?
I saw online this is a popular photo spot. I came to take photos.
Photo spot? What photo spot?
This is private property. No entry.
Just a few photos.
No.
Get lost, get lost!
Okay.
Where did that idiot come from?
Tell me about it.
Hey, Da Zhuang.
Hello, Master.
I've been to every herb source.
Only one place is heavily guarded.
There's no way to get in.
Where?
Lijia Village.
Seems Shen Yue wasn't lying to me.
Yes, Master. Come over and I'll lead the way.
No need.
Just go check on Ren Ran at the nursing home for me.
I'm quite worried about her.
When she's better, bring her back.
Okay, Master.
But she keeps glaring at me with those big eyes. It's creepy.
I bet she still prefers Senior Brother Wu.
She's had it so hard all these years.
Thankfully Senior Brother Wu took care of her.
How many days have you even looked after her?
Okay.
Second Uncle.
My surname may be Shen,
but I'm still a member of the Li Family.
How my mother died back then,
you know better than I do.
Feifan.
Why are you here?
Missing me already?
Take me to Lijia Village.
I've checked the USB evidence.
The key is in Lijia Village.
Well, since you want my help,
what do I get out of it?
You handed me the evidence against the Li Family.
Wasn't it to use me
to help you destroy the Li Family?
So if that's the case,
with this favor,
are you going to help me or not?
Feifan.
I want to talk to you.
I have nothing to say to you.
Feifan.
Feifan, listen to me.
Shen Yue can't be trusted.
Last night I saw her meeting with Wang Wenhao.
And you can be trusted?
Don't forget,
four years ago, you're the one who put me away.
My phone's ringing.
Give me my phone.
Come on.
No looking at other things when you're with me.
Confiscated. On silent.
Ruo Jin, are you with my brother?
Ran Ran, it's me.
Brother.
Something happened at home.
Come back quickly.
What?
Where are you going?
Ruo Jin, there's an emergency at home.
I need to go home first.
No, you can't go.
You can't go.
If you dare walk out that door today,
I'll call the police and say you raped me.
Did you know about this beforehand?
Feifan, you can't leave!
Mom!
Dad!
Ren Feifan.
Someone reported you for rape.
Rape?
Who did I rape?
We are now placing you under arrest
as a suspect in a rape case.
You have the right to remain silent.
My parents were murdered!
Aren't you going to do anything?
We'll notify Criminal Division Two immediately.
Wait a minute.
Let's go.
Get up.
Move.
Feifan.
Calm down.
Just calm down.
I'm the one who called the police.
We're a couple.
He didn't rape me.
I made the call.
I was wrong.
It's my fault.
Don't arrest him.
Please, don't take him!
You're the one who called?
Please, calm down.
Now I get it.
This whole thing was a setup.
Dad.
Mom.
Rest assured.
I won't let a single one of them get away.
That's not it, Feifan.
I'm the one who raped her.
I'll go with you.
Take him away.
What do we do?
What do we do now?
Feifan.
Can we...
Can we start over, please?
It's too late.
Feifan.
This time,
I'll be the one protecting you.
Why won't she just go away?
Just ignore her.
Let her follow if she wants.
Over there.
The Young Miss is back.
Young Miss, you barely care about family affairs.
What brings you back today?
Over the past six months, herbs from other farms
have been shipped on time and in full.
Only yours fall short in both quality and quantity.
And you dare ask why I'm here?
Um...
These two seem unfamiliar.
I haven't seen them around.
Who are they?
They're from the city Drug Administration.
They found problems with our herbs.
Luckily, we're personal friends.
So they came as friends to take a look.
Village Chief Li, if the herbs really have issues
and this gets escalated to the Drug Bureau,
you won't be able to handle the fallout.
Right, right, of course.
How about this:
Let me show the Young Miss and the two officials around.
If you don't mind,
try some of our country cooking.
Stay the night here.
Tomorrow, I'll report to you both
in detail about Lijia Village's situation.
Ginseng, matsutake.
When you bring them their meals later,
keep a close eye on them.
And don't eat any of it.
There's a drug in the food.
It's not poison.
I just want them to sleep soundly.
Don't cause me any trouble.
The stuff in the warehouse is fine, right?
No problem.
Good then.
Young Miss.
The Village Chief said you can't wander around.
There's a problem with the herbs.
Of course we have to check the fields.
Move aside.
Young Miss, the mountain is full of snakes and bugs.
Especially venomous snakes.
You should just have a good meal today.
And get some proper rest.
The Village Chief will arrange everything tomorrow.
To welcome the Young Miss and the two officials,
the Village Chief
brought out all his finest ingredients.
Please, help yourselves.
Tastes pretty good.
Okay.
I got it, Boss Li.
Alright.
Don't worry.
I'll send the Young Miss back first thing tomorrow.
Okay, okay, hanging up now.
Why does it reek so bad in here?
Bury all these corpses tonight!
I didn't eat that much.
I knew they drugged the food.
But it wasn't poison.
Are you sure you want to keep talking to me like this?
Let's go check on Shen Yue.
What's going on?
She's fine.
She just ate too much, so the dose was too high.
She'll wake up soon.
Then why didn't you tell us?
The skilled are bold.
This drug just makes us sleep more deeply.
Probably afraid we'd wander around at night.
Since we ate it without suspicion,
they won't be on guard against us.
I've noticed you're getting craftier and craftier.
You're a bit different from before.
Are you saying I used to be dumb?