Are you saying I used to be dumb?
How are you feeling?
What's going on?
They poisoned our food.
Poisoned?
I knew Lijia villagers were skilled with poisons.
But I didn't expect them to poison me.
Here, have some water.
I poured it myself.
They did poison us,
but they didn't mean to kill us.
If that's the case,
they'll definitely make a move tonight.
I remember Lijia Village used to be thriving.
How did it turn into a ghost town?
I think I'm picking up a strange smell.
Smells like death.
You two, hurry it up!
What's taking so long?
Hurry, hurry!
Why is one missing?
Li Dong, go find it, quick!
Let's keep working.
Okay.
It's alive!
Stop yelling! You scared me to death!
Village Chief.
Quit screaming like that.
Chief, I can't do this job anymore.
Not even for money.
Yeah, same here.
Why'd you roll down the slope?
Now I've got to carry you back up.
Unbelievable.
Li Dong!
What the hell are you yelling for?
Run!
Did you find Li Dong yet?
Did you hear something?
No, nothing.
Ren Feifan.
I know you've got sharp ears and a keen nose.
Don't try to scare us.
I think I heard something too.
But it wasn't a human voice.
That's impossible.
Ghosts don't exist in this world.
Let's get moving.
I heard some people become ghosts when they die.
And others become...
Jiangshi.
Are you out of your mind?
What's up with you two today?
So childish.
Let me tell you,
I don't scare easily.
Even if there really is a ghost,
let it show itself.
I'll take it on and see who's tougher.
Something's wrong.
Stay close to me.
Go!
What's wrong with them?
Are Jiangshi actually real?
No.
They're not Jiangshi.
Watch out, Feifan!
Feifan!
What caused them to end up like this?
I suspect they've all been poisoned by aconitine.
It's likely from long-term cultivation
of herbs containing aconitine.
That's why they've lost their minds,
acting like zombies.
Village Chief Li must have thought they were dead
and hauled them here to be buried.
He didn't expect the mountain wind
would wake these two villagers up.
The Li family in the old days,
if a grower fell ill from the herbs,
would treat them until they recovered.
But now,
they only think about silencing witnesses.
Can their poisoning still be cured?
Yes.
But not right now,
or anytime soon.
I can only temporarily restore their senses.
The toxins built up over years,
so it takes slow, steady medication to detox.
And whether they'll fully recover afterward
is another matter entirely.
So this medicine,
can you prescribe it?
Of course.
Nannan.
Why are you here all alone?
Where's your mom?
Where did she go?
Mommy
was taken by the bad chief to gather herbs.
He even locked Mommy up.
Don't cry, don't cry.
Do you know where your mom is?
I'm here to save you! Hurry, go!
Go!
Xixi.
Mommy!
Thank goodness you're okay.
I was worried sick.
How did you get back?
The Young Lady saved us.
Thank you, Young Lady.
Please, get up. Get up.
Stand up and tell me.
What on earth happened here?
How did they end up like this?
Four years ago,
Village Chief Li took on a job growing Aconite
and Pinellia Rhizome from someone.
The truth is, these herbs are all toxic.
Anyone who grew them
first got sores all over their body,
and then lost their minds.
Whenever a man lost his mind,
the chief would take him away.
Not long after,
those men vanished completely.
More and more men disappeared,
and herb production couldn't keep up.
So he forced us women
to grow those poisonous herbs.
By the way, where's Village Chief Li?
He's already dead.
Thank heavens!
Good riddance! Good riddance!
Aconite and Pinellia Rhizome are very hard to preserve.
Past their processing window,
less than one percent of their potency remains.
You were only in charge of growing them.
So where's the processing site?
It shouldn't be far.
That's right.
After the herbs were harvested,
they were sent to the old poisoner up the mountain.
Up the mountain?
Sir, Li Mei's been a vegetable for two years now.
Who knows when she'll ever wake up.
If we just keep dragging this out,
the Shen family fortune will never come to our Li family.
Feifan.
Ever since they killed my mother,
I've always wanted to destroy the Li family myself.
Thank you for giving me the courage
to let me
tear off their masks with my own hands.
Maybe a family like the Lis should've fallen long ago.
It'll happen just as you wish.
Ren Feifan.
Thank you.
Xu Ruojin.
Can you stop bothering the two of us?
Haven't you hurt Feifan enough already?
This is between Feifan and me.
It has nothing to do with you.
But he can't even stand the sight of you.
Can't you see that yourself?
Shen Yue, you've seen me as a rival since we were kids.
But in my eyes,
you've never even existed.
Who's there?
It's me.
I told you, I'm fine.
And I told you,
your wound may not be deep,
but the toxin is unknown.
Let me check it.
No need.
Just because I took a hit for you doesn't mean...
Shen Yue probably needs you more.
You seem to be back to your old self.
And even more jealous now.