[Adapted from Che Ye Liu Xiang's
novel of the same name]
[Episode 6]
You're back, Big Bro.
That's a lot of stuff.
You should've called me to help you carry it.
It's not that much.
Big Bro.
You left your phone in the bag.
The screen is cracked.
Just throw it in the trash.
But other than the screen,
everything else works fine.
It's too much trouble to fix.
It's a waste to throw it away
if it can be fixed.
You can have it if you want it.
Take it and fix it yourself.
Give it to me?
It's broken anyway.
If you don't want it, throw it away.
I want it.
Big Bro.
You have a pimple on your face today.
Eat less of the tiger-skin peppers today.
A pimple?
Where?
Right here.
Here.
Eat.
Eat... what?
Let's eat.
Stay over tonight.
Wait, let me do the dishes first.
I'll do the dishes first.
I'll take a shower first.
You can wait, but can it?
I bought you so many briefs.
Why are you still wearing boxers?
They...
They're uncomfortable.
How about this?
Is this comfortable?
I'd better take a shower first.
Fan Fan.
I've already spoken to Lv Xin.
Don't worry.
Big Bro, I'm going back now.
Stay here.
Let's go. I'll take you
to get your phone fixed.
Big Bro. Here's the key.
Just keep what I give you.
Looks wonderful.
The scarf?
The scarf is quite warm, too.
Let's go.
Okay.
Hello. How can I help you?
I'm going to the ministry first.
Call me if anything comes up.
Okay.
Sir, I have a phone here.
Can you see if it can be fixed?
It can't be repaired.
The whole component needs to be replaced.
I'll need to order the part,
and it might take a few days.
That's fine.
I'll just come pick it up in a few days.
Okay. Leave a 50-yuan deposit first.
Here you go, sir.
Keep it safe.
Thank you.
[Coffee]
Big Bro.
You still remember that I like these beans.
What are you doing?
Don't need it?
- Forget it then.
- Hey.
Once you write this check,
I won't see you for a long time again.
Every day, you're either sleeping at home
or hanging out with your friends.
As your brother,
I really don't know how to get along with you.
Why don't you use this check
to start a small business?
Take the chance to see
how the world has changed.
I'm not talking about having fun.
I'm talking about how
the world's operating logic has changed.
Once you broaden your horizons,
we'll naturally have more to talk about.
Don't you think so?
There's one more condition.
The Lu family is coming
to Yunjing in a few days.
As their daughter-in-law,
you have to treat them well.
Ow, ow! Big Bro!
I promise!
So, what are we eating later?
I know a Japanese restaurant
nearby that's really good.
Are you going to see Lu Xiao Fan again?
You're more attentive to
your fake brother-in-law than your own sister.
Just remember to keep your promise.
Hey.
Mom.
Wei Wei and I are in a fake marriage.
Sam is my friend.
Friend?
Friend.
Lover.
Mom.
It's not easy for gay people
to find someone they're compatible with.
It's very hard to just
make do and live together.
That's why Sam and I cherish each other.
Is it really that touching?
Look. Among our friends,
these so-called "normal couples"...
They're all actually quite pitiful.
Especially that white guy.
He never belonged in their world.
What happened between Wei Tong and Wei Wei...
It must be very heartbreaking to him.
Really?
Don't you think so?
Simon was actually betrayed by Wei Tong.
From now on, he'll only be
the most marginalized person in this family.
Fan Fan.
You don't need to overthink things.
Are you hungry?
I'll take you out to eat.
Let's eat something else then.
My parents are coming tomorrow.
I went and bought some things.
These two sets are for your father.
These two are for your mother.
This nightgown is for her, too.
The fabric is very comfortable.
This jacket is for your younger sister.
Young people should dress more fashionably.
This bracelet is for her, too.
Big Bro.
My sister is still young.
She doesn't need such an expensive bracelet.
This is what young people like these days.
I have things to do, so I'll head out.
When they arrive,
I might not have time to host them.
Don't feel burdened by it.
Okay. Thank you.
Big Bro.
You forgot your scarf.
That's not mine.
I saw you with a similar one last time.
Oh, you...
Hello? Big Bro?
What's wrong?
I'm still a bit worried.
Lv Xin didn't want to come this morning.
I'm afraid...
Fan Fan.
It's too noisy over there.
- Can you hear me?
- I really can't hear you.
Hello? Big Bro?
You just have to pick them up safely.
Everything is arranged.
All right.
Dad, why did you bring so many things?
Ask your mother.
How could we come empty-handed
on our first visit?
Things you can buy in a store
aren't anything special.
The Bei family is rich,
they can buy anything.
If we're bringing gifts,
we should bring things money can't buy.
Mom, why are your eyes so red?
She found out she was taking the train.
She was so excited,
she couldn't sleep all night.
So annoying. It's because of the train.
It was rocking and swaying.
And with so many people sleeping together,
how could we sleep well?
I like taking the sleeper train.
It feels like sleeping in a cradle.
Rocking and swaying...
I fall asleep in no time.
You silly girl.
You're too old to be in a cradle.
Look at how happy you are.
Why aren't we staying at your home?
It's too crowded at home.
I was afraid you wouldn't sleep well.
This is a grand hotel.
Lv Xin specially arranged it.
It's not easy for you to visit Yunjing.
You need to rest well at night,
so you'll have energy to sightsee by day.
Silly child.
Your dad and I are used to hard beds.
We could've just slept on the floor.
Besides, spending your money
is like spending ours.
It's not worth wasting it on a place like this.
Old Wu.
Let's go to the Bei house to see Lv Xin first.
Let's go, Old Wu.
Fan Fan, you look so handsome.
Auntie Lin, my parents are here.
Fan Fan's mom.
Fan Fan is here.
Mom. Look at their yard.
It's just like the pond at our house.
- It's full of weeds.
- Hush, child! Don't talk nonsense.
The whole family has no manners.
It's so nice.
Who's that running around?
Auntie Lin just tidied up.
The house was just cleaned.
Don't you have any manners?
Get down here, you girl!
How can you run around in someone's house?
What do you mean "someone's house"?
This is my brother's house.
The child is just curious.
Let her have a look.
Lv Xin, you're a grown-up.
Don't mind your sister-in-law's curiosity.
Lv Xin.
My parents are here.
Dad, Mom.
Darling.
Has your health improved over the years?
I'm fine.
Xiao Fan.
Did you take Mom and Dad to the hotel?
I specially booked that hotel.
It's closer to the tourist attractions.
We're not staying in a hotel.
We'll just sleep on the floor here.
Let's not waste that money.
But how will we all fit?
How about this?
I'll call your brother.
Let my parents stay in his room.
- What do you think?
- No.
Big Bro, why aren't
your things in Lv Xin's room?
Fan Fan, where do you sleep at night?
I stay in the attic.
I have a lot of work at night,
and I don't want to disturb Lv Xin.
What kind of married couple
sleeps in separate rooms?
This is nonsense.
Your mom and I were saying at home,
it's been five years,
and you still don't have a child.
That's enough.
They're adults now.
They can think for themselves.
Besides, work is important, too.
Then, we'll stay in Fan Fan's room.
Fan Fan, you move back to Lv Xin's room.
Don't work for the next few days,
so you don't disturb your wife's rest.
I almost forgot.
Lunch is almost ready.
Let's all go to the living room.
You've come so far and haven't had tea.
Mom, let's go.
I'm at my limit.
I really can't eat another bite.
I told you to eat less.
Now that I've brought you here,
I won't let you suffer when it comes to food.
As expected of a servant
in a wealthy household,
her cooking skills are top-notch.
Auntie Lin is our helper.
She's been with us since I was a child.
She's not a "servant."
Look at my big mouth. That's what I meant.
Mom, Dad, if you're done eating,
go upstairs and rest.
I'm leaving now.
The elders haven't even moved yet,
but the junior is already taking off.
The Bei family has a habit of taking naps.
Dad, Mom, you can rest in my room in a bit.
I have some things to do outside.
Big Bro, aren't we going
to look around Yunjing?
Hello.
I'm here to pick up a phone.
A phone?
Big Bro, you have a phone?
It's an old one from Lv Qing.
I brought it in for repairs.
The manager has your phone.
I'll go get him for you.
This...
It's all due to my lack of experience.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
It looks just like new.
With the case replaced,
it looks exactly like a new one.
See if you're satisfied with it.
I am. How much is it?
Don't worry about the money.
I can't take your money.
This device is still under warranty.
No charge.
Then, thank you.
Let's go.
I was wondering which girl
he was spending so much money and effort on.
He ordered two imported phones,
stepped on one to give to him,
and then swapped it for a brand new one.
I didn't expect it to be a young man.
Just focus on your own job.
Stop gossiping.
Big Bro.
Didn't you say you were busy?
I had to come even if I was busy.
I wouldn't feel right leaving it to you.
Besides, it's our parents'
first time in Yunjing.
Fan Fan is much more capable now.
He's a married man, after all.
He's much more mature.
Mom, like I was telling you,
all the most developed countries
are focusing on finance now.
Making money with money is the fastest way.
That doesn't sound very stable.
It is stable!
We have a client at our office.
He just has a relative working
as a receptionist at a securities firm.
He got a tip.
In just one week,
do you know how much he made?
How much?
- 30,000 yuan.
- How much?
30,000 yuan?
Fan Fan, is what your brother saying true?
Mom, Dad, don't listen to his nonsense.
How could a receptionist's information
be on the same level as Mr. Bei's?
That's so much money.
Trust your son.
I have the brains, just not the opportunity.
The eldest's brain is indeed
sharper than the second's.
He's the big brother.
It's no surprise he's doing better.
Besides, if it weren't for Xiao Fan,
could he have made it this far?
Mom, don't keep bringing that up.
Fan Fan stays at the Bei house every day,
so why is he still just
a lowly salesperson after all this time?
Lv Xin.
Long time no see.
Lv Xin is so pretty.
Old Lu, do you remember?
Back then, when the neighbors
looked at Lv Xin,
they were so jealous.
Just thinking about it makes me happy.
No matter how jealous they were,
she's our daughter-in-law.
I always thought Xiao Fan and Lv Xin
were the perfect match.
And you didn't believe me.
The stock market is complex,
but there are plenty of opportunities.
The key is to follow the right people.
Even a pig can fly
if it's in the right place at the right time.
When there's a pot of gold at home,
why would we let outsiders get to it first?
Lv Xin.
Come here.
I have something to ask you.
What is it?
Are stocks really that profitable?
Yes.
If you know how to invest,
you can make a lot of money.
This boy of ours must be too dim-witted.
That's why your father-in-law
won't help you make any money.
Dad.
You know what Fan Fan is like.
It's no wonder that Mr. Bei
doesn't help his own son-in-law get rich.
My dad doesn't even trade stocks himself.
Why would he involve Xiao Fan?
Fan Fan, look at her.
See how defensive she gets when I mention you?
Enough. Mind your own business.
Stay out of Fan Fan's affairs.
Big Bro, it's getting late.
You should head back now.
I'm not going back.
I took two days off
to spend time with Mom and Dad.
But there's no room for you to stay here.
Why don't you go find a hotel?
Isn't Lv Qing away?
I'll just stay in his room for now.
I've already booked a hotel for you.
Ping Ping, maybe you should
go stay at a guesthouse.
Mom, why don't I just
sleep in the courtyard then?
How was I to know that
staying at my brother's house
meant there wouldn't even be a room for me?
I didn't bring a letter
of introduction or my ID.
How am I supposed to check in?
No one is allowed to stay in my brother's room.
Lv Xin.
Do you just not want us staying at your house?
Dad, Lv Xin didn't mean it like that.
There are important documents
in Lv Qing's room.
Big Bro Lv Qing is back.
Mr. and Mrs. Lu, you're here.
Lv Qing.
Why have you lost so much weight
since the last time I saw you?
No matter how busy you are,
you must look after your health.
Big Bro Lv Qing, thank you for the bracelet.
Thank you for your concern, Mrs. Lu.
I brought some late-night snacks for everyone.
Big Bro Lv Qing is so good to our family.
My brother has been a lot of trouble
for you all these years.
Xiao Fan hasn't been much trouble at all.
What a huge mushroom!
What are you talking about?
This is abalone.
It really does look like a mushroom.
It does look a bit like one.
Dad, Mom.
This abalone is very expensive.
Just one of these abalones...
is worth as much as a pig back in our village.
Right, Lv Qing?
It's not quite that expensive.
Here.
Thank you, Mom.
Big Bro.
Big Bro Xiao Ping didn't bring his ID.
He can't check into a guesthouse.
The reason I came back...
was to bring you all a little perk.
A friend was dining out today
and the hotel gave him two free stay vouchers.
Since we're locals, we have no use for them.
They're for two deluxe
standard rooms at a five-star hotel.
I thought I shouldn't let them go to waste.
So, I brought them back.
I thought maybe one of you would like to go.
I want to go!
After we finish eating,
I'll have Old Wu drive you there.
Mr. and Mrs. Lu can share a room.
As for Lu Xiao Ping...
It's a pity.
Since you don't have your ID,
you can stay in Xiao Fan's room.
Lv Qing is so thoughtful.
Everything is arranged so well.
Lv Qing,
this must have cost you a lot, right?
I feel a bit bad about this.
Mrs. Lu,
please, just enjoy your stay.
Thank you, Lv Qing.
Big Bro.
You forgot your scarf last time.
I actually bought this scarf for you.
This... This scarf is way too expensive.
I have no use for it.
You... You should use it.
If you don't want it, just throw it away.
I got the phone fixed for you.
I've already put the SIM card in.
It's the kind that doesn't need top-ups.
Big Bro.
That phone looks brand new.
Maybe... you should take it back and use it.
It's fine.
I bought another one for myself.
You keep this one.
From now on, make sure I can always find you.
Do you hear me?
Are you a dog or something?
Big Bro...
Fan Fan.
Can we go back to how we were before?
Before when?
Once your parents leave,
will you move back in with me?