I'm going to make an absurd suggestion,
but hear me out, okay?
Can I have sex with other individuals?
What?
You, having sex...
With other men?
Even though we're married?
- What?
- No, let me explain.
It's apparently a thing overseas, and...
You must think it's so funny I have ED.
No, not at all.
Ouji, please listen to me. I...
This is serious to me.
But clearly you don't agree.
[Episode 7]
You sure we don't need to report him?
It's fine. I won't see him again.
I'm partly to blame for aggravating him.
How? You didn't do anything wrong.
Help me forget the bad experience.
Why don't we stay like this for the night?
I want you to touch me.
Please?
As you wish.
[Ouji]
[Where are you?]
[I'm calling]
He's left me on read.
For two weeks now.
Why did I say that?
Why did I think that was such a bright idea?
[Kato Publishing]
What's up?
One of my steady gigs
is ending our contract this month.
They're re-assessing their whole magazine,
or so I was told.
I see.
Nothing you can do about that.
I know.
But it's made me face an unfortunate truth.
- Huh?
- I now have zero steady gigs.
That's, well...
Don't bother cheering me up. I know it's bad.
It's an inevitable for freelancers.
But with your reputation,
work will come your way.
For now, focus on your one-time gigs, and...
Wait... None of those, either?
Yeah. I know I'm screwed.
I'm practically getting by on part-time jobs.
No, not even. I'm not making a single yen.
If I'm not a freelancer, what am I?
A vagrant?
Oh, I am so screwed...
At least your husband will support you!
Haru?
Okay. Have you ever had a bright idea that,
when executing it, didn't go well at all?
- Huh?
- An idea so bright,
that it clears up the fog in your brain.
Except, when you put it to action...
You must think it's so funny I have ED.
Is this about a project of yours?
Yes. You could say that.
It happens all the time with graphic design.
Clients will shoot down ideas
I think are great.
I see.
Ultimately, it comes down to conversation,
and reconciling our ideas
to create the final product.
Reconciling is important, that's for sure.
[Ouji]
[Where are you?]
[I'm calling]
[Touto Publishing]
Do you know Mukai, of Touto Publishing?
She was looking for a new columnist
to write a women's piece.
- Really?
- Why not give it a shot?
Okay.
Aizawa! Long time no see!
Likewise, Ms. Kotani.
Sorry, I guess you're an "Ouji" now.
Indeed.
Congratulations on your marriage.
Thank you.
To think you'd marry him.
The power of a fan is something else.
I wouldn't say that.
Sensei, the car.
Thanks.
"Sensei"?
A book I released became a hit,
embarrassing as that is to admit.
I see.
I hope you enjoyed the curry.
Huh?
Curry?
I saw the recipe on my friend's account.
[keiko^kotani]
'Sup.
Run away from home?
No. Just thought I'd take work seriously.
- Really.
- 'Sup.
- Run away from home?
- I said, no!
Why're you so prickly
when the band's back together?
I am not prickly.
Here's a gift to lift your spirits.
- What's this?
- Keiko's new book. I bumped into her,
and she gave us each a signed copy.
[I had fun! XXX - Keiko]
What "fun"?
You met up with her?
He's cheating on you?
Hold on. I'm not following.
Last I heard, Ouji lacked the drive,
but he hugged you, right?
It's not that he lacks it,
it's that he physically can't.
Physically can't?
Ah, I see.
Which led them to the brink of a divorce.
This is too much information to handle.
So, why do you suspect him of cheating?
This.
Curry?
It's the same exact dish Ouji made for me.
Is it?
I mean...
Look.
"#LeftoversCurry".
I can see why that'd get you.
Transforming leftovers into a meal?
She's practically showing off.
- But...
- See the canned mackerel she used?
Maybe?
Canned foods aren't "leftovers".
They're made to last decades.
Fair point.
It was in our curry, too.
He went and bought a can, for this.
I see.
- Even so, that's no reason to...
- Haru.
I might've seen it.
Seen, what?
Sorry, I couldn't find the time to tell you.
You can't see their faces.
- That's clearly Ouji.
- Maybe, but the woman...
- They came out, together!
- She may not be Kotani.
When?
About a month ago.
- We're taking a quick break.
- Sure.
[Haru: 10 Unread Messages]
[Haru: We have to talk]
[I'll be waiting at home]
I'm home.
What do you mean, "talk"?
Haruchan?
Why the nickname?
Huh? What are you talking about?
You asked her for the curry recipe.
Curry?
[keiko^kotani]
No, her post coincidentally appeared
on my timeline.
I was thinking it looked good,
when she happened to DM me,
so I asked for the recipe.
She "happened" to DM you?
Sounds mighty convenient.
What are you...
A text from your
longest lasting girlfriend of two years.
What sort of metric is that?
You kept in touch with her?
I'm telling you, it was a coincidence.
Then was November 13th also a "coincidence"?
What?
Why?
No, we weren't...
And where'd you get this photo?
Did you do it with her?
You can't with me, but with your ex?
- Like I said...
- Guess I can't beat two years of history.
I was only ever a fan in the background.
We got married because it was easy for you.
- Is that why...
- Knock it off already!
You don't trust a thing I said?
Well...
Fine.
Do what you want.
Doubt me, have sex with other men. Whatever.
Those eyes.
- Ouji...
- You're a bit too persistent.
Those cold eyes of his always shut me up.
This is serious to me.
I'd rather put aside my own desires,
than have this person hate me.
NOT!
Fine.
I will do what I want. Whatever I want.
But what is it I want?
Did you say something just now?
Let's just say being given sudden free reign
is difficult to deal with in its own right.
Your project was approved?
Huh?
Was this not about your proposal
to Touto Publishing?
I was hoping it went well...
Yeah, that's what I was talking about.
I'm just... waiting to hear back from them.
I'm glad things are going
in a positive direction.
Hello?
Sorry I kept you.
You don't usually initiate the invite.
What's up?
Well, I do feel partly responsible
for what happened, so...
You left the house?
Yeah. It's been three days since I left,
and I've been reading all the manga I want.
You're staying at a manga cafe?
Go to a hotel, you're not a broke student.
Well, I am a vagrant right now.
A vagrant?
Never mind.
Fuyumi says she'll be here soon.
But what about Chizuka?
She's apparently making up
for a canceled sleepover.
Sorry I'm late!
Fuyumi!
- Drunk already?
- Yeah, she's going fast today.
So? What happened?
- Your lamb chops. Enjoy.
- Thank you.
I see. Ouji got mad at you.
He did! I don't understand why.
I'm the one should be mad!
- So you got mad back.
- Yup.
Except, now you don't know what to do.
Why not have sex with another dude?
Ouji gave you his explicit permission.
Yeah. But that's only because I asked first.
No, I asked before his affair, not after it!
B-Before his affair?
So you weren't talking about revenge sex?
Ouji said if we couldn't have sex,
then we shouldn't stay together.
I want to stay with him.
But never having sex, is a bit...
So you suggested other partners?
It's apparently a thing overseas,
so I blurted it out.
And how did Ouji react?
- He completely lost his cool.
- I see.
Yet he makes his own affair an exception?
That's why I blew a fuse, too.
Make sense.
I'll introduce you to someone.
- Huh?
- The perfect man for you.
- Akina.
- A professional, with no strings attached.
- A professional?
- Oh!
The people from the male brothel?
Sorry, who?
I guess I haven't told you yet.
I'm currently in love with my therapist
from a male brothel.
So there are male brothels.
That's the part that shocks you?
I'm just a bit overwhelmed with information.
How about the three of us all call someone?
They can come chill, nothing steamy involved.
Jumping in solo is a bit much for you, right?
Yes, but Fuyumi wouldn't...
Married women call on them, too.
- They do?
- Yeah. To alleviate their stress.
But you don't have any stress
to alleviate, do you?
- My bad.
- Exactly.
Fuyumi's the only one of us
leading a respectable, happy lifestyle.
Hey, I lead a respectable lifestyle, too.
It's not respectable at all.
Ouch, that hurts.
- I was referring to myself.
- Huh?
My husband only acts like
he understands my work.
He harasses me to "do better".
I'm sorry.
Can I fess up about something?
Remember that coworker I mentioned
who was having an affair with an actor?
That was actually me.
- What?
- Y-You're so cool!
I'm not "cool" at all.
Sorry, I couldn't help myself.
- How long?
- About half a year now.
I spoke big to you, Haru. But the truth is...
First, you have to accept
your true feelings and desires.
Don't worry. Accept yourself,
and you'll feel a whole lot better.
I was talking about my own experiences.
I had no confidence in myself,
and would always worry alone.
But things became easier
when I began seeing him.
It was like I was affirming my own existence.
Affirming yourself.
But that's no reason to look highly of me.
Just the other day, I faced a definite risk.
- Did your husband find out?
- No, but it got close.
That's the end of my confession.
Aw, I want to hear more!
- Next time.
- No, now.
We're not here for my story, remember?
So? What'll it be, Haru?
Huh?
Want to be a bit adventurous?
Akina, actually...
Good evening.
We're with the Ebisu Boys Club.
Come on in.
My adventure has begun.
[Preview]