Thank you for choosing the Ebisu Boys Club,
"Multi-Partner Plan".
Multi-Partner...
Us guys will introduce ourselves first.
I'm Hakuto, 21 years old.
I'm a puppy-like, university student.
My name is Naoki.
Hey, third guy. Introduce yourself!
Natsuo Urushibara, 32 years old.
I work in delivery.
That sounds like...
His real, full name.
Next, we'll introduce ourselves.
I'm Akina.
And I'm Haru.
I'm currently...
Tell us more as the night goes on!
That's more exciting, right?
Sorry he's calling the shots.
How about a quick toast?
Was that to keep our age
and occupation to ourselves?
Here's to a great night together! Cheers!
Cheers!
You okay, Haru?
Yes.
I'm just marveling at this whole experience.
Looks like those two have already paired up.
Looks like it.
What about us?
Should we have a threesome?
Just kidding.
Sounds good. Have at it.
H-Haru?
I didn't realize you were so raring to go.
Isn't that what the nightlife is all about?
Sure, but not here, please.
Right. Sorry.
I've been hired to write erotic works before,
but I now see why
I never received another offer.
- Take a break.
- What? I still wanna drink.
Nope.
You're drinking too much.
You're allowed to cozy up too, you know?
I can't even remember the last time I did.
Really?
My partner and I married without ever dating,
and even after marriage...
We've never done a thing.
Never? Not even sex?
My friends are all finding
new people in their lives,
so why am I so hung up
on this one man?
He's told me I'm free to cheat, or whatever.
But even now, all I do is watch.
So here I am, unsatisfied,
yet unchanging in my wishy-washy ways.
Sorry. I must sound really annoying.
- No, not at all.
- You're annoying as hell.
Natsuo, where are you...
I'm not gonna sit around, waiting to piss.
I'll take a dump while I'm at it.
You didn't need to say that.
[Episode 8]
What are you doing, Chizuka?
Practicing how to dive into the pool!
I thought that wasn't allowed?
Mommy? What's wrong?
It's nothing, dear.
Chizuka! No laying on the floor!
You're a lady!
Hey, you don't need to yell at her.
And have Chizuka embarrass herself?
If anything, you should be scolding her.
There, there.
Everything is okay.
It's okay, dear.
[Hotel Cabana Tokyo]
No one saw you?
- Probably.
- "Probably"?
Be more careful.
Your wife's friend got a shot of you.
I am being careful.
Not careful enough.
One photo on social media, and you're over.
Then don't call me out here again.
We can't talk about this in public.
I'm still surprised you came last time,
only for you to blab my ear off.
- That's because...
- If I'm suspected of having an affair,
I'm telling the truth.
Huh?
I'm telling the world we met here,
at this hotel...
to discuss your ED.
- Hey now...
- I'll always prioritize my husband and kid.
That's all I called to tell you.
And what about you?
Huh?
Did you clear up the misunderstanding
with Aizawa?
She wouldn't believe me.
So I told her she could doubt me,
have sex with other men, whatever.
"Whatever"? How could you say that?
I agree with you completely.
What if she actually cheats on you?
- What?
- Oh, come on.
Haru? Cheating on me?
- That's impossible.
- How can you be so sure?
- Because Haru...
- "Loves me", is it?
You're so full of yourself. Loser.
Aizawa is a woman.
You think she'll stay with a man
who doesn't kiss her, have sex with her,
and now gets pissed at her over an ED?
Your husband sounds like the worst.
You have every right
to do it with another man.
You think so?
You told him you'd do what you want.
I did.
But I sort of blurted that out
without thinking.
Doesn't that mean
you were speaking from the heart?
Well...
Your hands are so small, Haru.
- They're cute.
- Really?
Check this out.
It's a pressure point
that makes you sensitive.
Oh, uh... Huh? Where's Akina?
She left with Naoki.
- What?
- Should we split, too?
No, we can't.
Don't you want to move on?
I mean...
Your glass is empty.
- I'll bring you something to drink.
- It's fine.
- So how about we...
- Wait. This is Akina's house.
We can't, not here.
Quit making excuses.
What?
Excuses?
You're annoying after all.
Jump.
Huh?
Jump, I'll catch you.
Or do you plan on staying there forever?
Want to do it?
So, how about it?
Will you take a shower?
Yes, I will. Alone.
Oh my god.
A man I met mere hours ago made me moan.
Jump.
Huh?
Jump. I'll catch you.
But...
It's like a beam of light
cut through the dark.
I'm sorry.
This would be a separate payment, correct?
How much will it be?
I don't need the money.
What?
I actually quit working this job.
I planned to dip early today, too.
But...
I am curious to see you lose it.
If you change your mind,
leave while I take my shower.
What is it you ultimately want from this?
Huh?
Do you want to break up with her?
I...
You're still muttering to yourself?
If you're so hung up, clearly you love her.
I can't believe I'm still listening.
Why not be honest, for once in your life?
Quit being a narcissist.
Make sure you leave long after I do.
I guess marriage isn't so bad after all.
I actually love you, Haru.
I feel so happy right now.
I love you, too.
Are we allowed to kiss?
You're like a maiden out of a period drama.
I just thought it wasn't allowed.
We've already gone far beyond kissing.
I guess so...
Personally, I'm fine either way.
But you'll really feel it if they're sealed.
Do it.
Was that...
Did you come?
I'm sorry. It's nothing.
It's clearly not. What's up?
I'd bought them.
Condoms.
I...
I'd bought them already.
I just remembered.
It was before he made that declaration.
I love him.
I got married to him.
I'm cherished by him.
I really wanted to have sex with him.
With Ouji.
But...
Now, I feel so good.
And I just... I don't...
[Haru]
You know, I do think you're cute and funny.
But I have no desire to care for you,
or steal you away from your husband.
Not one bit.
I'm not surprised.
But our bodies are compatible.
I actually got turned on, for once.
And what's so wrong about that?
That body of yours is honest. I like that.
- What?
- I'm not married, so I can't say I get it.
But wanting your husband to love you
is a separate feeling entirely, right?
Cherish the fact that your body's happy.
I'm fine.
Here. I had it for the job,
but you'd better take them.
Huh?
Toss your old condoms, and use these instead.
With your husband, another dude,
or me, if you want.
You?
I thought you quit this line of work.
I did.
But if we reunite, and I act
like a stranger, that's your cue.
See you.
Cherish the fact that your body's happy.
My body is... happy.
[Condoms]
Call us again.
I'm sorry.
No need to apologize.
Haru followed him anyway.
- But...
- Really, I don't mind.
Here.
Since we lost a member,
and our time together was cut short.
A refund is the least I can offer.
- No, really...
- Please, take it.
I should've expected that.
Morning. I heard you're off today.
Everything okay?
[I'm fine! Just have a bit of a cold]
[Hidamari Women's Clinic]
I'm home.
Welcome back.
- Um!
[Preview]