Mr. Gao...
Nothing can stop me.
Not that doctor...
And not these floral scissors.
They can't stop me either.
Leave. Otherwise, I'll...
What?
Are you going to stab yourself?
I don't believe you'll do it.
Fuck! You really did it!
Don't touch me!
Dr. Fang will be angry.
He'll be angry. So angry.
Okay, okay.
I won't touch you.
Mr. Gao, you need a doctor now.
I'll... I'll call a doctor for you.
Go away! Go away!
Okay, okay.
Fine, just don't do anything rash.
Hello? Is this the emergency center?
Someone is injured here.
Please send someone quickly.
He'll be angry.
He'll be angry...
Dr. Fang...
Did I do a good job?
[Episode 9]
Hello.
I'm Gao Zhun's emergency contact.
How is he now?
He's over there.
Mr. Gao, I've brought your medicine.
Thank you.
Just leave it on the table. Thank you.
It's me.
What happened?
How did you end up
with a stress-induced syncope?
Are you worried about me?
What exactly happened?
Just...
Matters at the company.
I was a bit too rushed in handling them.
Then I felt dizzy.
But I'm fine now.
Company matters?
Was it Justin?
Don't overthink it.
It's all been settled.
Now that you're here, let's go back.
Okay.
What do you want for dinner?
How about Japanese food or hot pot?
I'm fine with anything.
You pick.
Okay. I'll find a place near your home.
Dr. Fang.
Can we park above ground?
You know I don't like underground parking lots.
Dr. Fang, why are we here?
Fang Chi, say something.
Take me to your car.
What are you doing?
Treatment.
Now?
Here?
Yes.
Do as I say.
Where is your car?
There.
How are you feeling right now?
Scared.
Unsettled.
Anxious.
All of them.
Is that all?
Get in.
Lie down.
You're not going to listen to me?
Then don't come looking for me again.
I'll listen.
Imagine that I am that man from that day.
But... But he wasn't like this.
Then what was he like?
He... He was on top of me.
He hit me.
He pulled down my pants.
He pinched my thighs.
What else?
He was very rough.
He also said...
"What's so great about being rich?"
"You're still just the same."
"Getting fucked."
What else did he say?
He even put my legs on his shoulders.
And asked if I was enjoying it.
Is this how he did it?
He took off my pants.
Are you inviting me to do this?
Just to enjoy this kind of pleasure?
Were you like this with Justin too?
What?
How did you get that?
Justin sent it to me.
I told you to stay away from him.
I told you not to be alone with him.
Did you listen?
Are you dying to be raped again?
No, that's not it.
I did listen to you.
I stayed far away from him.
Liar.
What did you say at the hospital just now?
Since you don't trust me,
why should I continue your treatment?
You... You don't like me being near him.
I only hid it because
I was afraid you'd be angry.
Look, if you don't believe me.
What's that?
A stab from the flower shears.
It's not serious.
Justin tried something with me.
But I scared him off.
Dr. Fang, I really did listen to you.
I'm sorry.
I misunderstood you.
But self-harm is wrong.
- If you'd stabbed any deeper...
- I'm not afraid.
Compared to death,
I'm more afraid of you being angry.
Just like you are now.
Gao Zhun.
Promise me.
Don't hurt yourself again.
And, I am only your therapist.
Your choices shouldn't be for my sake.
I'm doing it for myself.
I need you to treat me.
You know how much I fear this place.
I lose sleep all night whenever I dream of it.
But ever since that person became you,
I'm not afraid anymore.
I even... yearn for it.
Because you... are different.
Dr. Fang, let the person
in my nightmare become you.
Only then can I be free from the pain.
You...
Do you know what you're doing?
I know.
I'm asking you to treat me.
Cut!
Okay, that's enough.
Why didn't you undo the buckle yourself?
Why did you wait for him to do it?
- I...
- Hey, Director.
At this point,
Gao Zhun has already gone all in.
He's luring Fang Chi to simulate rape,
so he should undo the buckle himself.
Isn't that right?
Gao Zhun's motive makes sense,
but the core of this scene is Fang Chi.
The wall of "rules" he built
must be torn down by his own hands.
No matter how much Fang Chi likes Gao Zhun,
all he feels now is heartache
and the fear of him getting hurt.
Gao Zhun is forcing his hand.
He's using both mental
and physical pain to pressure Fang Chi.
That's why Fang Chi loses himself.
That's why he'd resort to such an extreme
to help Gao Zhun escape the nightmare.
This is salvation.
What kind of salvation is this?
Isn't this just hurting him again?
Who told you love is only about protection?
It can also be a sharp blade.
Besides, this is drama.
It needs to be extreme.
Mr. Zhen, don't be so pedantic.
This scene is the climax of the film.
Only at the peak of darkness
can the light shine through.
Only when rules are broken
can the heart be seen clearly.
Come on. Let's get ready for...
Director, the producer is looking for you.
Oh, Mr. Jiang.
Hello.
Okay, I understand.
Right, okay.
The director has his interpretation.
But we...
Do you think Fang Chi
would really hurt Gao Zhun?
The answer in the script is...
He did.
Is the news on the trending list true?
What?
Are you getting married?
To whom?
Who else? Your girlfriend.
Xiao Chen.
- Yes?
- My phone.
We're on set. You shouldn't be like this.
- Zhun, I'm doing this for your sake-
- Shut up.
[Zhen Xin Marriage]
[Feng Yun Ting Claims Engagement Set...]
All right, all right.
On set, the scene comes first.
Let's focus on filming.
Don't worry.
Ms. Qin is already handling it.
Let's get into character first.
We have to finish shooting this location today.
Come on.
All right, everyone get ready.
Actors, get into character.
Come on.
You...
[Feng Yun Ting]
Pick up the scene. Action!
Dr. Fang...
Let the person in my nightmare...
become you.
Only then... can I escape the pain.
No.
I can't.
Fang Chi...
Please, treat me.
Help me.
Help me forget him.
Help me forget that terrible beginning.
And forget all that pain.
All right, I promise you.
Let that person... become me.
So what if you're rich?
You're still just the same, getting fucked!
Does it feel good?
Tell me, does it feel good?
Cut!
Good job, Mr. Zhen. Take a break.
Mr. Zhang, it's your turn.
This way.
Bro, I've confirmed it with the AD.
We can wrap up and head back to the hotel.
Are we going back now?
Your phone.
Ms. Feng called several times.
I was filming.
Did you see Weibo?
I didn't do it.
If it wasn't you, then was it me?
My agent has already called the police.
Wait.
Wait for Weibo to tell me
that the marriage is official, right?
Spreading rumors
over 500 times can lead to jail time.
The police will track the IP address.
It'll be resolved soon.
Anything else?
I have some good news.
Thanks to the fake news,
my endorsement deal is set.
I'm signing the contract today.
You'll be free soon.
Put his mind at ease.
After this last scene, we can call it a day.
Wait, why is he back?
I don't get why you got your ears pierced.
It won't match the upcoming scenes.
It'll be fine.
I'm tough.
The swelling will be gone by tomorrow.
Besides, who's going to look at my ears?
Who's going to look at your ears?
This is for the big screen!
I just felt like it.
You...
You're always so impulsive.
Qin Yao really can't control you.
So willful.
Hey, Xiao Chen.
Let's go, Zhun.
With all that mess on Weibo,
he still has the nerve to smile at you.
And you too, why do you even bother with him?
Seriously.
After the shoot, come to Room 1638
at the Grand Hyatt by yourself.
I'll be waiting for you there.
Let's go.
Okay, let's leave it at that.
Surprised to see me here?
The crew's hotel is full of prying eyes.
It's safer to talk here.
Does my earring look good?
Was that really necessary?
I wanted to be just like you.
But it really hurt.
I only endured it by thinking of you.
Hey, I'm the one who paid for this room.
Can you two wait until I'm gone
before you start flirting?
So...
what exactly is all this?
Someone insisted that
I explain it to you myself.
The marriage news is fake.
The trending search was bought by a rival.
I hope you don't overthink it.
I won't.
I never take gossip to heart.
But... I should still thank you.
No need.
I'm a woman of my word.
If I promise something, I'll get it done.
Look at how worried you were.
See?
He's much more mature and calm than you.
Fine.
I'll stop being a third wheel.
By the way, I've already handled the media.
I hope this little episode...
won't affect our agreement.
I'm off.
What agreement do you have?
We're in the same industry.
What other agreement could there be?
Just a clean break.
Come on.
Are you still acting?
Don't you think...
we're more dramatic than the movie?
What are you doing?
Try it.
Savor the red wine.
[Gao Zhun]
Hello, Senior.
It's me, Fang Chi.
I recall you have a clinic in the CBD.
Could I borrow it for a while?
Okay.
Thank you, Senior.
Ms. Feng.
Please inform all patients except Gao Zhun
that starting next week,
treatment will be at a new location.
I'll send you the address later.
[Gao Zhun: Can I go over to you earlier today?]
[Unpin]
Hello?
D-Dr. Fang.
You finally picked up.
Where have you been?
Why is your house empty,
and the clinic cleared out?
Did something happen to you?
Why...
Why aren't you saying anything?
Are you...
abandoning me?
Mr. Gao.
Your treatment is over.
But I'm not cured yet.
Your nightmare no longer exists.
Mr. Gao.
You'll get better in time.
Can you let me meet you?
Whatever we have to say,
let's say it face to face.
I'm sorry.
That wouldn't be appropriate.
I'm the doctor.
You're the patient.
I've already...
made too many mistakes.
You're not in the wrong. I was willing.
Enough.
Gao Zhun.
Listen to me carefully.
It's time for you to move on.
Do you mean...
it's over between us?
When did we ever start?
Just treat it as a dream.
No.
If this is a dream, I can't wake up.
I'm begging you.
D-Don't leave me.
Once a week.
Even once every two weeks is fine.
I won't like you anymore.
I'll stop liking you, okay?
Just let me see you. Don't leave me.
Don't... Don't force me.
Don't...
We can't...
keep making the same mistakes.
Cut.
Where is he?
He was crying too hard.
He went to the restroom to calm down.
Don't do this.
There are people outside.
Your eyes are all red from crying.
The movie is fiction.
But you and I are real.
I know.
But Gao Zhun's pain...
I...
I understand it completely.
If you understand Gao Zhun,
then you should know even better...
that Fang Chi's love for him never changed.
And off-camera, I have always loved you, too.
Is he urging us to re-shoot a scene?
No.
It's Feng Yun Ting.
My engagement and marriage to Mr. Zhen...
are both completely groundless.
Regarding the so-called exposé,
the police are now involved.
Is this just your side of the story?
Does Mr. Zhen feel the same way?
In fact, Zhen Xin and I have already broken up.
Regarding the fake news of our marriage,
we have both given it a lot of thought.
As for this relationship,
we both need some space.
May I ask who initiated the breakup?
It was me.
He agreed to it.
That must have been your agreement.
- Ms. Feng has really been wronged.
- Zhang Zhun.
There's something I must tell you in person.
I love you.
Not as Fang Chi.
But as me.
Zhen Xin truly loves you.
I know.
I love you, too.
I'm at the production crew's hotel.
Give me your room number.
I'm coming to see you.
What are you doing here?
Is something the matter?
"Best Actor Zhen Xin's change of heart on set."
"The third party is actually a man."
"Zhen Xin and Zhang Zhun bond over filming."
"Matching earrings on their left ears."
Who's Zhang Zhun?
The matching earrings are hilarious.
No one would care if he didn't
try to hype himself up, okay?
If Zhen Xin is gay,
I'm seriously going to stop being a fan.
That's so disgusting.
Nowadays, every guy tries to get famous
by selling a "bromance" narrative.
Please dig up some dirt on this Zhang Zhun.
Last night...
I actually had a gift for you.
Pick one.
Choose carefully.
This is the first gift I'll be giving you.
Oh.
I'll take this one.
These two are a pair.
You and I will wear a pair.