You know, this Xiaofang,
she's really got guts.
Two grown men
couldn't slaughter a pig all day.
She did it in one clean stab!
Don't move.
Don't move, don't move.
Xiaofang is pregnant.
Isn't seeing blood
kind of bad for her?
What's bad about it?
I think it's great.
The kid will definitely be brave.
Way better than your son.
No skills, but plenty of attitude.
Xiaowei, cheers.
My life's pretty much over.
Where are you two going?
Sis,
what if Mom really gives me away?
She won't.
I feel just like that pig.
Live or die,
it's all up to my mom.
Aren't I the same?
Grandma's still in the hospital,
and Mom actually has the nerve
to hook me up with Shu Qingcang.
Don't do what you don't want to do.
Find your own way out.
What a coincidence.
Perfect, let me drive you two back.
Sis,
have you
found your own way out?
A media company in town
sent me a private message.
They want to promote me.
I'm interested.
Might as well give it a shot.
Wait, but you're pregnant.
Don't worry.
I'm feeling great right now.
I don't want to be stuck like this.
It's time we started planning
for our futures.
Rather than let others choose for us,
we should choose for ourselves.
Ms. Yang Fanmei,
By the time you read this letter,
I'll already be gone.
I'm taking my
broken heart
and leaving you forever.
I will use the law
Law
I'll use the weapon of the law
to defend my rights.
I hope when we meet again,
you'll regret everything
you've done!
Fanmei,
Did you hit Dandan again?
Didn't I learn it from you?
Learned from me?
I'm grown up and you still hit me!
Stop, stop hitting me, Mom!
My sister's already not that bright.
Why did Dandan
run away this time?
How would I know?
That little rascal!
There's more here.
This is the last time
I'll ever call you Mom.
Your former son, Qian Zhenqing.
Former son?
Mom, don't worry.
Running away is a path every kid
must take growing up.
We've all been through it.
Nonsense.
Which one of you kids
has ever run away from home?
You just didn't know about it.
I ran away once.
I had no money and got too hungry,
so I came back at dinnertime.
You and Dad never even noticed.
You've got some nerve! Some nerve!
Enough, Mom.
Um, Fanmei,
did Dandan have money on him?
I think so.
That's good then.
That little rascal stole my money!
He's your own son,
and you keep calling him a rascal.
Then what does that make you?
What are you?
What are you still sitting here for?
Why aren't you out looking for him?
My brother went to look.
Don't panic, don't actually get mad.
My brother got Lao Miao,
and they're searching the whole village.
Don't worry.
Where's Xiaofang?
Xiaofang,
are you in your room?
What are you doing?
Mom,
Xiaofang isn't here.
Xiaofang!
Fang!
This kid...
With that big belly of hers,
where did she go this time?
Hello?
I'm in the car,
passing Industrial Park Zone 1, Building 10.
Just turn right, then right again.
Right turn.
Let me write it down.
Right, then right again.
Turn, and turn again.
You'll see a bubble tea shop.
What?
Then make a U-turn to the left.
Straight, right turn.
Turn, turn, turn.
Turn what?
Are you driving or am I?
Sorry about that.
Here, we've arrived.
Auntie?
Xiaofang,
where are you?
What are you doing?
Don't push, don't push!
I'm not rushing, not rushing.
Just want to know where you are.
And what you're doing.
Xiaofang!
Are you with Dandan?
Don't, don't touch my belly!
Yes, is Dandan with you?
Is he by your side?
Xiaofang, is he there? Is he?
Yes, yes, yes, he's here.
He's fine, he's fine.
I'm hanging up.
She hung up.
Dandan is with Xiaofang.
Mom,
relax, everything's fine now.
This is when the trouble really starts.
Dandan's still so young,
and he's already running away from home.
That was definitely Xiaofang's idea!
Usually,
when one person runs away,
it's on a whim.
They'll be back soon.
But two together, that's sticking together.
They probably won't be back till tomorrow.
You shut up.
Stirring up trouble all day.
What are you doing?
Stop worrying.
Driver, drive steadily, will you?
Yang Xiaofang, just wait till you get back.
See how I'll deal with you.
A bad workman blames his tools.
Can't handle your own kid,
so you blame others.
How am I...
Where did Xiaofang go?
It sounded chaotic on the phone just now.
Yeah, total chaos.
Fanmei.
Try calling Dandan again.
That little rascal.
You...
The kid blocked me.
Unknown number. Who is it?
Hello, who's this?
Yang Fanyan.
Look what you've done.
Zhi Qiang.
What's the matter?
Jingjing won't take my calls.
She even blocked me.
She won't take your calls,
she blocked you,
what's that got to do with me?
Did you set her up on a blind date?
When we divorced, you didn't want the kid.
Now she's grown, and suddenly you care?
Trying to find someone to support you in old age,
huh?
Let me tell you, it's no use.
You didn't care before,
don't expect any benefits later.
I didn't care before?
I did plenty.
Her monthly allowance,
did I ever shortchange her?
Holiday red envelopes,
did I ever miss one?
Her clothes, her things,
which weren't paid for with my money?
Fine, I'll make a list
and have Jingjing pay you back.
You, you...
This is outrageous!
What are you all staring at?
So unreasonable.
Sis.
Jingjing blocked her dad.
Try calling her yourself.
Hello,
the number you have dialed
is currently busy.
Please try again later.
Busy.
She blocked you too.
She couldn't have blocked me on WeChat, right?
The other party hasn't added you as a friend,
so voice calls aren't allowed.
I mean, so early in the morning,
these three kids...
This is totally absurd,
it's just bizarre.
I get it now, Sis.
Xiaofang, Dandan, Jingjing,
all three vanished at once.
Think about it, this isn't just
a simple case of running away from home.
Just think...
Enough, stop keeping us in suspense.
Just spit it out.
Here's my reasonable deduction.
One person is a coincidence,
two people is a fluke,
but three people
disappearing together?
Isn't this a
premeditated group operation?
Just my guess, just guessing.
You'd better make yourself clear.
Are you really in the dark about this?
Talk, now.
Yeah, what's going on here?
I heard Xiaofang ran off.
Can't be found anywhere.
Did she run off with...
that Shu Qingcang?
No, that wouldn't happen.
Xiaowei told me
the Yang family is quite pleased
with that Shu guy.
She wouldn't run off with him of all people.
Xiaowei!
Stop sleeping, get up now!
Get up, get up, something's happened!
Look at the time, hurry up!
Oh my God.
I didn't see him leave.
What the...
This...
No way.
Where on earth could
these three kids have gone?
Following Xiaofang,
they could be anywhere.
Back then, my plan was
Shanghai first, then Beijing,
and then head abroad, I'd...
Why don't you just fly to the moon?
Mom, you can't just say things like that.
Didn't you say Dandan was missing?
Xiaofang and Jingjing,
they ran away from home too?
Everyone, rest assured.
I've already posted in the group
and mobilized the whole village to search.
Any progress at all,
they'll report to me.
Lao Miao,
no need to make such a big fuss.
It's just Xiaofang and Jingjing
taking Dandan out to play.
They just didn't tell the grown-ups.
It's not running away or anything.
Trying to save face, huh.
Jingjing even blocked you on WeChat.
If that's not running away, what is?
Blocking you counts as running away?
That's not running away?
If I blocked you, would you run away?
What are you two doing?
Cockfighting?
Focus on business.
Yan'er,
you can't take this lightly.
Just last month,
a girl in Houshan Village
ran away from home,
and they still haven't found her.
How old was that girl?
About Dandan's age.
Do you even know how to talk?
Where's Dandan?
Where on earth did you go?
You're worrying Mom to death!
Don't worry, don't worry.
Didn't she just call?
What did she say on the phone?
It was chaotic, couldn't hear.
Couldn't hear clearly.
Too noisy.
Went to the market.
Sounds like it.
Right.
That other little girl,
she told her family
she was going to the market too.
Just stop talking!
What's your problem?
Every time I open my mouth, you shut me up.
Unbelievable.
Who are you to boss me around?
Enough, enough.
Flirting like that,
do it somewhere private.
Get down to business.
Here's the plan, here's the plan.
Let's go search the market.
Old Three,
you check the train and bus stations.
Go look around.
Lao Miao,
I'm counting on you for this.
Don't worry, don't worry.
To the market!
Let's go, go, go.
Mom, Mom, you rest, you rest.
Just rest, okay?
Alright.
Slow down.
Hurry, hurry, hurry!
Fanhu!
Hurry, hurry, come on!
Why are you all so slow?
Hung up.
Don't tell me he
actually ran off with Xiaofang.
Oh my god, this...
Yang Xiaofang!
Would it kill her to pick up?
Although nobody's answering,
at least it connects.
Sis.
That proves she's still around.
Nonsense, of course she's around.
What else could she be?
Huzi just called and said
they're not at the market either.
Hang up, Huzi.
Hurry, tell us.
The train station, the bus station,
they searched everywhere.
No sign of the three of them.
Lao Deng.
Say something.
Everyone, don't panic.
I've already sent Xiao Li to look.
Just wait for news.
Besides,
I think you've been in the big city
for way too long.
Our village may be small,
but public safety here is great.
The last time we caught a thief
was two years ago.
When I caught that thief,
Right, right, right, he...
I can vouch for that.
Under my leadership, our village
won for two years in a row
the "Model Civilized Village" title.
That was before.
We're talking about Dandan now.
How old is Dandan even?
What if he runs into bad people?
Call the police.
I want to report this.
Send officers out now, please.
What if he gets trafficked?
In the time we're wasting,
he could already be out of the province.
If you don't dispatch now,
it'll really be too late.
Someone saw
Xiaofang
taking a bus to the county town.
Let's go.
The county town.
Not answering the phone.
I raised Dandan
with my own blood, sweat, and tears.
He's my whole life.
Enough.
If Dandan is your life,
weren't you planning
to give him to Uncle?
Second Sister, giving Dandan to Uncle?
What were you thinking?
If you hadn't tried to set Shu Qingcang up
with Jingjing,
would Jingjing have run away?
Big Sister, what were you thinking?
What could I think?
I was doing it for Jingjing's sake!
Tell me,
how could this Xiaofang
egg Jingjing on to run away
with them?
Big belly and still won't settle down.
Exactly.
Still not answering the phone.
Who knows what she'll drag
Dandan into doing.
If I find her, I'll definitely...
You'll definitely what?
What's going on here?
It's clearly you people
who broke those kids' hearts.
Don't pin it on my daughter.
Her father is still alive, you know.
Big Brother.
No need to blow up like that.
Big Brother,
don't get angry.
That's terrifying.
Bro, don't drive while angry.
Don't drive while angry.
Watch the road!
Right, right, right.
Safety first.
Right, right.
Hello?
What are you doing?
It's Xiaofang.
It's ringing, it's ringing!
It's ringing!
Quick!
Hello?
Say something, say something!
Who are you?
None of your business who I am.
You three, keep it down.
Tie her up tighter.
Don't let her run.
Tighter!
What do you mean, tie her up?
Who the hell are you?
Where's my daughter?
I'm driving.
Seven p.m. tonight.
Ring Road Station.
I won't wait if you're late.
Dandan!
Shut up, you!
They're all tied up. Keep it down.
Listen to me,
they're just kids.
Kids!
Don't you dare lay a hand on them!
He hung up.
Call back, call back!
Call again, call!
The number you have dialed
He's not answering.
cannot be reached at this time.
Please try again later.
Hello?
Speak up, speak up!
Who are you?
Who is this?
None of your business who I am.
You three, keep it down!
What are you yelling for?
Tie them up tight!
Don't try to run!
Got it!
Who the hell are you?
Where's my daughter?
I'm driving.
Seven o'clock tonight.
Ring Road Station.
Get there fast.
I won't wait if you're late.
It's dead.
What the heck?
It's shut off.
I... I heard Xiaofang just now,
shouting inside.
And then he said something about
tying the three of them up tight.
Won't wait if late... this...
Oh God!
It can't be!
What do we do?
Didn't you say it was fine?
Now what do we do?
What do we do?
If anything happens to Dandan,
I won't go on living, I...
I won't live!
Why are you yelling at me?
Isn't Jingjing with him too?
If anything happens to Jingjing,
you think I could go on living?
Big brother!
Brother!
Big brother, call the police!
Call the police, call them!
Sis, sis!
We can't call the police!
If they panic, our kids could lose a limb!
What are you saying?
Just call the police!
Brother, save Dandan!
Call the police!
Save Dandan!
Please save Dandan!
He said seven o'clock, right?
Yes, yes, yes.
Ring Road intersection.
Won't wait past the time.
Hold on tight!
We're here.
Get out!
The cultural center's out of the way,
so I'll just drop you here.
Head over from here,
just a couple steps and you're there.
Thanks a lot, sir.
No problem.
I'm off.
Okay.
Take care!
Dear viewers,
it's been pouring for days now,
and all the farmland got flooded.
The grain's all soaked through.
I don't know what to do.
For a whole year, little me,
worked from dawn till dusk,
with our old ox,
plowing day after day.
What am I supposed to do now?
Feel bad for the host, want to support her.
Thank you, dear viewers.
Thanks for wanting to support me.
Our family right now,
beans, corn kernels,
we've got nothing left.
Would this work?
Look, dear viewers,
this is rice we grew ourselves.
It's really delicious.
Super fragrant, soft, and sticky.
And what's more,
it's all grown slowly by our own family.
Is it really that good?
It really is delicious.
Hello.
You're Yang Xiaofang, right?
I'm this company's
Chief Executive Officer.
I'm the one who DM'd you.
Weren't you HR?
HR is also me.
Chief Executive Officer,
Chief Operating Officer,
Chief Financial Officer,
every "chief" is me.
But,
that's because our company
is still in its startup phase.
Everything's kept simple,
so I'm wearing multiple hats.
But don't worry,
this won't stop our company
from becoming the industry's
number one.
Come,
let me give you a tour.
Thank you.
What's the name of this livestream?
I'd like to support it.
It's called Xiandao Livestream.
I'm very interested
in the short videos you make.
Good topics, knows how to hype,
and a natural sense for traffic.
Anyone can see you're a talent.
The best value and the tastiest.
But if you want to sell products,
you have to join our company
and go through our
standardized training process.
See this bottle of glue next to me?
One bottle in hand...
Our company
doesn't just focus on
livestream data metrics.
Can also buy groceries and shop.
We also care about livestreaming's
social welfare aspect.
That ox you just saw?
That's our farmer-support livestream.
In short,
we focus on both material and spiritual aspects.
These livestreamers you see here,
they've been here less than a week,
and they're already on fire.
Once you join us,
we will
tailor-make for you a
creative
livestream selling career path.
Isn't this just assembly-line copying?
Exactly.
You saw right through to the essence.
It's copy,
and paste.
That's the secret to livestream traffic.
And you
are about to join this
great assembly line,
and become one who copies money.
These are all from our
training class kids' drawings
Kids with zero experience,
after just one course,
can produce such excellent work.
All original by the kids.
Not copied.
How could these be copies?
Every single piece
is the kids' original work.
If you're interested,
I can walk you through
the details of our training class.
Right now, you only need
a small investment
to give your child
a future as an artist.
Teacher,
um,
I wanted to ask,
can I still learn at my age?
You want to learn?
Um, um, I...
Let me show you, I know a little.
Here.
But these are all copies.
The fundamentals are pretty solid.
So, do you guys
have an adult class?
I want to study systematically.
I want to create my own originals too.
Yes.
Of course we do.
I've always upheld
the philosophy of teaching all comers.
No matter
what age you are,
as long as you want to learn,
we can help you fulfill your artistic dream.
Great.
Come, come, follow me.
Look,
that
is the Chinese painting classroom.
And over there we have
the watercolor classroom.
Look at these other kids,
how well they paint!
Teacher,
with my level of skill,
how long would it take?
If you want better results,
we also offer one-on-one classes.
One-on-one?
But, uh,
for one-on-one, well,
the cost
might be a bit higher.
Why don't you go back
and discuss it with your parents?
Give your mom a call.
Me? Is that necessary?
Yes, it's necessary.
Mom
Hello
I was just about to call you
and you called first
Transfer me five thousand yuan.
Ask him what he needs the money for
Um, son
What do you need the money for?
Is Xiaofang with you?
Why would I be with Xiaofang?
I wish I were
but she'd have to be willing
Just hurry and transfer me the money
I need it urgently
Make him tell you why he wants the money
You've got to tell me first, you, you, you
What do you need the money for?
What if someone's scamming you?
Who could possibly scam me?
I'm not stupid
I need the money to learn painting
Painting?
Don't you already know how?
What I do,
you call that knowing how?
That's just tracing and copying.
I need to learn to create on my own
Originals
The teacher said
I have a solid foundation
Three months studying with him is enough
Wait
son
why all of a sudden
do you want to study painting again?
Are you giving up on Xiaofang?
It's because of Xiaofang
that I'm going to study painting
Dad wants me to work with my brother
but even if I work myself to death
I still can't win Xiaofang back
Only by painting well now
will I have a chance
to win Xiaofang back
Mom, let me tell you
I'm serious this time
Son, listen to Mom
Qi Xiaowei!
Where are you right now?
Get your butt back here!
I...
Where I am is none of your business
I'm not coming back
Hanging up
I'm not eating
Stop mimicking me.
Are you here to file a lawsuit?
Yes.
I want to sue my mom.
Little one,
are you scared 'cause you didn't finish your homework
and Mommy's gonna spank you?
I hate you grown-ups the most.
Faking cute on purpose.
You're so cheesy, not cute at all.
Your teacher must've told you,
respecting others is respecting yourself.
Wow, it really is
you post-00s kids' world now.
I'm a post-10s kid.
A post-10s little one.
Here, have some water.
You know what,
you're pretty cute.
You're cute too.
Thanks.
However,
filing a lawsuit requires lawyer's fees.
Money, do you have any?
I have money.
Little one,
is this from your New Year's red envelopes?
Hey, what are you doing?
What are you doing?
I said I have money,
I didn't say I'd give it to you.
How much are the lawyer's fees?
You haven't told me yet.
The lawyer's fees are... Wait.
What now?
You don't even know what my case is about
and you dare to charge me?
Oh, kiddo,
I really give up on you.
Tell me, why are you suing your mom?
The complaint.
Could you check my online
loan application process?
Why hasn't it
been approved yet?
One moment, let me check for you.
Th-thank you for your trouble.
No problem.
I really need the money urgently.
It's for my grandma's medical treatment.
Please hold on.
You've missed one field here.
Immediate family contact info.
Per company policy,
this is a required document.
I don't want them knowing about this.
If you don't fill in a family contact,
we can't process it for you.
Come on, relax, relax.
Give me a bit more emotion.
Perfect!
That's great!
That's spot on!
Wait, wait.
What are we doing?
We're imitating her!
I'm telling you,
we can totally pull this off.
Why should I imitate her?
Step one:
We piggyback on whoever's trending.
She's a huge celebrity!
We've gotta create something
with visual impact for the audience.
Come on, look over here.
Now, turn your body to the right.
Too much.
Back a bit, just a tiny bit.
Right hand, raise your right hand.
Rest it on your chin.
That's great!
Innocent with a hint of allure.
That look in your eyes is perfect.
Step two:
Build a persona.
And in that regard, your conditions
are even more outstanding.
Livestreaming with a kid!
You don't even have to act.
That belly of yours,
it's the real deal.
All we need to do is make up
a tragic backstory.
For example, your husband
died saving someone.
That kind of positive-energy storyline,
audiences eat it right up.
So basically, make up stories.
Quick learner!
Hey kid,
I understand your troubles.
But,
you're a minor.
I need to take you back to your parents first.
Got it?
Come on, let's take him to...
Hey!
Why'd he crawl under the table?
Hurry, get him out!
That's so dangerous!
Come out, come out.
Kid!
What are you doing to my leg?
Come on out.
Stop tugging on it!
Help!
I've already got the debut theme figured out.
We'll call it this:
"Women may be weak,
but mothers are strong."
When the time comes, you play up
your single-mom identity.
Milk the sob story hard.
There's huge potential!
What's so sad about being single with a kid?
Not actually sad, just fake it!
Don't be in such a rush to leave.
People like you,
I've seen plenty of.
The moment you get a bit of traffic,
you think you're a big deal.
But let me tell you,
this world has its own rules.
You get it?
I'm only saying this because you've got potential.
So I'll spell it out for you.
If you wanna make money,
don't treat yourself like a human,
and don't treat others like humans either.
Get the money in your hands first.
Am I right?
Everyone does it this way.
Who are you to be the exception?
I'm not the exception.
And don't feel inferior, okay?
Me?
Me, feel inferior?
What do I have to feel inferior about?
I run such a big company.
Sooner or later, you'll crawl back begging me.
I'm telling you, your words are too hurtful.
How can you be like this?
Me, inferior?
Do I, do I look inferior to you?
Where's my phone?
My phone.
I'm all flustered right now.
I livestreamed with it for a week.
Now I stink all over.
Just looking at it annoys me.
Relax, once we finish filming, it's gone.
We'll just sell it.
You won't have to see it again.
That useless thing.
Why bother keeping it?
I want it gone, right now.
You hear me?
I'm really busy.
I can't find a buyer for it.
I've got my own work to do.
Besides,
who'd want to buy such an old cow?
Forget it.
We've got a flight to catch.
Let's just go.
You borrow money, you spend it
Why must you tell the family?
Seriously
Just say so if you won't lend it
Jingjing
Xiaofang
This town is way too small
Where'd you even get a cow?
It... it got laid off.
Help! Help! Help!
Dandan
They're bullying me
What's going on?
Why are you here?
They're bullying me
I came to report my mom
Look
Your sis got you a cow
Dandan
Mom was wrong
I shouldn't have said I'd
give you to Grand Uncle.
Second Sis
Why would you give Dandan away?
Uncle wants the baby
in Xiaofang's belly.
Xiaofang won't agree
So I thought
Dandan is also a boy
And
Uncle's family is well-off.
Uncle wants the baby
in Xiaofang's belly
Who said that?
When did this happen?
Are you really that clueless
or just pretending?
Uncle hasn't contacted us
for so many years
Suddenly treating us, giving red envelopes
What's he after?
Isn't it all for that boy
in Xiaofang's belly?
Big Sis, if you knew
why didn't you tell us?
She thinks she can handle it
Like we're all fools and idiots
She knew exactly what Shu Qingcang
was scheming
Yet she forced Xiaofang to date him
She's the one who drove Xiaofang away
Jingjing's grandma is dying
And at a time like this
she pushes her to meet Shu Qingcang.
Yang Fanyan
If I were Jingjing
I wouldn't call you my mother
Fine
It's all my fault
All these years
I've toiled and sacrificed for this family
Thinking of each and every one of you
I was wrong, okay?
It's all my fault, alright?
If my life could buy back
the safety of my three children
I'd take it. I was wrong
Okay?
Dandan
After you finish eating
give your mom a call
She must be worried
I'm not calling
Let her worry
She's the one who wanted to give me away.
Fine, then eat first
Call her a bit later, okay?
I came to borrow money
Didn't get a single cent
I came to find a job
No job found
Lost my phone
Picked up this little guy
I came to sue my mom
Lawsuit fell through
Ate a burger
With him along
how are we gonna catch a ride?
Yeah, right
This...
No one will take us
Then...
Then we'll walk back without a ride
When would we ever get there?
Didn't you run away from home?
What, in a rush to go home now?
Who wants to see Yang Fanmei?
I just want to sleep
Just eat your burger
Boss
Um...
Are you using this cart right now?
Could you lend it to us?
We'll give you a deposit.
We'll return it in a couple of days.
I'm leaving in a few days.
I won't need this cart anymore.
If you want it, take it for fifty yuan.
Thank you.
Problem solved.
Boss.
Are you transferring this shop?
Actually, I'm just staying here as a traveler.
I've experienced this place enough.
Next month,
I'm heading to my next stop.
Wow, so cool!
This shop of yours,
does it make money?
It definitely makes money.
There are lots of my regulars
around here.
Whoever takes over won't have to worry.
I'm not going back to Guangdong to work.
I plan to stay in the county town.
Find a job and stay with Grandma.
Xiaofang.
You were right.
Live in the moment.
What I can do right now
is for every day Grandma's in the hospital,
I'll spend one more day with her.
As for the rest, I'll take it one step at a time.
Right.
I even learned to do nails before.
Maybe someday when I make money,
I could open my own nail salon.
Jingjing.
Haven't you always
wanted to open a nail salon?
Isn't this perfect?
I'm in a hurry to leave.
If you take it over,
I'll
give you an extra 20% off.
The shop has everything.
Pay today, open for business tomorrow.
Then how about
we don't be employees anymore
and just be our own bosses?
Isn't that too hasty?
Then I'll buy in as a shareholder.
I'll start from scratch,
run a business like Lao Qian and make big money.
Help Lao Qian pay off his debts.
Can't I?
Will it work?
Let's give it a try.
Even it says it'll work.
If it says yes, then I say yes too.
If it says it works, it works.
I've got it all figured out.
I want to make a drinks bar.
I can make coffee,
I can make coconut candy.
I don't know if people around here
like drinking this kind of stuff.
So I...
What do you think?
Give me some suggestions.
Your idea sounds great.
Let's go back and plan it out.
What kind of mess is this?
It was all a big mix-up.
It's all your fault.
Watching movies rotted your brain.
You were the one who took it seriously first!
And now you're blaming me?
Me, serious?
You... you...
Where do you think Xiaofang and them
could be right now?
My guess is
they're not coming home.
Let's head back too.
Go home.
What's wrong?
What happened?
We're out of gas.
Can you two handle this?
It's fine.
I just checked the GPS.
The nearest gas station
is ten kilometers away.
Ten kilometers?
Before the weather cools, we're done for.
We'd better find someone
to bring us some gas.
Who's gonna bring it?
Look.
It's not gonna rain soon, is it?
No way.
Then what?
We'd better hurry.
What if it starts raining?
Dandan!
Okay, hurry.
No rain yet.
Dandan!
Sis!
Slow down, slow down.
Look, everyone.
Dad!
Jingjing!
Stop, stop, stop!
Dandan, hurry, hurry!
Dandan!
Mom!
You scared me to death.
Why are they here?
Mom.
Are you okay?
You came looking for me!
You're drenched in sweat.
Son.
I'm so sorry.
Mom never once wanted
to give you away.
Mommy was wrong.
You scared me to death.
What happened?
I thought you guys
had been kidnapped.
I'm sorry.
I didn't see anything.
I didn't see a thing.
Good thing you're here, Brother Ox.
Guess we'll just make do together.
Your car broke down?
It's out of gas.
I want to file a complaint against my mother.
She may have given birth to me,
and raised me,
but she neither understands me,
nor respects me.
She always says I don't know a damn thing.
I want to grow up fast,
because only when you're an adult
do your words carry any weight,
and only then can you be respected.
I want to tell my mom,
I'm not some clueless
little brat.
And I'm not some object
she can just give away to anyone.
This time, I'm not the one in the wrong.
She is.
Blow a big one!
Look at them.
These kids, they've all grown up.
It's time to let them go.
Actually, it's them
who are pulling us forward.
Mom
I really want to go study painting.
I don't want to follow my brother into
that construction work.
Mom supports you.
Mom has a little stash
of cash.
Lao Qitou!
Where's my money?
Trying to mess with me?
Let's work hard.
Work hard to prove we don't need
them making decisions for us.
But right now,
we can't even scrape together the money.
We can find outside help.
Who?
Take them down one by one.