Are you okay?
You know, I have a thing for cute boys.
Hit me up if you're interested.
So your name is Ainosuke.
It's not like I'm into guys.
Because I want to try
having an internal orgasm.
Want me to help you?
I'm
really good at it.
I thought I was dumped.
Is it because sleeping with an
inexperienced brat is boring?
Shall we finish what
we started last time?
I might end up falling for you, you know?
How about we date until
Ai-chan gets tired of me?
Oh, no!
Today is my final job interview.
I have to go.
Are you serious?
Yes, really.
Come in.
Excuse me.
You're quite energetic.
Thank you for coming to
our company's interview.
Someone who looks just like him?
No way.
The interviewer is the older guy
who hit on you? This is ridiculous.
Are you being played by him?
Just fooling around.
You know...
I have a thing for cute boys.
Today, just focus on
making yourself feel good.
How about we date until
Ai-chan gets tired of me?
There are other companies anyway.
Don't sweat it.
(Incoming Call: Okumi-san)
Is it okay not to answer?
It's fine.
"Are the Sexy Buttocks Not Good?"
(Episode 2)
Ai-chan, did you secure a job offer?
Not yet.
Alright, alright.
I'll handle the rest.
Why don't you head off early?
I happened to be walking this guy nearby.
Your shift is almost over, right?
Yeah.
(Missed Calls: Okumi-san)
Talk to you later.
Ai-chan.
Today, just focus on
making yourself feel good.
It's Okumi.
I must have startled you. I'm sorry.
Are you eating well, Ai-chan?
I want to talk to you.
I'll call you again.
Are you treating me like a child?
(Voicemails left behind)
(They're all about how
he's worried about me.)
Are you finished?
Teramachi.
You came because you
were worried about me, right?
I'm just walking the dog.
I really act like a kid, don't I?
Huh?
Making people worry and getting comforted.
I thought I was dumped.
Is it because sleeping with an
inexperienced brat is boring?
That you couldn't even be
bothered to contact me.
Of course, if I were a player,
I'd probably just play around.
But...
You're different.
I want to grow up.
What's wrong?
I'm sorry, Teramachi.
- I'm leaving.
- Oh.
Wait, where are you going? Whoa!
I'm sorry.
- Ah!
- Ai-chan!
Why?
- Were you following me?
- No, I wasn't.
I'm his friend, Teramachi.
This guy is a really good person.
Please make sure to cherish him.
You don't have to tell me.
I will cherish him.
Well, that's good.
See ya, Ainosuke.
Yeah.
He likes you, doesn't he?
Huh?
No way. That's impossible.
You're the only one who hasn't noticed.
It's been a while.
Even though I hate to admit it...
I still like you.
Ai-chan.
I haven't taken a shower yet.
- I missed you.
- What's gotten into you?
I'm your man, right, Ai-chan?
Or am I mistaken?
What were you doing before you met me?
Did something happen with Teramachi?
No.
Nothing happened.
He has someone he likes.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
Probably.
Are you jealous by any chance?
But why?
Because I like you, of course.
Do you like me?
You're allowed to only like me.
Didn't you want to see me?
It's not like that.
Ai-chan.
If I were the president,
would you hate me?
You should have just told me sooner.
I'm sorry.
Well, it's not like I
hid it on purpose.
Even though I'm the president,
I just inherited the family business.
It's not like I'm anything special.
If I wanted to play you, I would've
bragged about being president long ago.
But I would never do that.
I still can't wrap my head around it.
After all, being a president
isn't that simple.
I won't join Okumi-san's company.
Huh?
So please reject my application.
- I understand.
- Let's leave it at that then.
Huh?
I want to get to know Okumi-san better.
- Is that okay?
- Yeah.
(I still know nothing about this person.)
(I'll probably keep
getting surprised by him.)
(Though I want to know Okumi-san,
there's no need to rush.)
What's wrong?
(I'll wait until the day
you're ready to tell me.)
Let's go.
I'm sorry.
I received a job offer.
- Huh?
- How did this happen?
(Job Offer)
Our company's hiring decisions
are made by HR, you know.
Are you still going to decline the offer?
Are we going to do this at the office too?
Yeah.
As much as possible.
You have no intention of behaving, do you?
I feel like my new life in the workforce
is going to be full of drama.
(Next Episode Preview) Sometimes
I wonder if I'm really good enough.
Long time no see, Ai-chan.
You really love to joke around, old man.
Just because I was married
doesn't mean I only like women.
Wait...
- We're outside.
- I thought I'd never fall in love again.
And that I'd just die alone.
I never expected to meet you.
If you're lonely, I'm here.
Let me see more of your face
when you're feeling good, Ai-chan.