All characters, actions, locations,
[KNOT]
organizations, professions,
and events depicted in this series
are fictional and created
for entertainment purposes only.
The series does not intend to endorse
or encourage any behaviors
shown on screen.
Viewer discretion is advised.
♪ You're so worth searching for ♪
♪ Do you love me at all? ♪
♪ Rounding with the little kisses
to my lips before ♪
♪ Oh, babe, I want you to be mine ♪
♪ Please do something ♪
♪ To show me signs ♪
♪ And make my world to be alright ♪
♪ Hold my hand tight ♪
♪ With bright eyes ♪
♪ Don't you think
that I belonged to you? ♪
♪ Always dominated someone talking to ♪
♪ Oh, you so look like a fool ♪
♪ Finally you have to lose ♪
♪ Oh, have to lose ♪
♪ Have to lose ♪
[KNOT]
[Previously on Knot]
Let my brother go.
You're moving in with me.
I'll take care of you.
Nakhin told me your name's Phatsa,
which means rain.
You really smell like rain.
I'll have Ai and Sila prepare
all the documents.
At your service, boss.
Take a look first.
Wow.
So many?
How many decades has your company
been around?
I only had them compile
the past three years.
Ah.
Take a look first.
Ask if you don't understand.
Why are the maintenance costs in Sathorn
so much higher than other places?
That's a commercial area.
So to avoid business hours,
maintenance can only be done at night.
Plus, with traffic congestion, there are
hidden costs like overtime pay.
That's why it's more expensive
than other areas.
OK.
If that's the case,
why are the maintenance costs in Ekkamai,
which is also downtown,
so much lower?
The alley we own
is in a residential area,
so construction can be done
during normal hours.
And over there,
we built it as
a community commercial center,
so we can close off one section
for construction
while keeping another section open
for business.
They won't interfere with each other.
I see.
I just don't quite understand.
With the costs so high in Sathorn,
why haven't the rents increased
accordingly?
During the day, all the shops
can operate normally
and use the space as usual, yet both
the rent and maintenance fees here
are about the same as Rang Nam
and Ekkamai.
I think the cost burden is too heavy here.
Mr. Phatsa is saying exactly what
Mr. Nakhun mentioned in the last meeting.
Not long ago, Mr. Nakhun also pointed out
the issue of uniform rent pricing.
Impressive. You understood all the details
after just one look.
And you even pointed out
the project's blind spots.
Isn't it obvious?
Anyone can see it.
Very impressive.
Sir.
Hello, Mr. Narate.
Nakhin, I want to start learning
how to shoot.
I want to shoot coolly like in the movies.
If you think a gun is for looking cool,
then I think you should just stand
and watch for now.
I was just joking.
You can't be impatient with guns.
You must stay calm when using a gun.
Remember, when the gun is in our hands,
other people's lives are too.
A gun is not a toy. It's not for fun
or showing off.
Don't act on impulse.
If you feel emotionally unstable,
whether it's being angry,
irritable,
or out of control,
stay away from guns.
As far away as possible.
Understand?
Understood.
Good.
Then let's start with the basics.
Hold the gun steady.
Stand properly.
And stop thinking about looking cool.
Got it. Then I won't
embarrass myself today.
We'll do it another time.
Hello, Nakhun.
Hello.
Your partner is really pretty.
Hey, it's not like that.
Oh, really?
No.
Don't talk nonsense.
He was just giving a compliment.
Don't join in and tease me too.
This is a shooting range, but why does it
feel like a couple's public reveal?
I told you it's Nakhun's partner.
I told you no.
Blushing like this, can you still
hold the gun steady today?
Of course I can.
I'm not blushing.
Still being stubborn
when you are blushing.
Go practice your shooting.
Aim carefully.
Mm.
Then slowly pull the trigger.
OK.
It's a small world.
I didn't expect to run into you here.
I didn't expect you to come
for shooting practice either.
People need some self-defense skills.
Especially with the news
being so lively lately.
I heard the eldest son of the Devathitirat
family bit an Omega's neck.
And a helpless Omega at that.
Phatsa is not helpless.
It seems he is very special to you.
Of course.
Much more special than most people.
Then I should get to know him.
See what kind of person makes a True Alpha
so protective.
I am...
Amintra.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Phatsa.
Do you know how to shoot?
How about a competition?
Miss Amintra...
Uh, that's not necessary...
Enough.
This is not a place for a game of dare.
Or are you afraid?
Sure. I can do that.
Miss Amintra.
Phatsa.
If you want to compete,
I'm happy to keep you company
and relieve your boredom.
Good.
I like that you don't back down.
I like it too.
You are very skilled.
I concede this shooting match.
You win.
You gave up faster than I thought.
A loss is a loss.
No need to put on a brave face.
What a pity. I thought you could
let me have more fun.
I'm not here to spoil the fun.
Well said, sister-in-law.
Forget it, today is boring.
Let's go, Kingyok.
OK.
Hope we can play something
more interesting next time.
I thought you two would really go at it.
This is enough.
At least it ended well today.
I'm going to the restroom first.
Sila, you go with Phatsa.
OK.
No need.
Phatsa shot this.
Nice shooting.
At least he didn't miss the target.
What's wrong?
Phatsa didn't shoot to score.
What do you mean?
This shot
is to disarm the opponent.
This shot is to restrict their movement.
This shot...
is to end the fight.
As for this top shot,
if it hit,
it would be fatal.
Phatsa didn't aim at the bullseye
to score.
But he fought back immediately
upon picking up the gun,
as if his body instinctively knew
where to hit to stop the enemy instantly.
Like shooting in actual combat.
Mm.
But Phatsa looks like someone
who has never practiced shooting.
That's what makes it interesting.
That's an instinct.
Not an instinct that an ordinary shooter
would have.
But an instinct that only someone
who knows how to kill a target would have.
At least he knows what to do
to stop the target instantly.
So, he's quite formidable.
Yes, quite formidable.
If so, it seems many interesting things
will happen in the future.
Yeah.
Is Phatsa here, Ongsa?
He's not here today.
He didn't answer my calls
or read my messages.
Phatsa must be quite busy lately.
I heard he moved in with someone else.
Hmm...
Really?
I wanted to invite Phatsa to a movie.
Isn't it almost time to be in Heat?
I think it's safer to stay at home.
Yeah, but I'm wearing a collar,
so it should be fine, right?
And it's safe if Phatsa's with me,
isn't it?
Is it really safe?
Of course, because Phatsa
could be an Alpha, right?
You misunderstood.
Phatsa's an Omega.
What?
That's what the test results say.
How is he doing now then?
I heard
he has already formed a bond.
Has he really formed a bond?
Mr. Phatsa.
I didn't order this, did I?
Mr. Nakhun ordered us
to prepare this for you.
Enjoy your meal.
Thank you.
Please eat.
Aren't you coming in?
We need to watch you finish the meal.
I can do it myself.
No, these are Mr. Nakhun's orders.
Sir.
It's fine.
No.
Don't.
Don't move.
Sir, I can't get it on you like this.
Sorry.
Put it on properly.
Do you want to play together?
Mr. Phatsa.
Mr. Nakhun has asked me
to prepare the meal.
Please go eat first.
You have an online meeting this afternoon.
I have put the materials in the study.
OK.
Mr. Phatsa hasn't come down
for a meal yet.
OK.
Why didn't you go down to eat?
I'm not hungry.
You have to eat even if you're not hungry.
It's not good to keep everyone
waiting for the meal, you know?
But I don't know what to do.
I'm bored to death staying here all day.
And someone has to drive me
every time I go out.
When you're not around,
I don't even know how to cope with
being in this empty house.
Here,
you can do whatever you want.
Didn't I tell you?
I will give you everything you want.
But...
You are so busy with work.
But I will still make time
for important things.
Let's go eat now.
I'm hungry.
Nakhun.
How much longer do I have to stay here?
Maybe for a lifetime.
I used to think...
That after I graduate,
I would find a good job,
work hard,
live the life I want,
and go everywhere I want to go.
I'm sorry.
Making this bond is no different
from being tied up in chains.
It's like a dead knot
trapping me constantly.
If this continues, one day...
I will die of sorrow.
I won't let that happen.
Where are you taking me?
Nowhere.
Whose is this?
Yours.
Mine?
Yesterday you said you didn't want to
bother the driver every time you went out.
I can't accept it.
It's too expensive.
This car is a gift for you.
All the paperwork is in your name.
But...
I don't want it.
If you don't want it, you can leave it
parked, or sell it. Whatever you want.
Hey.
Are you mad at me?
I just wanted to buy it for you.
If accepting it feels like a burden,
just throw it away.
It's not that I don't want it.
It's just that the things you give
are too expensive.
Didn't I say I'd give you everything?
Are you working tomorrow?
Do you want me to drive you?
My company is very far away.
I'm a very good driver.
Do you have a license?
Of course I do.
Are you not mad anymore?
I wasn't mad in the first place.
The car is dirty.
Let's go check out
the Rangsit warehouse tomorrow.
I want you to see the actual site.
I can go too?
Didn't you want to help me with work?
Of course, boss.
Just tell me, I'll do anything. But...
Can you afford it?
Then name your price.
What's your minimum salary?
As my assistant, about 30,000.
But if it's you...
Is 300,000 enough?
300,000?
Is it too little?
Or 500,000?
At 30,000, I was ready to latch onto you.
300,000, deal.
Someone has already bought it.
Phatsa.
Smells so good.
I think if this place is transformed into
a creative space,
or a rental studio, it would be
more suitable.
You
always manage to impress me.
Didn't I tell you? I really want to work.
I'll go take a call.
Ai,
I'll leave Phatsa in your care.
OK.
Do you want to keep looking around?
Sure.
Hello.
I'm at the warehouse now.
It'll probably be a while.
There's so much stuff here.
What was this place used for before?
It was probably a warehouse.
Hey!
Ah!
Phatsa!
Mr. Nakhun!
What happened?
Stay with me! Are you OK?
Phatsa.
Stay with me!
Are you OK?
Phatsa.
Mr. Nakhun.
Slow down.
Phatsa.
Mr. Nakhun.
Ah, easy!
Be careful.
Easy.
-Ah!
-Slow down.
Can you walk?
How do you feel?
It's safe now.
I'll take my leave then.
Thank you, doctor.
Are you OK?
Why are you so pale?
I'm fine.
When I saw you standing there just now,
my heart really felt like it stopped.
But I'm right here now.
And everything is fine.
Are you sure?
How did you get into an accident outside?
Does it hurt, kid?
Ouch,
a little bit.
Where are you hurt? Where?
Oh, you scared me to death!
Thank you, Ms. Kampirada.
Didn't I tell you? Call me Mom.
Uh...
OK, Mom.
You...
Nakhun, how could you take him out
and get into an accident?
Why didn't you take good care of him?
No, Mom. It's not his fault.
I usually heal quickly from injuries.
Oh, it must hurt a lot.
If you can't even take care of yourself
with this little thing,
then you shouldn't do anything at all!
This little injury won't kill him.
What's wrong with this family?
Instead of doing your own business,
you're hovering around a
helpless Omega!
We have a problem.
Our bar in Thonglor
was raided by the police for drugs.
How did this happen?
Mr. Naphitch was there at the time.
He's been taken to the police station.
What?
Wasn't it already inspected?
Hello, Mr. Nakhun.
What's the situation?
According to the preliminary urine test,
Mr. Naphitch tested negative for drugs.
However, the reason he's still here
is because he got into a fight
with the bar owner.
That bastard deserved to be beaten,
didn't he?
Hey,
calm down first.
Calm down? I didn't do anything wrong!
Let's talk this through calmly.
It's good that nothing came up.
Nakhin,
take Naphitch to the car.
I'm not going.
I'm not leaving until I beat that bastard
until he spits blood!
I've kept him for nothing.
Leave this to me.
Let's go first, bro.
We'll talk in the car. Get up!
Listen to me first.
Did you put drugs in my bar?
I...
I had no choice.
That place was originally
your family's property.
After the mortgage was released,
I bought it back.
I opened a bar on that land
not because I wanted to do more business,
but because I wanted to leave you
a place to stand.
I wanted you to come back and take over
the place that once
belonged to your family.
I know you're helping me.
I know.
I never forgot.
You know what?
You didn't just ruin yourself.
You ruined your family's reputation.
And you ruined my trust in you.
Why are you so impulsive?
So boring.
Bro, what do you know?
You're back.
Why are you still up?
I was waiting for you.
Are you tired?
A little bit.
Then get some rest.
I can't help you with anything,
but at least I can keep you company.
Then may I hug you?
No.
Didn't I tell you not to?
But you're hugging me right now.
Oh.
I'm not hugging you.
It's just a touch.
Hmm.
You're so bad. Aren't you tired?
Go take a shower first.
You'll feel better.
I'm going to take a shower.
I just realized how tiring it is
to be an Omega.
Not only does your body change,
but your freedom is also restricted.
It's just like being a prisoner.
Well.
You've already been bitten.
And the one who bit you
is a True Alpha.
Just bear with it for now.
Once your pheromones stabilize,
things should slowly get better.
Oh, Phatsa, Ongsa,
everyone is here today.
Are you guys talking about
something serious?
It's just Phatsa
complaining about his life as an Omega.
That's normal, Phatsa.
Being an Omega in an Alpha-dominated world
is not easy.
Let me, the expert, give you a lesson.
I'll teach you how to use your instincts,
what to be careful of,
and how you can control Alphas instead.
You can count on it.
Since you're being my expert,
about being bitten,
is there any way to get back at him?
Speaking of being bitten,
I really want to meet that Alpha.
His character is so bad.
You barely knew each other,
and he bit you already.
These Alphas
are all the same.
They always trust their beastly instincts
more than their brains.
That's true.
However,
you can't entirely blame them
for losing control.
Phatsa, are you defending them?
No, I'm not.
Since I got bitten, he's been
really good to me.
So good that I almost forgot
he took away my freedom.
Taking good care of you is one thing,
but ruining a rare breed like us
is really hard to forgive.
But let's not talk about Alphas anymore.
I'm hungry.
Let's order some food. It's on me.
Let's treat it as a celebration for Phatsa
dodging that falling beam.
Speaking of that piece of wood,
it really hurt when it first hit me.
But it got better quickly.
Later, it hardly hurt at all.
Is that some special Alpha-Omega trait?
But I've never heard of it either.
Could it be that you are
that type of Omega,
so your body recovers faster than normal?
Let's eat.
Phatsa.
The car is already waiting for you
at the door.
What the hell? I've been here
only for less than an hour.
Mr. Nakhun specifically instructed
that you shouldn't stay out too long
because he's worried about the injury
on your arm.
And it seems Mr. Nakhun still cares a lot
about the warehouse accident.
He has a point.
I just heard Phatsa saying
the wound was itching.
Go home and rest.
Bro, why are you taking his side?
Go back and tell your boss
to give me another half hour.
Let me finish dinner
with my friends first, OK?
I'll go back as soon as I finish.
I promise I won't run off.
But Mr. Nakhun...
Just tell him if he doesn't let me finish
my meal, I'm not coming home at all.
OK.
Oh my, Phatsa,
you even have bodyguards watching you
all the way.
I don't know if he's worried
about the wound or worried about you.
Saengnuea...
I'm just joking.
He's so worried that he's going insane.
Bro.
Hand me the drink menu.
I'm thirsty. I want to have
four or five drinks.
I'll wait for your order at the bar.
Five drinks.
What do you want to drink?
You can order, bro.
Do you want anything?
No, thanks.
Saves me some money.
I'll have a glass of this.
This one.
And...
This one and this one.
This one.
Right.
Another cup.
Four drinks.
This one.
No way.
Oh, Primprao. Do you want donuts today?
Yes. Are there any left?
Yes, a moment please.
OK.
Bro, can I ask you a question?
Sure.
Is it weird if I haven't gotten
my secondary gender tested yet?
Not at all.
Why do you ask all of a sudden?
My family keeps saying they're waiting
to see what I'll present as.
So I was thinking, if the result isn't
what they hope for,
will I still be the same me?
Of course you will.
Whether you're an Alpha, a Beta,
or an Omega,
you're still a human being, aren't you?
Really?
Of course.
But more importantly, it's about
what kind of person we become.
Not what the test results say we are.
Don't overthink it.
Primprao, your donuts are ready.
Thank you.
And thank you, bro.
Mm.
Take your time growing up.
The drinks are ordered.
Let's eat.
Sister-in-law, Brother has
a last-minute meeting,
so he asked me to take over.
He was afraid leaving a beauty outside
for too long
would attract moths
and infect your wounds.
Didn't I tell you not to call me that?
And what's with that guy, sending people
to watch me endlessly?
So, did you like the flowers
I sent to the shop?
What flowers?
Or did something happen
that I don't know about?
Have you eaten?
Come.
Phatsa.
Mr. Nakhin must be busy.
And I happen to be hungry.
Hungry and free, I won't hold back then.
Eat up, these are all Ongsa's favorites.
Hello, I'm Saengnuea.
Are you an Alpha?
I can smell your pheromone.
Hello, Saengnuea.
With this scent, you must be an Omega.
Yes.
It's rare to see an Omega as pretty as you
with such a nice pheromone scent.
You are really pretty.
Ongsa.
What's wrong? You look pale.
Nothing, this food is just too bland.
I'm full.
Come again next time, bro.
Saengnuea, teach me more about Omegas
next time.
I'll teach you when you are free, Phatsa.
Ai.
Can you give me a little more time?
What's the rush?
I haven't finished chatting
with my friends.
But it's been a while.
Just a little longer, OK?
OK.
Hello. I know. I'm getting in the car
right now.
Stop nagging. It was just a moment.
Oh, Phatsa, since you became his,
you really do go left when he says left
and right when he says right.
Honestly, are you in such a rush
to get back
because you can't stand being away
from his pheromones,
or because you can't stand
being away from him?
It's not about that at all.
I'm just afraid his family
will cause a scene again.
I just don't want things to blow up.
What are you laughing at?
I'm leaving.
I'm going to work.
Wait.
Where are you rushing off to?
I haven't finished speaking.
I'll come find you tonight.
No need to come.
There's nothing between us anymore.
I also forgave you
for what happened that night.
Let's be clear in the future.
Don't let the life of an ordinary Beta
like me
become more messy than it is now.
Oh, why isn't anyone answering?
Ongsa.
I can't get a car to pick me up. Look.
Let me see.
I called several times
and no one answered.
Nakhin happens to be free.
May I trouble you to take Saengnuea
for me?
May I?
If it's convenient, may I trouble you?
Yes.
I'll head off then, bro.
See you later.
Thank you.
Did you have fun?
Yeah, I did.
But you really shouldn't have asked Nakhin
to pick me up.
Ongsa and I haven't finished talking.
Ongsa is a Beta, right?
Yes.
Then invite him to come to our house
next time.
Can I really invite him?
Of course. Isn't he your friend?
Actually, I have another friend
named Saengnuea, who is an Omega.
He taught me a lot about Omegas.
Can I invite him too?
There are still many Alphas who haven't
formed a bond here.
Your friend Saengnuea...
It's best he doesn't come here.
Is it really that dangerous?
If something goes wrong, or an Omega
goes in Heat, they might get bitten.
So it really is quite dangerous.
Hey!
You...
Didn't I say not to get touchy-feely?
Can I hug you?
No.
I just came back from outside.
I'm all hot and sweaty.
But I want to smell you.
No.
Then smell my hand first.
Hey, you!
Why are you licking? Stop! Get out!
Phatsa...
No.
Then give me your clothes.
Clothes...
Clothes?
Take off your shirt and give it to me.
What is he doing?
Why is it taking so long?
Phatsa.
I should go take a shower.
Why did you have to fall in love
with a Beta like me?
[In the next episode]
So what if you're a Beta?
Alpha, Omega, or Beta,
aren't we all human in the end?
I don't want to do it today.
Why are you so moody today?
I'm not moody.
Why did you send people
to Nakhun's warehouse?
There's been no damage this time.
I won't report it to the police.
I'll handle this myself.
What exactly happened?
My brother was shot yesterday.
What did you say?
♪ I linger in those beautiful memories ♪
♪ I used to think we were destined ♪
♪ But I also know ♪
♪ that reality isn't like that ♪
♪ I tried so hard to keep you
from leaving ♪
♪ But this broken love
is already shattered ♪
♪ Because I always believed
you would stay ♪
♪ I would give up everything for you ♪
♪ We should have had
the most beautiful future ♪
♪ But there's no result anymore ♪
♪ Only tears are left ♪
♪ Only memories remain ♪
♪ How many more times do I have to hurt
to understand ♪
♪ How much longer do I have to cry ♪
♪ Before my heart tells me
it's time to let go ♪
♪ If one day I leave ♪
♪ You probably wouldn't feel a thing ♪
♪ Like I never existed ♪
♪ I must admit, it really hurts ♪
♪ I must admit, I really miss you ♪
♪ If there were a little love left ♪
♪ You wouldn't have chosen to leave ♪
♪ But I don't know what's the point
of holding on ♪
♪ My words and heart are always at odds ♪
♪ My heart won't listen
no matter how much it hurts ♪
♪ I must admit, I really miss you ♪
♪ I understand it all,
but I never accepted it ♪
♪ We should have had
the most beautiful future ♪
♪ But there's no result anymore ♪
♪ Only tears are left ♪
♪ Only memories remain ♪
♪ How many more times do I have to hurt
to understand ♪
♪ How much longer do I have to cry ♪
♪ Before my heart tells me
it's time to let go ♪
♪ If one day I leave ♪
♪ You probably wouldn't feel a thing ♪
♪ Like I never existed ♪
♪ I linger in those beautiful memories ♪
♪ I used to think we were destined ♪
♪ I must admit ♪
♪ It really hurts♪
♪ I really miss you. If one day I... ♪
♪ left, ♪
♪ You probably wouldn't feel a thing ♪
♪ Like I never existed ♪