[Episode 15]
Put this on for me.
My shoulder hurts.
Miao Jing.
You hate me.
You resent me.
Punish me all you want. I can take it.
Just don't hurt yourself.
Yi.
Do we book the renovation costs this month
or next month?
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I'm really fine.
Wait here.
You're burning up. Give it to me.
I'm fine. Some medicine will do.
Lie down. I'll get you medicine.
You're sick or hurt every other day.
You said you got caught in the rain.
Was it like something on television?
Was it because of Miao Jing again?
Heavy rain, and she chased you from behind?
"Chen Yi, this is all your fault.
It's all your fault, Chen Yi."
Isn't that funny?
Wait, was that true?
She made you stand in the rain downstairs?
I went with her
to the old factory to look for something.
What did you two lose that was worth
going out in that kind of rain?
Why didn't you call me and Yong?
What really happened?
It's been so long.
If she wanted revenge,
she would've done it long ago.
You must've done something else
to upset her.
What was it?
Tu Li. It's Tu Li.
Miao Jing may not have been that angry.
But right after she came back,
she found out about you and Tu Li.
Of course she'd be jealous.
That's love turning into hate.
Thank you.
You suddenly invited me to dinner.
This can't just be about old times, right?
Miao Jing.
A while ago, I heard a monk give a lecture.
It was really interesting.
He said everyone has attachments in life.
But only when you let go of prejudice,
attachments, and regrets,
can the lotus in your heart bloom.
Yes.
So... if he's the right person,
you don't need to fight so hard to keep him.
Exactly.
Look at me. I only met Li Qiao
after I broke up with my ex.
Look at us now. We're happy.
Sometimes you have to let go
before things can turn around.
Then I wish you happiness.
Thank you.
This tastes pretty good.
Yes. It's an old local deli.
Don't you just want a happy future?
To be honest, Miao Jing,
everyone falls for someone new.
But if you stay stuck,
you'll be the only one getting hurt.
Yi finally came back to live a quiet life.
He finally came back.
How many years was he sentenced to?
Was he locked up in Teng City?
No. Who told you he went to jail?
He was overseas.
He was doing business overseas?
That's good too.
Hasn't foreign trade been profitable
these past two years?
Why come back to open a billiards hall?
I don't really know the details.
I came here today just to...
Miao Jing, don't you get it?
Yi already has a girlfriend.
- I'm treating you, and you brought a friend?
- Miao Jing.
Bo.
Li.
I'm done eating. Let's go.
- Let's go.
- Thank you.
- Bye.
I know he has a girlfriend.
Yi. Guess what I just saw?
Miao Jing and Tu Li.
They were holding hands and shopping together.
Jing. Sorry about last time.
Just call me Miao Jing.
Okay.
I'm paying today. Anything you like,
just say the word. Don't be shy.
How about this one?
You have such a great figure.
It'll look great on you.
Try on anything you like too.
We'll make Chen Yi reimburse us.
No need.
Let's go.
When you two go shopping,
doesn't he usually pay?
Usually?
My shop is busy,
so I don't have much free time.
That's how it gets after a while.
How about this one?
It looks a lot like the one you're wearing.
Forget it. This one's not great either.
I think it's pretty.
And it's a much better deal than mine.
You know how to pick shops.
Really?
When you earn your own money,
you spend it wisely.
Excuse me, do you have this in other sizes?
- I'd like to try it on.
- Yes. This way.
Have you been waiting long?
Their sweet soup is really good.
Here, I'll open it for you.
I'm sorry.
- I have tissues. Let me wipe it for you.
- It's okay.
- I'm really sorry.
- It's okay. It's fine.
Xin, want some lemon tea?
No, thanks.
Isn't that Li?
Li?
Oh no, Yi's new girl came after Li.
Look.
My boyfriend sent me this.
This is bad.
What about our shop's business now?
Yi won't abandon Li, will he?
I'll go take out the trash.
- What should we do?
- This won't do.
Let's confront her. Go.
Hello?
Where are you?
I'm at the shop.
So it's you.
Who are you to make Li grovel to you?
Don't you know Li has people around here?
Xin.
Yi.
Why aren't you watching the shop right now?
What are you doing here?
We were buying lunch nearby.
Miao Jing, sorry, it was all a mix-up.
Don't hold it against them.
Li, she walked all over you.
We're just venting for you.
She's Chen Yi's sister.
Sister?
Why didn't you say that earlier?
I didn't get the chance.
Li, this is on me.
What do you want to drink? I'll get it.
Is everything fine at the shop?
What are you thinking all day?
Go back.
We'll get going then.
Come by the shop sometime. I'll do your nails.
Didn't you say you were at the shop?
Get in first.
Yi, what are you doing here?
Why are you two together today?
I asked her out.
I thought I was rude last time,
so I wanted to apologize to Miao Jing.
I didn't expect a bigger mix-up.
Are you not feeling well?
Do you want to go to the hospital?
I caught a chill.
Don't forget to take your medicine.
Tu Li, you used to study dance?
That was a long time ago.
Why didn't you keep going?
I wasn't cut out for that life.
You have a dancer's build.
You're well suited for dance.
I'll drop Miao Jing off first.
Then I'll take you.
What kind of company puts us
in a place like this?
There's not even a decent office.
And the air conditioner is leaking.
Stop talking and get to work.
I need to talk to Tu Li.
You head back first.
What's wrong, Yi?
I really didn't mean it today.
I wanted to buy Miao Jing some clothes
to apologize.
Do I need to make myself clearer?
Tu Li, "girlfriend" is just a label.
It's just an arrangement.
We agreed not to interfere
in each other's lives.
If you don't want to go along anymore,
I don't care.
I don't mean that.
Then what about my shop, Yi?
You know you're not into me.
You just need my help once in a while.
Don't bother Miao Jing again.
What took you so long?
You haven't changed at all.
Tu Li won't come looking for you again.
Don't go looking for her either.
Why are you so against me seeing Tu Li?
I just don't want her bothering you.
So considerate. Have you fallen for me now?
[Haoting No. One]
When will the representatives
from Hai City arrive?
Probably next week.
I've arranged things with finance.
If they don't cooperate, then...
What century are we in?
You're still talking about killing?
Can you act more maturely?
Yes.
Once the audit team arrives,
what happens to Mr. Liu's business?
Whether this succeeds or not
depends on that big shot in Country Jin.
I didn't expect Chen Yi to become the key.
Take good care of the audit team.
Most importantly,
nothing can go wrong with Hongshen.
Okay.
[Diagonal Billiards Club]
In this game, there are fifteen red balls.
Where is the shot line?
It's here, right? Let's start with two groups.
- Okay, let me...
- Could you tell me about this course?
Have some water first.
- Okay. Thank you.
- Take the water.
For the other sets of balls,
players control the cue ball's power.
See? That's a lower-middle hit.
The lower-middle hit is against the rail now.
For beginners, we can start
with basic billiards training.
They've all won championships here.
If anything comes up on your end,
call me anytime.
Three long-term classes nailed in one morning.
That's amazing. A top salesperson.
Look how well the kids are learning.
Mr. Zhuang, come check their progress
when you have time.
Sure.
Everything was rearranged the way you wanted.
Look at the desks. We never had those before.
What spell did Miao Jing cast on you?
You weren't this picky when I used this room.
Once it's fully set up,
let her come see it first.
You really do worry about everything.
Wait. Are you sure she knows about this?
Don't act first and tell her later again.
I gave up this room. It better be worth it.
Your room? It was the finance office.
If you need to sleep, go sleep at home.
Yi. Someone came to return a cue.
- Who?
- I don't know him.
He just drove off.
I'll get back to work.
Wasn't that Zhang Bin's car?
Did you go play pool with Zhang Bin?
[Two days ago]
Mr. Liu, let me toast you.
You play really well.
I heard you love pool,
so Mr. Zhang invited Chen Yi to spar with you.
Cheers.
Sit down and talk.
Tao Jiang was right.
You're good, but...
your reputation in Country Jin is bigger
than your game at the table.
I was just getting by.
You're being too modest.
After all your years in Country Jin,
you're far more capable than us.
Mr. Liu, now you're being modest.
Chen Yi, Mr. Liu has a sharp eye.
No need to turn him down.
No deal is too hard with you at the helm.
Mr. Liu, now that Yi is back,
our road will only get broader.
I hope we work well together.
Mr. Liu.
Money is no problem. What about the risk?
We share the risk.
With Yi here, you can rest easy.
Good. Let's drink this.
From now on, we're in the same boat.
- Cheers.
Yi.
[Miao Jing]
Sorry. Family call.
That's Owen for you. What a temper.
But he's got the skill to back it up.
Let's keep drinking.
- Come on.
- Cheers.
The number you dialed is on another call.
Please try again later.
Sorry.
Hello, Yong. What's up?
- I think I saw Jing at Haoyun Freight Station.
- What?
[Haoyun Logistics]
Let's see what kind of show
Mr. Tao is putting on this time.
I'm looking forward to it.
[Ding Lei, Lead Auditor]
Ding Lei, audit representative
from Mingtong and Associates.
Tao Jiang from Haoyun Logistics.
As a third-party firm,
we've been assigned to audit your company.
I hope you'll make things easy for us.
I understand.
After all, we all want the company
to go public.
The sooner the report is done,
the sooner we settle up.
But your firm came too suddenly.
We didn't have time to prepare.
Office space is tight right now.
I'm afraid we can't arrange an audit room
that meets your needs.
How about this?
You all came from so far away.
Why don't I host you here for two days first?
Mr. Tao, audit work follows a fixed process.
Why so rigid?
Consider it a taste of local culture.
If you disrupt the plan like this,
our work will be hard to carry out.
And we can't answer to the client in Lingang.
Hey.
Didn't we email them the audit process
two weeks ago?
Could you find a delivery for me?
All right. What's your name?
Then we'll all draw lots.
I have a friend who works at your company.
He said Haoyun doesn't do commercial logistics.
Don't listen to his nonsense.
How much can individual parcels make?
Our commissions come from commercial logistics.
I don't know what got into our company.
We've had tons of those shipments lately.
We're swamped.
Weren't you looking for a delivery?
Never mind.
Miao Jing.
What are you doing here?
Starting work. Didn't you want me to get a job?
Fine.
As long as you found a job.
Don't ignore my calls again.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Why are you so hot?
Come on.
You can't just get into anyone's car.
This is the company's car.
Let's go.
Don't take me to the hospital.
Okay. Home first.
Wake up.
We're home. Let's go home.
Where's the thermometer?
In my bedroom drawer.
My fever's gone. I'll be fine after some sleep.
You're burning up and still denying it?
Hold it under your arm.
If I hadn't made you stand in the rain,
you wouldn't have such a high fever.
I'm sorry.
How much longer?
Three minutes.
I really feel like my fever's gone.
We're having congee tonight.
What kind do you want?
Anything.
Why the long face?
You found a job.
Is the pay good?
Weekends off and full benefits.
Five thousand a month.
It's good you didn't go to the pool hall.
What do you mean?
You think I look down on the pool hall?
A top Hai City graduate coming back
to handle the finances at a small pool hall...
But that was my plan for the future.
Stay in Teng City and run a pool hall with you.
We can live a simple but happy life.
I remember you said
that we'd be together forever.
What if a broken mirror can't be whole again?
At least it's still beautiful.
Here is all the financial data
for the companies they asked for.
Okay, manager. Do we have any other...
Check if they need these contracts.
Once you have everything ready...
You go first.
Sorry I'm late, Mr. Tao.
Deputy team leader, Miao Jing.
Thank you. I was just talking with Mr. Ding.
You only just arrived.
You started work before you even rested.
We haven't been very good hosts.
I understand the general situation now.
You're considering our needs,
but the client in Lingang is pushing hard.
If too much piles up and delays us,
we may make mistakes.
Of course, if the office setup is adequate,
we can move faster too.
She's right.
We do urgently need a fixed office space.
I hope you'll arrange it soon, Mr. Tao.
If you can't do it today, that's fine.
We can keep working at a nearby cafe.
We can't have guests working outside.
That wouldn't look proper.
Don't worry. We'll clear a place today.
Thank you, Mr. Tao.
That's our Jing.
She solved it with just a few words.
Just leave it to Miao Jing.
What's this place?
Please take my things home for me.
I still need to go to the company.
What kind of company is this?
They don't even have a fixed office.
Where are you moving now?
The new office wasn't ready.
So we have to make do here.
Doesn't sound like a proper company.
Are you worried about me?
I just think it's unreliable.
The pool hall is good too.
At least I can give you an office.
Let's go.
Don't forget to buckle up,
or I'll lose license points and get fined.
Where are we going? This isn't the way home.
We need to buy something first.
Come back if you like them.
Welcome. Are you looking
for men's or women's styles?
It's for her. Get her a comfortable pair.
Something good for commuting.
So thoughtful.
This pair has high rebound cushioning.
The arch follows an ergonomic curve,
and they're light and comfortable.
Best of all, they match your boyfriend's.
They're designed as a couple's set.
They're very popular here.
What size do you wear?
37.
Size 37.