[Episode 16]
Here, miss. Try these in size 37.
Here.
How do they feel?
What do you think?
Take them off. They don't fit.
I think they look pretty good.
They're too cheap. They don't suit you.
Aren't you wearing the same pair?
Are you afraid people will get the wrong idea?
They just don't fit, that's all.
Miss, try this pair.
This pair is lambskin,
so the style feels a little younger.
They're comfortable enough for the office.
Lambskin for work? Isn't that too expensive?
They're meant to be worn. It's fine.
Here. Try them on.
This style sells really well here.
Do they feel a little tight?
Would you like a bigger size?
No, this is fine.
I know whether these shoes fit me.
We'll take this pair.
Please wrap up the old ones.
Sure.
This way, please.
This pair is 2,000 yuan.
- Will that be card or cash?
- Card.
Okay.
What's wrong?
It's raining.
The new shoes will get ruined in the rain.
If they get ruined, I'll buy another pair.
I bought them for you to wear.
No way. This is a gift from you.
Come here.
Lower.
Carry me on your back.
It's only a few steps anyway.
I'll buy you another pair of slippers.
Forget it. No need.
Get on.
Chen Yi.
Your bones are digging into me.
If you're uncomfortable, get down.
Then don't let your heart beat so fast.
It's making me uncomfortable.
Everyone, send me your photos later.
I'll print them all.
Jing.
This pink is pretty cute.
Of course. Real men wear this color.
Yu.
Di's stuff is here.
[C Y]
Manager Ding.
Hello.
How's it coming along?
I heard Haoyun sidelined your team
as soon as you got there.
Are you here to gloat?
That's not what I meant.
I just came to check on my ace.
And to ask how I can help.
It hasn't been going smoothly.
We still don't have all the basic records
or financial statements.
So I went to the freight station
to see if anything looked suspicious.
What happened?
Stay out of it for now. I'll keep an eye on it.
Business as usual.
Okay.
[Zhang Bin]
[Storm Garden]
Don't miss a thing regarding the fleet.
Lingang isn't about just one or two shipments.
Put your best people on these routes.
Understood, Mr. Zhang.
I handpicked everyone in the fleet.
Good.
Chen Yi was ruthless out there
a few years back.
He can't just walk away from that life.
He's way too naive.
Still, I should thank Zhai Feng Mao
for sharpening him into such a fine blade
and leaving him by my side.
Mr. Zhai has a keen eye,
but we admire you more
for how you control the big picture.
Chen Yi is here.
Mr. Zhang.
You're here.
I've been thinking.
I was out of line the other day,
calling you over in such a rush.
I didn't ask you here today for anything else.
Just to have dinner together.
Let me make it up to you.
No need to put it that way.
It's a good day for a walk. Walk with me.
Let's go.
This used to be a swimming pool, right?
No one's used it in ages.
They filled it in and landscaped it.
Isn't this way much better?
Yi.
Don't turn me down.
I don't make empty moves.
If you change your mind,
Haoyun always welcomes you.
Plenty of people want your favor, Mr. Zhang.
Why me?
Do you know why it's called "Storm Garden"?
"See that little boat,
rising and falling in the storm."
Interesting.
Looks like I was right about you.
Sharp instincts, bold, but careful.
As for Haoyun...
Right now, we're a ship in a storm.
It doesn't just need a good helmsman.
It needs a good sailor like you
to keep her steady and go the distance.
Mr. Zhang, I don't have big ambitions.
I can't help you.
I remember when, for money and family,
you were willing to serve Kuangxia.
Now Haoyun is finally on track.
It's doing legitimate business.
Now you're making excuses.
What is that supposed to mean?
Back then, I had no way out.
Pick the right time and the right person.
Didn't Zhai Feng Mao ever teach you that?
I told you, I value real talent.
Haoyun and I are here for you.
Will you stay or walk away?
Just give me an answer.
[Storm Garden]
[Hai City]
Come in.
Mr. Cen, these two files need your review.
And this letter came in from the earlier case.
It needs your signature.
Please organize all the other documents
that I need to review in person.
- I'll handle them all at once.
- Alright. I'll bring them over shortly.
Also, cancel tonight's business dinner.
Let the team know
we'll need to work late tonight.
Coffee's on me.
One more thing.
Change my flight to Teng City to next week.
Okay.
[Business Trip to Teng City on 24th]
[Teng City]
Miao, it's late. I can drive you home.
No need. Someone's picking me up.
Okay.
Xiao Yu, Ma Yang, I'm heading out.
- Bye.
- Bye, safe travel.
- Do you want me to drive you home?
- No, it's fine.
All right.
- See you next time.
- Bye!
Okay.
What exactly does your company do?
One minute it's a cafe meeting,
the next it's a team dinner.
Does your boss have that much free time?
A partner company invited us out.
We couldn't exactly say no.
- Take care.
- Are those guys all your coworkers?
Yeah. Some are from my company,
some from partner companies.
That guy next to me was my college junior.
I knew it. He had that slick-talker look.
He doesn't look reliable.
You can read faces now?
What about the older guy next to him?
A Teng City local.
A senior reviewer on our team.
He's only in his early thirties.
He does have a lot of experience.
But he's a little old.
Three years is a generation gap.
There are other options.
There are alumni from Hai City
and guys with houses and cars in Teng City.
We've got those, too.
Were you there to find a husband?
You know a lot about their backgrounds.
I only mentioned a coworker.
Why are you so worked up?
Are you trying to pick out your brother-in-law?
Or is it that you're afraid someone
will steal me away?
I was just asking.
Is that right? I thought you were jealous.
I don't get jealous.
Get in.
[Tu Li]
Come take a look.
[Li's Nails, Grand Opening]
It's our new shop's opening event.
Good! You should treat me to a manicure.
Come by anytime this week.
We're running a special.
You two look around. I'll greet the others.
- How is it?
- It's great.
Did you have a drink? Here, have some.
Okay.
We're running a special this week.
Come by anytime.
See any style you like? Come by anytime.
How have you been? I haven't seen you in ages.
- It's almost time.
- Okay.
Take your time.
This is...
Chen Yi, we're about to cut the ribbon.
Want to come with me?
It's your shop. Why would I get involved?
Don't say that. I got to move upstairs
because of you, didn't I?
Besides, I want you to cut the ribbon with me.
Yesterday, you only asked me to come by.
You never said I'd have to play along
with all this nonsense.
Miao Jing.
Miao Jing is here. Let's go. Come join the fun.
Miao Jing,
why didn't you come with your brother?
We weren't coming from the same place.
Happy opening!
- Thank you.
- You're here.
Why did you bring a gift?
Li, look how much Yi cares about you.
I thought Yi wasn't coming.
He talks tough, but he's a softie.
Don't you still have a ribbon to cut?
There are a lot of people. Go on.
I'll get ready, Li.
Li's Nails is now open.
To thank our regulars and new customers,
we're offering discounts this week.
Happy grand opening. May the cash roll in.
Why are you looking at me?
I'm not the one opening a shop.
I'm looking at the flowers.
I'll do your nails before you head back.
Sure. Nude nails, then.
I haven't had that in ages.
Okay. Go in and take a look.
We have plenty of color samples.
This is my new place.
You never even came to my old one.
Come here.
- Xin, come help me with Miao Jing.
- Li.
- I got it.
- I'll be right back.
Let's keep some distance in public.
What happened?
Didn't we agree you'd pretend
to be my boyfriend and have my back?
I can help keep admirers away, too.
Your new shop is up and running now.
We don't have to pretend anymore.
I think things are fine as they are.
My new shop just opened.
There's still so much to sort out.
Aren't we having dinner
with property management next month?
Miao Jing's still waiting for her manicure.
I'll head back.
Next week then.
I'll go with you next week
to meet them for dinner.
- Li.
- Sorry for the poor hospitality.
If you need anything, ask Xin.
Sure. Go on, get back to work.
Li.
I'll take over here. Go look after Ms. Zhang.
Okay.
Your brother doesn't like crowds, so he left.
What would you like?
You have such nice, full nail beds.
Do you get your nails done often?
Not often.
Has Chen Yi been acting strange lately?
Like what?
Like, has he been close to any girls at work?
I don't mean anything. Just asking.
Do I count?
Of course you don't.
Then no.
Forget it. Let's drop it.
What color do you want today?
This jelly shade is the hottest this year.
See anything you like?
Let's keep it simple.
This one is more nude.
It'll look very subtle when it's done.
- That works.
- Okay.
Hello. Have Ma Yang book a meeting room first
and get the data roughly copied over.
I'll be there soon.
Okay. I'll send it to you.
Working overtime again?
Didn't you say you had weekends off?
Headquarters called
a last-minute remote meeting.
You never see it coming.
You've never left on time at this company.
But I'm paid to do a job.
I'm running late. Wash my clothes for me.
Eat before you go.
[Jing, Haoyun Logistics]
So careless.
Chen Yi, what are you doing?
Doing laundry.
Then why are you spacing out?
If you have something to say, say it.
You're acting weird.
Why didn't you say you work at Haoyun?
What? What's wrong with Haoyun?
They make you work late every day.
That's reason enough.
What decent company does that?
At least it's a job I found myself.
Did Haoyun put a spell on you?
You've only been there a few days.
Why so loyal already?
Isn't that just how work is?
You can't just switch jobs on a whim.
Or are you going to pull strings
and parachute me into a job?
I hate privilege more than anything.
Connections only matter if they want you.
You were the one who turned down Jianye.
If you had no skills, who would hire you?
Then stop worrying about me.
When I really can't take it anymore,
I'll come work for you at the pool hall.
I'm full. I'm leaving.
[Zhang Bin]
[Call Mobile]
If you have any questions after you get back,
remember to contact me.
Please check this file again.
I've already reviewed it.
- Is that so?
- There shouldn't be any issues.
Then I'll move it forward.
You bought this brand of tea again?
After all these years,
you haven't changed your taste.
You don't get it. It's cheap, tasty,
and keeps you awake. Right, Captain?
Enough. Stop messing around.
Don't drink it anymore.
[Teng City Confucian Temple Floral Troupe]
You made it yourself, right?
This is handwoven. Take a look.
Let's go give thanks.
Let's watch the show first.
Let's stay a little while longer.
The show's almost over.
The parents handle all this stuff.
You can't eat that.
Right.
[Every Prayer Answered, Studies Blessed]
[May Your Name Top the List, Studies Blessed]
Her name topped the list as I wished.
I'm here to give thanks.
Let's go.
Bravo!
Excellent!
This opera only runs until Sunday.
Come see it with me.
Okay.
Great.
Let's go. Drive me to the office.
You still have to go on a weekend night?
Work's been busy lately.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
That's all your food. Enjoy.
Thanks.
Yi, go ahead. What did you need me for?
I do need to ask you a favor.
I heard Haoyun is hiring lately.
Hiring?
You're interested in that too, Yi?
Or have you already said yes to Mr. Zhang?
Are you joining Haoyun?
Do you know which department is hiring?
A friend of mine runs meal orders nearby.
He wants to find a way to get in touch
and ask around.
Well, I might not be able to help with this.
Haoyun has had a lot of new people lately.
But we didn't hire them.
They're not from Haoyun?
Right.
They were recruited by the Lingang Group.
Accountants or something, I think.
Yi, you know that I'm just the driver.
I forget a lot of things
as soon as I hear them.
I know what I'm supposed to know.
And it's better not to know
what I'm not supposed to know.
Then I'll have him try another way.
[Mr. Zhang]
Yi, work just came in. I have to go.
Go ahead.
Thanks for the meal.
Contract? Accountant?
Delivery's here.
Coming.
Everything's here.
Have your boss settle the bill.
One moment.
Mister.
I think this item doesn't match the picture.
Don't start making things up.
These are all original imports from Japan.
What do you mean?
It doesn't match what we ordered.
They're basically the same. They still work.
No. We paid for this.
You can't just say it's close enough.
Once goods are opened, no returns.
What do you mean?
Stop right there!
- Li.
- What's wrong?
This doesn't match the photo.
Are you blind? You're trying to scam me now?
Where does the contract say
that opened items can't be returned?
Don't try that crap with me today.
If it's not in the contract,
I'm not accepting it.
Refund me. I don't want any of this.
Take it back where it came from.
Can you people be reasonable?
I delivered my goods to you.
You can't just decide you don't want them.
You think I'm giving you a refund?
What do you think you're doing?
You think we're pushovers?
Give me back my deposit, or I'll expose you
for passing off junk as quality goods.
I'm warning you, my boyfriend...
My boyfriend's sister is a college student
from Hai City.
No student can help you.
You think it's refundable?
Here. Take a look.
Look closely. It says non-refundable,
not refundable.
[Deposits are non-refundable]
Even in the highest court, it wouldn't help.
So that's the trap.
- You did this on purpose, didn't you?
- You have only yourself to blame.
You said the contract was what mattered.
That's exactly what the contract says.
Learn your lesson next time.
Where do you think you're going? Stop.
Where are you going?
You want to hit him?
We barely make anything
sticking rhinestones on things.
This jerk took it all.
Stay out of it, kid.
[Haoyun Logistics]
- I have to take a taxi to work every day.
- Is there any good restaurant around here?
- Let's carpool.
- No.
I still haven't found anything good here.
I haven't been able to order anything either.
Jing, does that person know you?
I've been waiting for you forever.
Did Tu Li send you to find me?
No. I came here on a hunch
after hearing you worked at Haoyun.
Take a look at this. Please don't tell her.
Whose contract is this?
They're playing word games.
They won't refund you now, right?
How did you know?
It's a standard shady contract,
totally one-sided.
Don't worry.
I'll fix this for you within three days.
Really?
Thank you so much.
Let's go.
Who was that?
A friend.
I told you not to bother Yi
over something so small.
I was just trying to scare the guy.
Then you went and bothered Miao Jing?
- I know, but she's so smart.
- I said I wouldn't bother her.
And she was willing to help.
Did you even think about
whether she was free to help you?
She just returned to Teng City
and finally found a job.
What if that supplier shows up at her company?
Hello.
This is Tu Li.
The cafe on the corner, right?
Okay. I'll get ready and head over.
Who was that?
The beauty device seller.
Why is he coming to you now?
I don't know. He didn't say anything.
[Chen Yi]
Forget it. It doesn't matter.
Watch the shop for me.
- I'm going out.
- Okay, Li.
Li, maybe you shouldn't go.
I have a bad feeling about this.
You think I don't have a bad feeling?
But this never had anything to do
with Miao Jing.
If anything happens to her,
I'll make it right no matter what.
Okay. Go ahead.
This really wasn't my fault.
Tu Li.
This way.
Then pay up and apologize as we agreed.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have passed off shoddy goods.
Nor should I have used fraudulent clauses
in the contract.
All right. Can you drop the lawsuit now?
Thank you, Miao Jing.
He probably won't try anything again,
but you should still count it.
Just a little something. Take it.
Your new shop just opened. You need the money.
It was no big deal. Don't worry about it.
Then let me buy you dinner sometime.
Really, no need.
Educated people really are sharp.
I wouldn't even know where the courthouse is.
Just get off the Route 14 bus.
You can sit in on trials, too.
It's pretty interesting.
I was just saying that. I wouldn't dare go.
Why not?
I barely went to school.
They wouldn't even let me into a courthouse.
All they check is your identification.
None of that matters.
Really?
I didn't even know that.
Even if I went, I wouldn't understand it.
I wish I'd been able to stay in school.
I was actually just like you.
How is that possible?
I almost couldn't go to college back then.
Miao Jing, please don't tell Yi
I bothered you again.
When you're free, let's have dinner together.
Just us, without Yi.
Mister.
If there's something you want to do, do it.
Don't overthink it.
[Wei Ming Zhen: Busy with school?
Why aren't you replying?]
[Busy with school? Why aren't you replying?]
[Are you settling into college life?
Be sure to get along with your classmates.]
[Are you still mad at me?]
[Why not come home for winter break?
Do you want to come stay with me?]
- Hello?
- Hello, Jing.
What's wrong? You sound a little down.
I'm fine. Is Ding Lei making another move?
Yes. Ding Lei wants the team
to turn in the workpapers now.
He's forcing everyone to sign.
Hold them off however you can until I get back.
Okay.
How many times do I need to spell it out?
If I say the procedure is fine, it's fine.
Besides, I've reviewed the workpapers.
What issue could you have?
The data hasn't been reviewed.
How can you be sure it's accurate?
Xiao Yu, it's just a signature.
Why make this so ugly?
Ding, you're the one making this ugly.
The confirmation procedures, major inspections,
and cutoff tests haven't even been done.
How can you vouch
for the quality of these workpapers?
As deputy team leader, I can't sign either.
You know what this is really about.
It's just to get through the formalities later.
The client is pushing for the report.
If the listing is delayed, that's serious.
The more they push, the less we can rush.
If an accounting firm can't even guarantee
the quality of its workpapers,
what credibility does it have?
Haoyun has tax issues.
Its cash flows are unclear.
Those are all ticking time bombs.
How can you turn a blind eye to that?
Listen, if you make a claim, you need evidence.
Haoyun doesn't even do commercial logistics?
Don't listen to his nonsense.
What do walk-in parcels even pay?
We get commission. It's all commercial freight.
Lately, our boss must have lost his mind.
We've had tons of these packages lately.
We can't keep up.
This is the evidence I found
during my visit to Haoyun's freight station.
Haoyun's offering filing says
its clients are mostly individuals.
But in fact, it mainly handles bulk freight
for corporate clients.
Recently, to cover up that listing lie,
they started creating these odd small batches.
Ding, what do the workpapers say about this?
Are you talking to me?
I thought you were the team leader.
The way you acted just now made it feel like
if I said no, I'd be off the project.
I was only following the procedure.
If you really followed the procedure,
you wouldn't be making trouble like this.
Miao Jing, let me remind you.
Don't think you can get arrogant
just because you have backing.
You're the deputy.
To put it nicely, a senior auditor.
But I'm the project manager
for Haoyun Logistics' initial public offering.
Mr. Ding.