[alarm beeps]
[theme music playing]
THIS IS A WORK OF FICTION
CHILD ACTORS WERE FILMED SAFELY
WITH SUPERVISION
[sibling] How was your last relationship?
[chuckles] It was a failure.
Still though,
I learned a few things from it.
YOON DA-RA
WEB NOVEL WRITER
What kind of things did you learn?
"Don't fool yourself into thinking that
love can change a person."
So, how come you even considered
getting married?
I fooled myself into thinking
that marriage would
solve all our problems.
That he would completely
become "my person."
And I'd be able to escape
from my loneliness.
What type of person
would you like to date next?
Someone more grounded.
And that I don't have to babysit.
[Da-ra] Would you say
you're the grounded type?
Yes.
By the way, why are you still standing?
I didn't get a chance to work out today.
Oh, I see.
You're not married, right?
Actually, I'm divorced.
Huh?
Then how do you think that experience
affected your next relationship?
I guess it left me with a fear of love.
Will you ever give love another try?
-[smacks lips]
-[sighs]
-I'm not sure.
[romantic music playing]
[Si-woo] I like you.
[Ji-yoon] I like you too.
In the beginning,
you're convinced everything will go well.
You picture only the good stuff
rather than the hardships.
I'm probably fooling myself again.
That's for sure.
But what can I do?
Starting all over again.
That's the magic of love.
EPISODE 7 HAVE A NEW SECRET,
STILL CLOCKING IN!
[panting]
[chuckles]
[inhales deeply, exhales sharply]
[phone alarm playing]
[groans]
ALARM
[sighs]
[phone chimes]
[Si-woo] Good morning.
[cheerful music playing]
MANAGER KANG SI-WOO
GOOD MORNING!
[chuckles]
A new relationship has begun.
Why does my skin feel so rough?
No, this won't do.
After all, today is a special day.
[sighs]
[scoffs]
Smooth as a baby's bottom. [chuckles]
[giggles]
I'm sorry
that you missed your morning run.
I did run.
But it's only 7:30 a.m.
I woke up at 5:00.
Wow. [chuckles]
What is all this for?
I got you some red ginseng
for your immune system,
and also, women's health supplements.
Set an alarm to take them every day.
[chuckles]
Thank you.
Because today is a day worth celebrating.
You should've left the flowers at home.
I'm going to put them on my desk
and look at them all day.
How should we go about it at work?
I think it's best we keep it a secret.
Why?
Well, if people find out about us,
they won't see us
as a boss and a subordinate anymore.
They may say,
"Are they here to work or date?"
Or they'll whisper, "Did they fight?"
Whether you compliment me or tell me off,
they'll always view it
with some prejudice.
I don't want to have to walk
on eggshells at work.
Once there's a secret,
we'll have to tell that many more lies.
Well, I'm a good liar.
I managed to hide my feelings for you
pretty well, didn't I?
Did you now?
[scoffs] Wait. Did it show?
Let's keep it a secret
as you want, Ji-yoon.
"Ji-yoon."
I really like it when you call me that.
Okay, then.
And would you call me the same way?
-[Ji-yoon] "Si-woo"?
-[record scratch plays]
I think I'll need
a little bit more time for that.
[chuckles]
[gasps] Oh.
You can drop me off right there.
Why? There's still a long way to go.
[sighs] Do you think you could be
a tad more discreet, Mr. Kang?
[chuckles]
[Ji-yoon] Here's how it goes at an office.
[upbeat music playing]
You'll be joining us
for lunch today, right?
Or should we make an excuse
to sneak off together?
I'm sorry.
I still have some work to finish.
You go ahead without me.
[sighs]
But I want to eat with you.
Here even messages like this
are sent with a straight face,
like it's just work.
Mr. Kang, let's go for lunch.
I'll be eating alone today.
But it's been so nice
having you eat with us.
Can you do it after lunch?
Let's not bother Mr. Kang
and let him stay.
Okay.
[Ji-yoon] So nothing's really changed
between us.
-Well, then we'll head out for lunch.
-[Si-woo] Okay.
[playful music playing]
[Ji-yoon] Well, maybe just a little.
[chuckles]
He doesn't wear a ring…
so I don't think he's married.
[gasps] A girlfriend?
Who?
Well, Mr. Kang.
[No-ah scoffs]
He's practically at the office
like built-in furniture.
Do you know anything, Ms. Cha?
Not really.
I don't pay
much attention to him, so…
[sighs] Lie number one.
Of course. [smacks lips]
We have no romantic energy left,
so how could we know?
Mmm. [chuckles]
Hmm? Come on.
Our dear Ms. Cha is
dressed up so nicely today. Hmm?
She even came in with flowers.
What was with that?
A special occasion today?
No.
I just thought I'd air it out
before it grew mold.
And the flowers were
a spur-of-the-moment, uh, purchase.
[Na-ri] Hmm.
-You bought flowers for yourself?
-Hmm.
That's really kinda sad, you know? Huh?
Have some more meat.
Here.
You can have all of my tangsuyuk too.
[Ji-yoon] I did it again. I lied.
[Na-ri] You know
we're here for you, right?
We're back, sir.
[Ji-yoon] I wonder if he's eaten.
Mr. Kang, have you eaten already?
No worries. I'll eat after the meeting.
[Ji-yoon sighs]
He's going to pass out at this rate.
I know work's important and all,
but you shouldn't skip meals.
Here. A Dubai Chewy Cookie.
Have one, Mr. Kang.
[amusing music playing]
Thank you, but I don't eat sweet things.
Someone else can have it.
Oh, I love Dubai Chewy Cookies.
These are hard to get too.
-I'll have that, thanks you.
-Wait!
Do you know what I went through to get it?
You can't just take it.
-[chuckles]
-[huffs]
Let's start the meeting.
[Na-ri] So unfair.
In a month, we'll invite overseas buyers
and hold a Home-AI demonstration.
We'll do a demonstration in a month?
But nothing is prepared yet.
Unlike other products,
experience is key for Home-AI.
We'll need to do a demonstration
to identify any issues.
The schedule will be tight,
so let's prepare for it
like it's our final check before launch.
I guess that means
we'll be incredibly busy.
Even so, presenting the project
within a month is pushing it.
When does testing
for the living appliances finish?
Uh, everything except the washing machine
should be wrapping up soon. Yeah.
Can we get the brochures
made within a month?
Oh, brochures?
Yes, that's definitely doable.
And kitchen appliances?
Uh… I haven't even had a meeting
with them yet.
We have a long way to go.
Then all we need is for you to
pick up the pace, Ms. Cha.
As long as everyone here
does their part,
then I'll coordinate everything else.
-Sure.
As for you, Ms. Cha,
please see me in the showroom
after we finish this meeting.
Yes, sir.
[coworkers chattering, laughing]
A-A demo?
Yes.
Apparently,
they're inviting overseas buyers.
If President Han
delivers real results with that,
the Vice President
can forget about the next President spot.
And then our side
will be dead in the water.
We can't let that…
[tense music playing]
We-We can't let that happen.
How's the digging into that punk
coming along?
Oh, uh, I haven't--
Well, hurry up and find something.
And also, figure out a way
to sabotage the demo while you're at it.
Uh, b-but what if we sabotage the demo?
Wouldn't that take a toll
on the company too?
What? You think a massive company
like this will go under over one bad demo?
Once it fails, we'll hold Han U-jin
and Kang Si-woo responsible,
and take over the Home-AI project.
Oh!
And set up a meeting
with that guy we talked about, okay?
Yes, sir.
[sighs]
What did you want to see me for?
To give you more work, of course.
You've already assigned me an
excessive amount of work.
Is there more?
You seem to have a lot of complaints.
I can't say I don't.
I just wanted to deliver
a high-quality product
without having to race
against the clock this time.
What's the biggest issue
with the kitchen side of things?
The issue is Mr. Ko.
I asked for help many times,
but he won't respond.
Then I'll take care of that for you.
How's that?
By playing the President card.
That's why we're reporting
to her directly.
Wow. You wanted your work
to speak for itself.
You play politics too, huh?
Making things work isn't playing politics.
It's coordination.
In that case,
could I use the Mr. Kang card
sometimes too?
That, I can't allow.
Why not?
I tend to find it hard to draw the
professional-personal line around you.
[scoffs]
Will you be working late again today?
Probably.
[Ji-yoon] Hmm.
-[footsteps]
-[Jung-in pants]
I just heard a rumor.
-Oh, yeah? What rumor?
-Apparently, if you kiss in here,
your married life will be smooth sailing.
-[Jung-in] What are you talking about?
-Just give me one kiss.
-No, we can't. People will see us!
-No one's coming now. Just one.
[romantic music playing]
[gasps softly]
[gasps]
[softly] Those two?
I never would've guessed it.
-They'd say the same about us.
-[chuckles]
Your foot.
I'm sorry.
I could get used to this too.
As nice as this is,
we can't stay here forever.
Then what?
Take your time coming back.
So, what do you think?
You think we have a…
-Geez!
-[grunts]
[groans]
Jung-in! No, I mean, Ms. Choi.
[chuckles]
Guess no one's coming here for a while.
[in French] Excellent.
That's it for today.
See you next time. Thank you. Goodbye.
[class] Thank you, goodbye.
Everyone, come and pick up
your pop quizzes.
Oh! How sweet!
What's this?
[Jae-in] "On y go."
Where to?
Somewhere fun.
[gentle music playing]
[groans, sighs]
The other day
you told me you had many talents.
-Is this one of them?
-No, I'm not good at this.
That's why we're making a bet.
What kind of bet?
Well, if I win then
you go on a date with me.
Are you asking me out?
Does it sound like it?
Then I guess I'm good at that too.
And if I win, what?
That won't happen,
so just tell me what you want.
All right, let's do this then.
Sweet!
-[groans]
-[chuckles]
[clears throat]
All right, your turn.
All right, fine.
[intense music playing]
Show me what you've got.
[upbeat disco music playing]
-Ooh.
-[huffs]
-[chuckles]
-[sucks teeth]
[grunts]
[No-ah huffs]
So, do I just tell you what I want now?
Yeah.
I want you to be my tutor.
Huh?
I can manage reading and writing,
but the pronunciation's too hard.
Tutor me on the weekends.
I don't come cheap, you know.
I have a pretty high salary.
-[chuckles]
Okay, deal!
Deal!
[amusing music playing]
Since we're both busy this week.
HOW TO SABOTAGE DEMO?
[sighs]
[phone buzzes]
PRESIDENT HAN U-JIN
Yes, ma'am.
Yes.
No, no, not at all.
Yes, I understand.
Yes. I will take care of it right away.
Yes, yes. Yes. Thank you. Goodbye. yes.
Damn it.
Ms. Yoon No-ah.
Sir?
You may go and help with the task force.
Keep it within reason so it doesn't
interfere with your main tasks.
Do you understand?
Yes.
[tense music playing]
[sighs]
How dare he play the President card?
What the… [breathing heavily]
[muttering] Just who does he think he is?
[phone buzzes]
[Young-sam] Tell me,
why haven't you replied yet?
Do you want that promotion or what?
[smacks lips, inhales deeply]
[smacks lips, groans]
Damn.
Are you okay? Did something happen?
No, I'm just so far behind
on my loan payment.
[gasps] Oh, no.
[whispering] It's okay. It's okay.
You'll be fine.
[Kee-tae, whispering] Snap out of it.
The dishwasher, water dispenser,
and oven are taken care of.
-And the most important…
-Yeah.
…is the refrigerator.
Besides it being the hub for Home-AI,
I'd like to add other features to it.
Like what exactly?
A "food manager."
Basically, it tracks what ingredients
are in the fridge, lists them out,
and it can even suggest recipes you
can make with whatever you have in there.
Wow.
You never run out of things
you want to do, do you?
And you?
Do you have any ideas
since working on kitchen appliances?
There was but I gave up,
because they said it was a no-go.
What was it?
My sister once forgot a pot
on the induction cooktop,
and everything burned completely.
So then, I thought it would be great if
we could somehow
control the cooktop remotely.
But it's not allowed
under safety standards.
Hmm?
It's meant for safety,
but it didn't meet safety standards?
It doesn't make sense.
There were remotely controlled products
on the market before.
With the safety standards changing,
no one's allowed to develop it now.
[Ji-yoon] Hmm.
[gasps] No-ah,
see if you can crack this.
-What?
-Someone has to crack this
once and for all.
It’s basically a race
to see who lands on the moon first.
So, you want me to be Neil Armstrong?
Mmm.
[tender music playing]
Mr. Kang!
I haven't seen you all day.
Yeah, I was in a meeting.
Anyone see where Ms. Cha went?
Oh, yeah. Ms. Cha's in a meeting as well.
Yeah.
Oh, looks like she's done.
[Ji-yoon] It's Mr. Kang.
I just met with Planning Team 1.
Okay. Good work, Ms. Cha.
Did you have anything else to say?
Ah.
I think we can start discussing
the design now.
Should I set up a meeting
with the Design Team?
I'll take care of the design matters.
You just focus on the tasks
you already have.
Well, should I give the person in charge
a heads-up?
No need.
I will have a talk
with Ms. Choi Soo-jin myself.
Sure.
I'll go see the Development Team.
[playful music playing]
[chuckles]
All right, so a map view
pops up like this.
If you tap on the products
at each location,
you can see their current status
and control them.
Plus, it can identify family members
by voice
to provide personalized management.
Right.
It has all the features it needs
to be the Home-AI Hub.
That's right.
Uh, but regarding that food manager idea…
Yes?
Look.
So you're saying you want to put a camera
in the fridge
to manage the ingredients, right?
Yes, that's what I want.
But look at that.
What about the items in the back, or
the things stacked on top of each other?
Like I said, installing a camera
isn't going to work.
The inside of a refrigerator
is as unreadable as the human mind.
What should we do?
Is there no other way to achieve it?
Is there?
There's not.
But do we have to do this?
We're already adding
plenty of other features as it is.
Exactly. We can't do all of this
in a month.
But the whole point of a refrigerator
is storing and managing food.
I really want to pull this off
for this project.
I'd like to do that too.
We just don't have anyone
who has enough time for it.
It'll have to wait.
Then, what if I can find someone else?
From where?
Someone from the outside if I have to.
Go and find someone then.
Make sure you get a Gen AI expert.
GEN AI: GENERATIVE AI
Yes, sir.
[no audible dialogue]
[somber music playing]
[sighs]
They're just coworkers.
I can't be bothered
about stuff like that too.
Oh, Mr. Kang.
You know,
I barely got to see your face today,
and now you're leaving
without saying a word?
You seemed busy, so…
You seem completely fine, Ms. Ji-yoon.
Because I've been struggling all day.
Me too.
[tender music playing]
Looks like you'll go home alone today too.
Do you have a lot of work left?
Hmm. A little.
[sighs]
Seems like dating a workaholic
sure is hard.
Then how about a date this weekend?
Yes.
-Congrats, man.
-Hey, let's drink!
-Let's drink, come on.
-Cheers!
[coworkers grunt]
-Congrats on the promotion.
-Congrats.
Thank you. [chuckles]
Our resident associate Jeong-su
is finally making senior associate, huh?
My team lead
really looked out for me this time.
Didn't you guys go to the same college?
Guess the school ties
worked out for you. [chuckles]
It wasn't the school ties. It's thanks to
my dedication and hard work.
You know, I hate the heat,
but I still went with him to the sauna.
[chuckles]
[coworker] That's my point.
If you two hadn't gone to the same school,
do you think your team lead
would've taken you to the sauna?
You're right about that.
[chuckling]
Hey, hey, hey, you got healthier
and promoted thanks to that, yeah?
So, that just leaves you now, huh?
Oh, is that it? [chuckles]
Geez. [clears throat]
-Hey, it'll happen in no time, yeah?
-Yeah.
-Hey. Let's drink.
[Jeong-su chuckles]
Hey. So, did you guys hear about her?
-The one who was on maternity leave…
-[phone buzzes]
…and got promoted the second she returned.
-Kim Mi-yeong?
-Mi-yeong, yeah.
Yeah, she came back…
[Han-gyeol] Dad, when are you coming home?
Can you get me that bread with
the dinosaur stickers on your way back?
Hey, uh, let me make a phone call
real quick.
Oh, sure.
So then what about Mi-yeong?
I think she's got some connections.
[Young-sam] Tell me,
why haven't you replied yet?
Do you want that promotion or what?
[tense music playing]
[Kee-tae] What is it
that you need me to do?
[whimsical music playing]
So, Mr. Kang.
When did you start having feelings for me?
Hmm.
Maybe when you made me
play the bad guy
while you took care of people
like the sun,
or when you asked if I was lonely.
Or maybe it started long before that.
You know, at some point,
I caught myself looking at you
and smiling without even realizing it.
Then, I can assume
all those compliments you gave me
were because you really liked me, right?
Do I look like the type who would do that?
Uh, no.
And I'm actually glad you're not.
You're brave and responsible,
and you make everyone around feel at ease.
-You're someone I want to learn from.
-I am?
Except for the snacks.
[chuckles]
I had tteokbokki just last night.
[gasps, breathing shakily]
[sighs]
Do you know him?
Yes, that's my brother.
What the heck is he doing out?
He should be studying for his SAT retake.
Come on, come on.
[yelps]
[comical music playing]
Playing hide-and seek a lot I see.
[chuckles] I know, right?
Okay, now. This is it. Let's get out.
He looks so familiar.
Where have I seen him before?
Why did he smile at me though?
God, that was close.
-[sighs]
-[sucks teeth]
If he's taking the SAT,
he must be quite younger than you.
12 years younger.
He's the baby of the family.
Is there anything you need to buy here?
Well, can you help me pick out a toner?
Sure.
[Ga-eul, on radio] ♪ The important thing
Is where I'm standing ♪
♪ It's a relief that by my side is… ♪
[patron] Ga-eul is super popular now, huh?
This song's practically everywhere.
Yeah, he blew up after B.A. posted
about him on social media.
Ji-yoon, should we go somewhere else?
I don't see anything I like here.
Yes.
We could've just gone to a café.
Why come all the way here?
Language happens in real-life.
Immersion is important.
[quirky music playing]
[chuckles]
What's going on with you and Mr. Kang?
And on the weekend, hold on…
Why were you holding hands?
Well…
It just sort of happened.
-So you two are dating?
-[gasps] Quiet.
Wait a second, since when?
How did that happen?
[sighs] Don't tell me.
At the baseball game?
No, not then.
We even trash-talked him
for being a jerk together.
All that trash-talk
somehow got me to understand him.
Wow. Oh, geez.
I mean, you must really like him
to be risking a relationship like this.
Still, try to be more careful.
Look at the chaos
the baseball game photo caused.
Imagine what would happen
if word gets out.
Exactly. So forget you ever saw us.
[sighs]
Why are they making a big deal?
That's because I have a lot of flaws.
And anyone
can see that she's too good for me.
And what are your flaws, sir?
I like her more than she likes me.
Ah.
By the way,
who's that kid you came with?
'Cause he looks super young.
He's the French TA.
He's… [chuckles] …23 and in college.
What? College?
[sighs]
You and I are both taking the hard path,
aren't we?
-No. Not me.
-You're not?
Well, not yet.
Don't worry about No-ah, okay?
She agreed to keep it secret.
Okay.
What should we have for dinner?
Uh… let's find good places to eat nearby…
Let's just head back.
Sorry?
My stomach's a little upset,
so I don't really feel like eating out.
Oh.
Okay, then.
We can just have dinner separately.
Let's eat at my place instead.
Did I put you on the spot
with the abrupt invite?
[Ji-yoon] I've been waiting
for that actually.
Well…
a little.
I may have rushed things a bit.
[Ji-yoon] How adorably naive.
-Maybe another time…
-Oh, no!
It's not my first time there,
and you're not feeling well,
so I guess I have no other choice then.
Truth is, I'm making up an excuse
to be alone with you.
What?
[laughing]
[in French] I'd like to pay, please.
Will that be by card?
Yes.
In three installments, please.
Pardon?
Could you repeat that, please?
Yes, in three installments!
[in English] Can you speak English?
Hey! Keep doing that, and you're fired.
All right, all right. Repeat after me.
[in French]
In three installments, please.
[clicks tongue, inhales sharply]
The receipt, please.
Would you be my boyfriend?
-Huh?
-[in English] Come on, repeat after me.
[in French] Would you be my boyfriend?
Would you be my boyfriend?
Yes, I'd like that.
[in English] What did you say "yes" to?
I thought you said you were a good cook.
I said I liked cooking,
I didn't say I was good at it.
You're right.
You said that.
Okay so what you're making now is…
I'll make you
a shrimp, tomato, and zucchini pasta.
Sounds like there's gonna be a lot
of chopping to do.
So you should just sit back
and relax while I cook.
[chuckles]
If I sit back and relax,
we'll have this for breakfast.
[sighs]
Okay, so you can do things your own way.
And I'll do things my way.
-Sound good?
-Yes.
So why were you going back
to the States, huh?
Because at that time,
I had no reason to stay here.
What about your family?
I only see my father once a year
on mother's death anniversary.
Even at his age,
he still feels uncomfortable to be around.
Oh.
There was no one
I'd regret leaving here,
and the States are easier
for Three-No-Man to work in.
But then I stopped you from leaving.
Yes.
Ms. Ji-yoon, you're the only variable
that changes my plans.
[somber classical music playing]
I made…
I made you hide all day today.
I'm sorry.
That's because of me, not because of you.
I'm the reason that you had to hide,
so why are you the one apologizing?
Besides
that word carries more weight
the more sparingly you say it.
Please don't say that
when you're around me.
Especially at work.
That explains the "no sorry" part.
You got me.
[sighs]
Looks like I've uncovered
all of the Three-No-Man's secrets.
The moment you uncover
all of someone else's secrets…
You get eliminated.
Since you're too pretty to eliminate,
so I'll just have to make you forget.
[upbeat K-pop music playing]
[Ji-yoon] The smell of toothpaste.
You're such a sly fox, Mr. Kang.
Hmm. Look at Korea and America.
The main ingredients people use
are completely different in each country.
Don't you think the refrigerator
should be able to recognize all of that?
That would be amazing, right?
[can pops]
Are you drinking beer right now?
Pu-erh tea for you, and beer for me.
Cheers!
Go to sleep.
[yawns] I don't want to.
I'm not going to sleep.
-Sleep.
-I'm telling you, I'm not sleepy at all.
[Kee-tae] What is it
that you need me to do?
[Young-sam] Dig into Kang Si-woo
and find his weakness.
[Kee-tae] Mr. Kang!
-Have you eaten already?
-Yes.
It'd be nice to eat together,
but you're so busy
that you're always eating alone.
[chuckles] I don't really mind.
[stammers] We're family now, aren't we?
So part of being a family is sitting down
and sharing meals together…
Would you like some tea?
Why not? [chuckles]
No need.
Allow me to bring a cup to you.
Please, take a seat.
Oh, no.
I couldn't possibly do that. [chuckles]
I will shamelessly take a seat, then.
He won't let me get close to him.
So how am I supposed to dig anything up?
You're working hard.
Mr. Kang.
Looks like things aren't going so well.
No.
The Development Team
said it's going to be hard
to develop the food manager
with their current workforce.
So, I'm looking for a separate
Gen AI expert who can take it on.
A Gen AI expert, hmm.
Right, Lee Young-hun
would be perfect for it.
Mr. Lee Young-hun,
who's currently on leave?
Yes.
Nobody else can match him in that field.
He's returning soon,
so you should look into it.
Great.
Then I will reach out to him today.
You do this whenever you can.
Remind me who said we should be careful?
Cut me some slack, will you?
We've been so busy this week
we barely even saw each other.
I mean, tell me, what kind of
secret meetings are you having
that you're meeting with the President
day and night?
That's confidential.
No fair.
Should we leave work together?
Yes! [gasps] Oh, I can't.
Do you have plans?
I have to practice a song today
for a friend's wedding.
Hmm… Then I can drive you
to practice if you want.
You don't have to, but if you insist.
Since it's pitch-black outside
even when I clock out on the dot.
So dangerous. [chuckles]
-[Kee-tae] Mr. Kang.
-[gasps]
Goodness.
[footsteps approaching]
-Gosh, you spilled it?
-Yeah.
Are you all right?
Yes, sir.
Geez, you should've been more careful.
I'll do it.
What's the matter, huh?
You took so long, I thought you were
picking the green tea leaves yourself.
It's not green tea,
it's hibiscus.
Hibiscus.
Blood?
Well then, enjoy your tea.
Wait, I thought we were drinking to…
[sighs] Man, it's not easy
to get close to Mr. Kang.
-[chuckles]
-[slurps]
[groans] That's sour.
So what do you do here exactly?
Audio mixing.
Can you show me?
I want to see how it's done.
[acoustic pop music playing]
[gasps]
[music stops]
I blend all these separate tracks together
to turn them into one cohesive song.
Oh…
It's kind of like my company.
We also have different teams
collaborating to make one product.
I never would've guessed that
you work at an electronics company.
Why? I suddenly look grown-up?
Mm-hmm.
You must've worked really hard
in your life.
Yeah, I kept my head down
and worked diligently.
And what's the result?
You've seen how that turned out.
Isn't it for the best though?
You're better off
not marrying a jerk like that.
That's true. I guess I got really lucky.
Of course.
And you got a young handsome guy now.
[laughs]
So, teacher, when are you teaching?
Yeah, I should.
Oh, next time, should we do it
at my place instead?
It's closer to your place too.
Hey… [scoffs] …um, come on.
You can't just invite me
over to your place like that.
Is that a bit too much?
Then, what if we started dating?
Why do you keep…
Or wait.
Are we actually already dating?
[door opens]
Lee Jae-in!
What's this?
You broke up with me
because you got a new girl?
No. I'm not the cheating type of guy.
Who are you?
What's going on between you two, huh?
You two talk.
I'm going to leave now.
-No-ah.
-Hey!
Jae-in.
Where are you going?
[Jae-in] No-ah.
No-ah.
Call me Ms. Yoon.
Okay. Ms. No-ah.
[scoffs] Never mind.
It doesn't matter
what you call me now, does it?
You're fired now.
Are you angry at me?
When did you break up
with your girlfriend?
Two months ago.
About the same time you did.
Hmm.
And you were totally fine with it?
Yeah.
I wasn't that sad actually.
The feelings weren't there anymore.
It's over, No-ah.
My feelings for you are gone.
Do you have any idea
how selfish you sound?
What keeps a relationship going
isn't that first spark you felt,
it's effort.
Have you even thought about how
she must've felt coming all this way here?
How can effort ever turn into love?
I don't think that's love.
You're way too shallow.
And I just hate that.
That's not true.
And I'm not shallow.
[sighs]
Thank you so much for the ride.
I'll call you tonight.
Hi.
What's wrong?
[Ga-eul] Long time no see.
Have you been well?
What's going on?
Well, Ha-eun had to drop out last minute,
so I told Seung-jun, and…
Yeah, so Ga-eul insisted
he wanted to do it.
How could you consider
doing a wedding song without me?
It's Hye-ji's wedding.
I was really hurt, you know.
Hey, Ga-eul.
You should… [whispers] …get lost.
-[chuckles] Mmm.
-[sighs] Let's practice.
[Seung-jun]
Okay. Since it's the first day,
let's just do a quick run-through
and call it a night. Yeah.
Yeah. Sounds… Sounds good.
[Hye-ji exclaims]
-Hey. I'm going to go--
-[Seung-jun] Hey,
Ga-eul got a car with his signing bonus.
[Hye-ji] What?
-This is yours?
-[Ga-eul] Yes.
[Hye-ji gasps]
Hop in, guys. I'll drop you all off.
Whoa. No way.
Let's go and stomp all over
his brand-new seats.
-[gasps]
-[Seung-jun] Let's go, let's go! Come on.
Whoa, nice car.
Hey, remember when Seung-jun
drove his dad's car
and we all went to Gangneung?
[groans] Don't.
Just thinking about that day…
We ran out of gas,
couldn't find a station,
and called roadside assistance.
Yeah. It was bad enough that we
were waiting in that boiling hot weather,
but then Ga-eul started singing
in the middle of the road. [scoffs]
[laughs] You're right.
Yeah, someone even tossed him coins,
remember?
That's right!
[Hye-ji] Wow. He's come a long way.
Well, I have my own place again.
I'm happy for you.
It's far away,
but you can still see the Hangang River.
And there's a park in front.
A family of cats live there too.
I feel like the future
we imagined together
has gotten closer.
[Ji-yoon] Your once blurry dream
is starting to come into focus.
Congratulations, Ga-eul.
Next time,
I'll invite you over with the others.
You can drop me off over there.
Why? Let me just drive you home.
No.
I don't think this is a good idea.
Can't we at least stay friends?
We were friends for so long
before we even started dating.
I don't think I can do that,
not with you.
Drop me off here.
[phone buzzing]
[buzzing continues]
[sighs] If I answer now,
I might end up lying.
MANAGER KANG SI-WOO
Maybe later.
I can tell him tomorrow.
[sighs]
[operator] Your call cannot be completed.
You will be connected…
[line clicks]
[Si-woo] After I wrap up my day,
I wait to hear from you.
It's become my favorite part
of the day lately.
But it looks like that little joy of mine
is missing tonight.
I just hope everything is okay with you.
Sleep well.
Did you sleep well?
Yes.
I hadn't played the drums in a long time,
so I was exhausted.
-Yesterday, I…
-[Na-ri] Mr. Kang.
Should we prepare some drinks too?
Yes, please do.
Oh, and, Ms. Cha,
could you please give me a hand?
Hmm.
[Soo-jin] This is the mock-up design
based on the new Home-AI concept
proposed by the task force.
We've hidden the voice recognition module
and open-door sensors
for a clean aesthetic.
Additionally, the camera is positioned
at the top center of the unit,
while the screen remains
on the upper-right door panel.
Well, it looks very nice and clean.
The exterior design
hasn't changed much from before.
Yes. Our assessment for now is that the
current placement and size of the screen
is still our best option.
Hmm.
Should we proceed with this then?
If we keep the current screen size,
it will be released
as an ultra-premium model, right?
Yes, it most likely will.
Then how about we scale back
the screen size
to lower the retail price?
[Soo-jin] Hmm…
If the screen is too small, it will look
like a purely functional gadget.
I want this product to bring the Home-AI
experience to more and more people.
That's why I'd like to
lower the retail price.
Even if it means reducing the screen size.
Consumers these days care prioritize
design elements over functional features.
They want their fridge to look
like furniture, not a home appliance.
Well, I think promoting Home-AI
should take priority.
We call it aesthetics, right?
We might just be
making electronic appliances,
but it's still a value
we must never sacrifice.
Yes, however--
Let's move on to the final mock-up.
Fine.
As the product planner,
I wanted to explain my intent a bit more.
I thought your point came across
clearly enough.
I don't.
I didn't get to explain everything
because you cut me off.
Dragging out the discussion
could lead to needless conflict.
When the mock-up is done,
we'll discuss this again.
[sighs]
How could he just
cut me off like that
without even letting me finish?
And he only listened to Ms. Choi.
[sighs] This is ridiculous.
Things like this
happen all the time at work.
I know it's nothing,
so why am I feeling so miserable?
[sighs]
[exhales heavily]
Oh, Ms. Choi.
Where's Mr. Kang Si-woo?
Did he go somewhere?
Oh, well, he's probably in a meeting
with the President.
Did something happen?
He just wasn't answering my calls.
I wonder when he's back.
I'm not sure. He's been working late
every day, so…
-[sighs]
-[phone buzzing]
MANAGER KANG SI-WOO
All right, then.
I'll reach out to him later.
Okay.
Oh…
You did great today.
Seeing you speak your mind
so confidently was impressive.
Thanks to you,
I noticed what I've been missing too.
I'll keep it in mind.
-[sighs]
-[phone buzzes]
[Si-woo] It's been hard to catch you
on the phone lately.
You are so pathetic,
Cha Ji-yoon.
[secretary] Mr. Kang Si-woo?
-Yes.
-She's ready for you.
Thank you.
[Young-hun] Ms. Cha Ji-yoon?
Oh…
Mr. Lee Young-hun?
Yes.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you too.
Please sit down.
-Sure.
-Yes.
[chuckles] So we finally meet in person.
I know, right.
The post you wrote really helped clear up
the misunderstandings about Mr. Kang.
[chuckles] Thank you.
Ah. So you need Gen AI technology?
Ah, yes.
Uh, we'd like an ingredient
recognition feature on the refrigerator.
Do you happen to have a project proposal?
-Uh, just a moment.
-Sure.
-Here you go.
-Thank you.
INGREDIENT RECOGNITION
AND RECIPE GENERATION
Hmm.
This looks fun. [chuckles]
If you're able to return to work,
I wanted to ask you
to start working on it right away.
Before another team snatches you up,
you know.
[chuckles]
Um…
That sounds good. I will give it a shot.
Uh, well, In that case,
would it be possible
to move up your return date a little?
Thing is,
we're on a really tight schedule.
Sure.
I've actually been itching to
get back to work anyway, so this is great.
I'll return right away.
[sighs] Thank you so much.
I look forward to working with you.
I look forward to working with you too.
-Well, take care then.
-You too.
-Thank you.
-Likewise.
CALLS
MISSED - MANAGER KANG SI-WOO
[phone buzzes]
MESSAGE FROM
SR. ASSOCIATE CHA JI-YOON
[Ji-yoon] Mr. Lee Young-hun
has agreed to join the task force.
[sighs]
[line ringing]
Yes, Mr. Noh.
I have agreed to join the task force.
You know, I missed you all day long.
You saw me during the day though.
I meant outside of work.
We've been missing each other
a lot lately.
That's because you're always so busy.
Were you very upset about earlier?
A little.
Well, no, very.
From now on, I'll put
all personal feelings aside at work.
and treat you strictly as a team member.
I might even be tougher on you.
My mind seems to understand it,
but my heart doesn't.
I want to keep it a secret,
but I hate that it is.
You seem so relaxed,
while I'm the only one feeling anxious.
And things that never really
bothered me before
just keep making me feel upset now.
These days, I can't focus on work.
Working out isn't so fun,
and I keep forgetting
to take my supplements.
And if I don't get to speak to you
before bed,
it feels like my whole day's ruined.
Like a teenager.
[chuckles] You do know how to coddle.
[groans]
I should whine more often.
As much as you want.
-Are you working tomorrow?
-Hmm.
I threw a little tantrum at the CEO
to have the day off tomorrow.
You really have become a teenager.
So, you wanna come over
for some late-night snacks?
There they are, the brows of truth.
[laughing]
Mr. Kang, do you feel uncomfortable
now that you're here?
Not at all. I'm comfortable.
I promise that I won't bite.
Just relax and feel at home.
How disappointing.
[chuckles]
Just a moment.
[phone buzzes]
[Ga-eul] Let's just keep things
comfortable between us
at least until we're done
with the wedding song.
I'll see you at practice tomorrow.
Ji-yoon.
Can you pull out of the wedding song?
What?
I guess it's too late
to pull out now, isn't it?
Hmm.
Yes, I've already agreed to do it.
It's my best friend's wedding too.
Why, all of a sudden?
Well, there's a big sale
at the supermarket tomorrow.
Oh.
Should I just tell him now?
No. Tomorrow.
So, should we meet after practice then?
Yes, of course.
By the way,
Ms. Choi came by earlier saying
she couldn't reach you when she tried.
Did you two get to talk?
Yes.
What did she call you
during that phone call?
"Mr. Kang Si-woo"?
Or was it "Si-woo"?
-The song…
-The call…
Ooh! Oh, no!
-Ji-yoon!
-Yes?
There aren't any towels in the bathroom.
Oh. Hang on one sec.
Do you want to come in?
Sorry?
Yes.
[romantic music playing]
MISSED CALL
MANAGER CHOI SOO-JIN
MESSAGE FROM
[Soo-jin] Have you thought about
the favor I asked over the phone?
[music continues]
[Hye-ji] You said you wouldn't.
You told me not to worry!
[Seong-min] You like her that much?
[Si-woo] She's too good for me.
[Soo-jin] Kang Si-woo,
you've changed a lot.
Tell me.
Something's up with Ji-yoon, right?
[Hye-ji]
You said his ex-wife was your mentor.
[Ji-yoon] To be honest, it bothers me.
It seems that I lied to you.
[Ga-eul] I want you to stop seeing him.
[Ji-yoon] Why did you two divorce?
Whatever the reason,
is it something
that I'll be able to handle?