(This murderer imitates the murders
in an underground manga called Nekros.)
This is the work of a serial killer?
I’m sure it is.
His pen name is Mr. Kill.
I bet some editors have seen
his work before.
Oh, Mr. Kaye.
Inspector, the editor’s in today.
We’re looking for the artist
behind this manga.
Where are you rushing off to, Mr. Kaye?
Anti-anxiety med…
You look distressed.
Take it easy.
We…
We have a lot to talk about.
Hey.
Yes?
Do you recognize this art style?
Uhh, no, no, I don’t.
I’ve never seen this before.
And if you actually think about it,
a work of this violet nature,
compared to mine,
is completely opposite.
Like, look.
I do think it looks familiar.
It looks like an old art style of…
If I ever drew something
as graphic as this,
I’d probably lose all my fans.
Inspector.
The editor said this art style
looks like it belongs to an artist
named Kaye.
I–I think he must have misunderstood.
Oh, he’s right.
Kaye hasn’t written anything experimental
like this for a long time.
This won’t sell.
I might really have misunderstood.
Many artists draw like that
these days, you know?
Follow him.
Have your fill.
Because I…
might not be able to come
and feed you anymore.
Inspector.
Why are you suspecting him?
People don’t panic like that
even when being cornered.
Only someone with a secret does.
When he feels safe and at ease,
this is how he is.
Let’s see if he’s gonna stay that way.
I have to go.
I’ve got Kaye’s previous works.
The publishing house’s database
is full of artwork like this.
What do you want to do now?
Looks like he’s going outside.
METROPOLITAN INVESTIGATIVE BUREAU
Are you sure about this?
We don’t have a warrant, sir.
We could get sued for this.
Not if he never finds out.
We’ll just get in
and get out.
Yes, sir.
Whoa.
This is K.Cupid’s room?
It’s kinda spooky, sir.
I’m installing a remote software.
It can restore any recently deleted files.
Okay.
A photo with a fan, huh?
Wait.
Isn’t that you, Inspector?
Oh!
Mr. Kaye!
He’s the guy whose autograph
was on your jacket that day!
Oh, Inspector.
Why didn’t you tell me
you’re into that kind of manga?
Who’d have thought
from your usual smolder?
We’re working.
Get it done and over with.
Yes, sir.
(Sir, the target is on his way to you.)
Yes?
I’m on my way.
Of course.
I’m off, Mom.
Prim.
Don’t forget to drink this.
You’re the best.
Oh, Praew.
You’re early.
You had breakfast?
No, I didn’t.
Here.
To start off your day.
Is it good?
Thank you.
Shall we?
Hello.
What should we do?
Yesterday Thun didn’t tell us
what we had to do at all.
Should we ask these people
if they need us for anything?
Hey, guys. Welcome to your first day.
Here.
This is all the information
on the two murders.
Try to analyze it and compare it
to the manga shot by shot.
Find a connection
that this is no coincidence.
Can you do that?
Of course.
Yes, of course.
Okay.
I don’t care whether you’re young or old.
I only care that you’re hard working.
Give it a shot.
Alright.
Let’s begin.
Oh, wow, we might as well die.
I bet it will take us a whole week
to read through all this.
And it’s just the two of us?
Come on.
It’s good that we get to do
real work, right?
I’d say it’s better than
taking coffee orders.
Alright. I’ll do my best.
Alright!
Let’s get to work.
Slay.
Look at this.
The rope and the wounds
are exactly the same.
This can't be a coincidence.
I think the murderer didn’t just kill
to imitate the manga,
I think they even made sure
the setup looks exactly alike.
Honestly…
I didn’t think you’d be a fan
of such a graphic manga, Praew.
I guess I’m kinda repressed.
I don’t have any power in real life,
so I find comfort in manga like this.
It’s cathartic.
I understand.
Oh, I’ve read through
the details of both cases.
Shall we combine it?
I’m dying to see Thun so stunned
his jaw drops to the floor.
That’s good.
So this page…
And this one…
Inspector.
Isn’t this cat food?
Yeah.
Did you grab the wrong bag or what?
No.
Ugh, it’s so fishy!
Hello.
You’re lucky today, huh?
Someone already fed you.
I have to go.
See you later.
Yes?
Oh.
Of course.
Inspector.
IT just told me
they found something important.
IT looked through Kaye’s IP address
and found that he’s accessed Nekros blog’s
back-end system several times.
More importantly,
they’re able to recover more than 50%
of the files deleted.
It’s Nekros’ manuscript.
Inspector, only the artist himself
would have something like that.
I think Kaye is Mr. Kill.
Proceed with the team.
Issue an arrest warrant.
Yes.
We’re bringing him into custody.
What happened?
Don’t tell me he got away.
Yes, sir.
I bet he’s still around here somewhere.
Spread out.
Be careful. He could be armed.
Yes, sir.
Let’s go.
Bun, Nat, go that way.
Yes, sir.
Nop, you go there.
I’m–I’m sorry.
I won’t run anymore.
But I really don’t have it.
You gave Chid all the money yesterday,
didn’t you?
They told me you’re here.
Where’s my money?
I gave them all the money.
I don’t have anything right now.
Will you try to understand me a little?
No, I won’t!
It’s my money.
You will give it back to me.
Turn out his bag.
Oh, he has a hammer.
Why are you carrying a hammer?
Are you gonna smash our heads open?
Huh?
You think this is Whac-A-Mole
or something?
You’re broke, huh?
That’s fine.
I’ll just take what little interest
you can pay up for now.
Hammer, huh?
How arrogant!
How dare you!
You dare bring a hammer!
You planned to hurt us? Huh?
Your father may be gone,
but his debt isn’t.
You gotta pay for it.
If you don’t,
just be ready to meet your dad
in the grave.
Let’s go.
You sure you good?
I don’t have a connection, man.
I’m out of data.
Just hurry up.
Drop your weapon.
I said drop your weapon!
Hey! Drop your weapon!
Slowly.
The doctor said you’ll be fine.
It’s just some scratches
and a cut on your head.
Speaking of which…
What should I call you?
Atima?
Chankacha?
K.Cupid?
Or Mr. Kill?
Your name changes history…
Five times in five years.
The IP address used to log into
the back-end system of Nekros blog…
is at your place.
Am I right?
Oh…
There’s also the high definition
manuscript you deleted.
What I said just now…
Was any of it incorrect?
Hey.
Silence won’t save you, Mr. Kaye.
Right now,
you’re the prime suspect
in the serial murder case.
Do you understand your situation?
Well, then, let me ask…
Last night,
what were you doing in a dark alley?
Why did you run when you saw the police?
I–I…
I didn’t do it.
Hey!
What innocent man walks around
with a hammer covered in blood
alone in a dark alley
in the middle of the night?
Why do you carry it?
For your next victim?
It–It’s not like that.
I carry it…
For self-defense.
Self-defense?
From who?
The…
Debt collectors.
Okay.
The debt collectors
and the hammer check out.
But explain this…
Why are these two cases
exactly like your manga?
I–I don’t know.
I wrote from my imagination.
I’m telling the truth.
I swear.
I don’t know anything about this
and I didn’t kill anyone.
Thank you.
Oh, Inspector.
This guy’s life has been one living hell.
His father was one of the suspects
in the Thai Investment Bank 20 years ago.
He was charged with fraud
and declared bankrupt.
His father is dead now.
But he’s still paying for that debt.
And the weapon analysis?
Almost done.
He’s still a suspect.
We’re keeping him in custody.
Yes, sir.
(What looks like coincidences
at first glance)
(has been proven by my team.)
(It is undeniable that the details
left behind by the murderer)
(are the exact replica
of the manga Nekros.)
(There’s only one question left:)
MURDERS IMITATE MANGA
(Will the murderer stop here
or will he do it again?)
Listen, you guys.
This is amazing.
The hashtag Looking For Nekros
is still in top trending today.
That’s so cool.
You two are more than
just interns now, you know?
You proved this is true.
Let’s give them a round of applause.
You don’t believe you could do it?
I do.
I’m just still confused.
Let’s pack up and celebrate.
What should we have for dinner?
You can pick.
Well…
Barbecue?
Nah. My hair’d smell of smoke.
Hotpot?
Not bad.
Okay.
Traikanawut.
That’s a familiar surname.
Oh?
Praew, wait up.
Everyone knows
my dad was the dirty cop
in the Thai Investment case.
Who knows how many people
killed themselves because of him?
But my parents are dead.
Only my brother and I
were left to carry their sin.
Who your father was
has nothing to do with who you are.
Surnames are nothing
but a word on your badge.
It’s what you do that defines you, Praew.
To me,
you’re the coolest friend ever.
Stop looking so glum!
He’s been pacing around for hours.
He doesn’t ask for water or food,
and he doesn’t say a word.
ททท
Uh…
Anybody there?
Officer?
Is anybody there?
There’s going to be another victim!
Officer!
Is anybody there?
Officer.
Take a look at these again.
I don’t think the murderer imitates
my manga just to feed his own ego.
He’s trying to communicate
by leaving clues in the crime scenes
in a way that no one else would notice.
Like this one.
From the look of it,
it’s nothing more than
the victim’s attempt at saving his life.
But…
What if the murderer actually
meant to leave a clue
meaning the number 10?
And what does ‘10’ mean?
It means the next victim
comes from Chapter 10 of Nekros.
And that became this case.
Nonsense.
Blood splattered everywhere.
The victim was hit in the head
and bloodily struggling on the floor.
It was only natural all 10
of his fingerprints were on the floor.
Inspector.
I think it’s just a coincidence.
He’s just making things up.
If your theory is right,
what about the second case?
In the permanent secretary case,
what clue did the murderer leave?
The permanent secretary case
happened in Chapter 10 of Nekros.
But I wrote this panel as the cover
for Chapter 14 of Nekros.
In my opinion, I think the murderer
is giving us a clue that
the next victim is going to
come from Nekros,
Chapter 14.
Is Chapter 14 in the files we recovered?
Some files were destroyed in the process,
and I couldn’t recover all of it.
I’m not sure, sir.
Look it up.
I found it, sir.
It’s intact.
Open it.
Uh…
Chapter 14 of Nekros
is about a famous lawyer
who uses his words
and the loophole in the laws
to frame scapegoats
in order to save his rich clients
from going to jail.
In the end,
the murderer, Nekros, kills this lawyer,
and sews his mouth shut
as a symbol that he will never tell
another lie again.
I think the next victim is going to be…
a rule-bending defense attorney.
The first two victims
were a civil servant and a businessman.
Which coincide
with both chapters of Nekros.
His theory might be right.
How many evil lawyers do you think
there are in this country?
How will we know who’s the target?
This murderer is meticulous
with their plans.
According to the first two cases,
the victims were locked up for three days
before they got killed.
So what the murderer needs is time.
They need time to find the right place
and time to set up to imitate Nekros.
Look through our nation-wide database.
We’re looking for a lawyer
who’s been reported missing,
or been incommunicado
for the last few days.
If we find someone like that,
by all means assume that
this is the next victim of Nekros.
Yes, sir.
Inspector.
We got five more reports
for missing lawyers with ambiguous history.
Here.
I’m not hungry.
I can’t have you saying us police officers
don’t take good care of our suspects.
It’s not like I’m allowed to say anything.
Just eat.
I didn’t put anything weird in there,
except my well wishes.
I can’t stomach anything.
Stubborn bastard.
Give me your hands.
Can I go home now?
No.
What?
You must stay where I can see you 24/7.
At least until we find that lawyer.
We have to be sure
you’re not just messing with us.
You go where I go.
Eat where I eat.
Sleep where I sleep.
And if I need to go to the toilet?
I’ll go with you.
Are you for real?
Oh.
And don’t even think about running.
If you do,
I’m not above shooting you in the leg.
Got it?
Yes.
How are you gonna hammer
someone’s head in that state?
Three of these, please.
Three bags…
That makes 210 baht.
Can I have one instead?
I’ll return the rest.
Of course.
That’s 70 baht.
-Here.
-Thank you.
Thank you.
Of course.
Uh…
I’ll take these two he didn’t get.
Of course.
Two bags. That’s 140 baht.
Okay.
Here.
-Thank you.
You think I’m okay with my manga
being used as death sentences?
From now on, you’re not a suspect.
Sorry I’m late.
You’re the special consultant
to the Nekros Investigative Team.
If you want to stop feeling
so guilty about it,
work with me.
Let’s catch this guy.