"Blue Lips"
(Episode 4)
Something's not right.
How come every time Brother Mo shows up,
Xiao Wu switches to these
tender, romantic songs?
He changes the song,
and you change your drink.
Could he be singing
them specifically for you?
What are you talking about?
You know exactly what our relationship is.
Where's my Long Island Iced Tea?
Right.
Xiao Wu.
The guests at that table are
waiting for you to go over.
Looking handsome as always today.
What's wrong? Not happy?
I bought you a few bottles.
If you ever need anything in the future,
just call me anytime.
Why the attitude when
you're out having fun?
I brought so many people here and
you're just going to have that attitude?
Drink this glass,
and we'll call it an apology.
He's a singer who draws
in such a big crowd.
Are you really going
to let him drink like that?
That's a bit unfair, isn't it?
Look who's talking.
Blue Moon is a respectable place.
We're all looking out for him.
Besides,
the kid needs the money.
He's willing to drink with customers.
Who wouldn't want to make
some extra cash while they're young?
He knows his limits.
If I book that booth,
can I get him to drink with me?
Why? Do you want to try?
Brother Hao, let me explain.
I was just playing around with him.
[An extremely smarmy string of
texts pining after Wu Shixian]
If you were just playing
around, why are you panicking?
I heard you go to Blue Moon
every day to listen to music
just because of him.
Brother Hao.
He's the one who seduced me first.
When he was seducing me,
you were the only one
on my mind, Brother Hao.
You were flirting with him like crazy,
and he completely ignored you.
And you're telling me he seduced you?
Do you think I'm blind?
No...
You...
Even though you've only been
with me for a couple of months,
we still have some history.
While I'm still letting
you keep some dignity,
get the hell out of here.
Let him go.
Brother Hao!
You're really the only one in my heart!
Drag him out.
Guan Zhenghao, who the
hell do you think you are?
How dare you treat me like this?
Guan Zhenghao!
Don't think you're a big shot just
because you have some dirty money!
You're just a bastard
with no father to raise you!
In this world,
no one truly loves you,
and no one will ever care about you!
Bury him.
Guan Zhenghao!
You bastard!
This ball is mine.
Hey, can you give it back to me?
Xiao Le, slow down.
Xiao Hao.
Why are you bullying
your little brother again?
Xiao Le, right?
This ball...
is mine now.
What is wrong with you?
He's your brother!
Does a stepbrother even count as a brother?
Besides,
it's just a toy.
What's the big deal?
He's not like you.
You're right.
Of course he's not like me.
Xiao Hao.
Today is your birthday.
I won't scold you.
Go back to your grandmother's house early.
Don't make her worry.
Let's go.
Xiao Wu.
The guest in the VIP booth
wants you to go over for a drink.
I got it.
Have a seat.
Come on.
How do you want to drink?
Should we cross arms,
or just drink together?
You don't have to drink
when you're with me.
Who knows if you've slipped
something strange in here.
Drink up.
Then...
what about all this alcohol?
Return it.
Just kidding.
Is that funny?
That's cold.
This booth has a minimum spend.
You really went all out this time.
I spent a little,
but it's hardly going all out.
Consider it a treat for once.
Are you enjoying it?
There are many ways to enjoy things.
This is the first time
I've sat in front of so much alcohol
without taking a single sip.
It feels quite nice.
What kind of feeling?
A feeling of solitude.
Do you want to skip work?
What?
Even though I'm not a local,
still,
even the locals in Jinyang
don't know this place as well as I do.
I don't believe you.
Why not?
This place tonight is the best proof.
By the way,
there's a question I've
been meaning to ask you.
Go ahead.
The first time you came to
my shop to buy medicine,
there were so many shops on that street.
Why did you choose mine?
Because of...
the light at your storefront, I guess.
The light?
The lights at the other shops
were either white
or red.
Only your shop's light
was yellow.
I...
I just...
Just because of that?
What else would it be?
Because you're handsome?
Am I not handsome?
Don't flatter yourself.
Actually,
this is...
the best stargazing spot around Jinyang.
Most people can't find it.
Here,
let me show you.
Look,
that's Jupiter,
to the west of the moon.
And to the north is Sirius.
Further east
is Mars.
And then?
The brightness of planets
is much more stable,
because they don't change.
They aren't affected by anything.
But stars
are affected by atmospheric interference.
They look like they're twinkling.
Look,
it's twinkling, right?
So as long as the distance is far enough,
even the biggest things
will seem tiny.
It's the same with human worries.
Shixian.
Your nights
should be reserved for beautiful things,
like the ocean,
like the stars,
not spent at Blue Moon,
and certainly not on some
insignificant people.
But,
but I still need to make money.
Then make it tomorrow.
Here,
let's play with this tonight.
Where did you get this?
I stole it.
Then let's light it together.
Pretty?
Yes.
Teng Mo.
Thank you.
Search every single booth!
Today,
even if I have to turn
this place upside down,
I will find that bastard.
Throw them out!
Are you okay?
I'm fine, I'm fine.
Be careful, there might be
glass shards in your clothes.
Are you guys okay?
We're fine.
Are you alright?
Well...
I...
I'll just go back and
put some ointment on it.
Clean myself up.
Teng Mo,
I'm going to step out for a moment.
Go on, hurry.
Go ahead.
We're closed for today.
Please come back another day.
Let me do it.
Does it hurt?
It's okay.
What on earth happened today?
Someone just came to catch a mistress.
No wonder.
Barging around like crazy.
You shouldn't be so
impulsive in the future.
A glass cut to the neck is no joke.
I wasn't thinking much at the time.
Why were you late today?
Don't I usually come around this time?
Usually, you're here right
when my performance starts.
I got held up by some
things at the shop today.
So...
were you...
rushing over just to see me?
Half and half.
Half of it is because...
you got hurt because of me.
And the other half?
I have no more Vandacon.
You still...
You still want to take it?
Is that all you wanted to ask me?
Can you stop working there in the future?
Why?
Although Blue Moon Bar
is a legitimate business,
it still attracts all kinds of people.
If that bottle had hit you today,
what would you have done?
Do you love poking your nose into
other people's business that much?
Yes.
I was being nosy.
Wait here.
Here.
Didn't you want to buy Vandacon?
Here you go.
It's not what you think.
Brother Mo.
Whiskey...?
Just a beer, please.
Sure.
Thanks.
Go wait outside.
Brother Mo.
I'll head over there.
Brother Hao.
What brings you here?
Nothing much.
Just brought the boys out to have some fun.
Then have a great time!
I'm sorry, sir.
Today's VIP booths have
already been reserved.
What guest could be more
important than Brother Hao?
Go ahead.
Okay.
Brother Hao,
I'll get it sorted out.
Just a guy from the streets.
An old acquaintance.
He doesn't usually hang out at bars.
Who knows what he's here for today.
He's barely got any peach fuzz,
and he's wearing blue lipstick.
Pretty flashy.
I heard he drinks with customers.
Chris likes this type.
So he's that kind of trash.
No wonder.
Call him over.
Sure.