"Blue Lips"
(Episode 5)
Barely got any peach fuzz,
yet he wears blue lipstick.
Pretty flashy.
Chris likes this type.
I heard he even drinks with the customers.
So he's that kind of trash.
No wonder.
Call him over.
Sure.
Waiter.
The one with the blue lips.
Bring him over.
Right away.
Pour the drinks.
I heard Blue Moon got a new cash cow.
I came here today just to
shake some money loose for you.
Drink up.
Oh, right. I forgot.
Drinking with you
costs money, right?
Curly.
Not enough?
Drink.
Brother Hao.
What's...
What's happening here?
Ah Heng.
Don't be nervous.
I really like this kid.
I just want to make friends with him.
But Brother Hao...
Don't just stand there.
Keep drinking.
Ah Heng,
go tend to your own business.
Ah Heng.
Go.
Okay.
What?
Not enough money?
Think about it.
How many songs do you have to sing,
and how many drinks do you have to take,
to make this much in one night?
Drink.
I thought Chris found
someone really special.
Is that it?
Boss,
I'll drink for him.
Look at this.
A loyal lapdog who can drink.
Boss,
you really shouldn't do this.
Things could get out of hand.
You have a point.
But I, Guan Zhenghao, am
the last person to fear trouble.
Boss,
there's no need for this.
Let's go.
They didn't follow us.
We're safe.
Are you okay?
How about this?
Want to race?
Let's see who gets there first.
What's the penalty for the loser?
Granting the winner one wish.
Then prepare to lose.
You're on.
Three,
two,
one!
Go ahead.
What's your wish?
I'm exhausted.
I'll save it.
I'll tell you next time.
I'm beat.
I'm heading out then.
You can stay here and catch your breath.
Wait for me. I can't walk.
I'm starving after that run.
I'm sorry.
I dragged you into this.
Look at you, growing up.
You actually know how to apologize.
Actually, it's not your fault.
Those thugs were dead
set on causing trouble.
The more you resist,
the harder they push.
That's just how they are.
But credit where credit is due,
you looked really cool back there.
How are you holding up?
I'm fine.
Really?
Why would I lie to you?
Because you lie all the time.
But seriously,
how did you cross them?
I don't know.
Never mind then.
Why the sigh?
I was just thinking...
We got through today,
is behind us,
but what about the next few days?
Don't worry.
It'll figure itself out.
Leave it to me.
Let's go.
What do you want to eat?
Grab whatever you want.
My treat.
Here.
Have some milk.
You drink a lot of alcohol.
That can take a toll on you.
Yogurt works too.
Anyway,
drinking this will make you feel better.
Didn't you say you were hungry?
I bought you a cake.
Eat up.
How old are you?
Thirty.
Is there a rule saying
you can't eat this past age ten?
Childish.
This is actually pretty good.
It doesn't taste like
childhood anymore, though.
But seriously,
what are your plans for the future?
Like what?
Are you still going to
sing at Ah Heng's place?
At worst, I just won't go back.
I can sing anywhere.
That might not work.
If Ah Heng has a big mouth
and tells other bar owners,
what if no one hires you?
Then what should I do?
Don't worry.
I'll find a way.
What could you possibly do?
Problems...
always get figured out.
Anyway, for the next few days,
stay away from Blue Moon.
Next month,
you can come back to work.
Why are you helping me?
I'm worried no one will
buy Vandacon from me.
Get lost.
Just eat your popsicle.
It tastes bad.
Here, take it back.
Speak.
Brother Hao,
yesterday was a misunderstanding.
I'm Wu Shixian's brother.
Xiao Wu.
Even though he fought
back out of self-defense,
he still ended up hurting your man.
I'm here to apologize on his behalf.
Well, well.
Every word you say puts the blame on me.
Your brother cracked my man's head open,
and now you're blaming me?
No.
At the time,
your man's fist was already in his face,
which constitutes unlawful assault.
Xiao Wu only acted to stop it.
This action,
legally speaking,
is defined as self-defense.
But I know.
Brother Hao is a man of honor,
and your men
are fiercely loyal.
You are reasonable,
so you must understand this.
You're using all these fancy words
just to stop me from
getting to your brother, right?
Brother Hao,
you're a very busy man.
I know that.
Picking on ordinary folks like us
is beneath you.
And what if I say...
I want to pick on you anyway?
Then, for Wu Shixian's sake,
I'll have to stand up to you.
Let's hear it.
How exactly do you plan
to rise to the occasion?
Brother Hao, you front for others
and use blank contracts
to collect interest.
I know all about it.
If word of this gets out...
Are you saying
you're planning to go up against me?
You're joking, Brother Hao.
What's your background, kid?
Nothing special.
Just like Wu Shixian,
I'm just an ordinary citizen.
If I have a choice,
of course I'd rather make a friend
than make an enemy.
Besides,
I didn't come empty-handed.
Curly.
Interesting.
How did you find this guy?
I just happen to have some connections.
Fine.
You can go.
Thanks, Brother Hao.
I finally found you.
Ah Hao,
Uncle is going to take
you to do something fun.
Sound good?
I haven't ordered yet.
I ordered it.
It's on me.
That's a first.
Why are you buying me a drink?
Because this is...
Blue Moon's new drink.
I wanted
to get your feedback on it.
Using me as a guinea pig?
A bit sour.
Not my thing.
Just kidding.
It's better than whiskey
or Long Island iced tea.
Brother Hao.
Brother Hao is here.
Waiter!
Here.
Come, come, come.
Let me pour you a drink.
Last time,
I couldn't bring Xiao
Wu to apologize to you.
That was my bad.
Stand up.
Here, Brother Hao.
It was my fault. Let me make it up to you.
Come on, you two.
Before,
we were too impulsive.
We were wrong.
Please don't hold it against us.
Please forgive us.
You startled me.
Xiao Mo,
you're a friend worth having.
If anything happens on
this street in the future,
you can use my name, Guan Zhenghao.
Understood.
Hurry up and thank Brother Hao.
Thank you, Brother Hao.
Ah, youth.
I have things to do. I'm leaving.
I won't stay.
Remember our agreement
for the day after tomorrow.
I'll be on time the day after tomorrow.
It's finally settled.
How did you settle it?
First of all,
you have to calm down.
People
can always be reasoned with.
Appeal to their emotions and reason.
And then,
buy them a couple of bottles of wine,
and it's done.
Who are you kidding?
I'm going to perform.
Wait.
What time do you finish
the day after tomorrow?
Around
11:30.
Okay.
Go ahead.
What a coincidence.
What are you doing hiding here?
What do you mean hiding?
I was waiting for you here.
Why were you waiting for me?
To give you some candy.
Here.
Brother Hao gave it to me.
Is it poisoned?
You dare to eat something
Brother Hao gave you?
I'll test it for poison for you.
Okay.
This kind of candy
isn't meant to be bitten.
Like this.
How did it light up?
You look so silly.
You're the silly one.
Still, I should thank you
for helping me deal with Guan Zhenghao.
Let me tell you,
luckily no one hit any
vital spots this time.
If you had accidentally
hit his face or neck,
no one could have saved you.
How about...
I buy you dinner?
If you don't want to, never mind.
Fine, fine, fine.
I'll let you buy.
It's closed.
What do we do now?
We won't find any other place open now.
Um...
can you cook at your place?
My place?
If not, never mind.
Adults shouldn't back out.
Come on in.
Do you have slippers?
No.
I don't usually have guests,
so I didn't prepare extra.
Just come in. No need to be formal.
Where's the kitchen?
Okay.
Do you usually eat this stuff?
I usually just order takeout,
eat instant noodles, bread, or whatever.
Just to get by.
Do you have noodles?
On the table.
Okay.
Go sit over there and wait a bit.
Can you actually do this?
[He's searching "Ten Ways To Make
Eggs" and earnestly looking at the results]
How is it?
Are you okay?
Did you get burned?
I'm sorry.
It's nothing.
Go wash up in the bathroom
and change your clothes.