‎AGENT KIM REACTIVATED
‎EPISODE 8
‎Who's the commander who spared your life?
‎Who are the bastards
‎that slipped into the North?
‎Where's the route they used to cross over?
‎None of you have first or last names.
‎Let's see if you can take this.
‎Get it together!
‎Return to our country as heroes.
‎Should we see how long you can last?
‎You'll talk in the end.
‎The North may have discarded you,
‎but you still need to find a way
‎to make a life here.
‎Who makes up the chain of command
‎in the Cheonsan Unit?
‎List all of them, starting from the top.
‎You son of a bitch!
‎List all the schemes
‎you've been a part of!
‎This won't be easy to bear.
‎Who are the bastards that worked with you?
‎Give me their names and their networks.
‎You're a real man, aren't you?
‎Tell me who did what.
‎I want every single detail!
‎Forget everything, leave the past behind,
‎and live as Min-ji's dad.
‎Daddy!
‎Dad.
‎All right, then.
‎Let me cool you down.
‎Do you understand? Do you?!
‎You must've been thirsty.
‎Come back. I'll wait for you.
‎I love you a lot too, Dad.
‎Min-ji…
‎Tell me the location of the unit.
‎Tell me!
‎You can live if you tell me.
‎We can bury the past.
‎Now serve your country.
‎This is your country!
‎You're finally back where you belong.
‎You'll once again
‎become a proud revolutionary warrior
‎for our country!
‎You bastard.
‎Is this what you want?
‎You son of a bitch.
‎You know what?
‎I'll make sure your daughter
‎has the same experience as you.
‎I can even do worse than that.
‎It'll drive you insane, no?
‎Hey, asshole.
‎Have you passed out already?
‎That's disappointing.
‎Hold on.
‎You're not actually dead, are you?
‎Hey.
‎Number 66.
‎Welcome back to South Korea.
‎AGENT KIM REACTIVATED
‎The setup must've been convincing,
‎seeing how
‎even a North Korean fell for it.
‎That door acts like the 38th parallel.
‎What did I tell you?
‎This man would never betray us.
‎Why are you keeping me alive?
‎I think you asked me that same question
‎about 20 years ago too.
‎Our position remains the same
‎as it was then.
‎It's not because we like you
‎or pity you.
‎We've merely decided
‎to use you one last time
‎for our country's best interests.
‎If you complete this mission,
‎you'll become free again.
‎And your daughter too.
‎You'll have new identities.
‎What's the mission?
‎Brief him.
‎A few days ago,
‎a top-level North Korean official
‎escaped to China
‎and has requested asylum with us.
‎Getting them here isn't difficult,
‎but it just so happens to coincide
‎with the upcoming
‎high-level inter-Korean talks,
‎which puts us in a predicament.
‎If the North finds out
‎we've granted them asylum…
‎No, it's only a matter of time
‎before they find out.
‎Regardless, we have no choice
‎but to deny it.
‎That's why you're being assigned
‎to protect the asylum seeker.
‎You'll do so until the talks are over
‎and the delegation returns to the North.
‎Thanks to the trouble you've caused,
‎the North is bringing operatives as well.
‎How will you guarantee Min-ji's safety
‎while I carry out this mission?
‎Don't worry about that.
‎The SMD will take responsibility
‎and protect her.
‎You?
‎I don't trust you either.
‎I don't trust spies like you,
‎but your daughter
‎is a South Korean citizen,
‎and I'd put my life on the line
‎to protect South Korean citizens.
‎Come on now.
‎Even you can't deny
‎this man's sense of duty.
‎He just happens to be a jerk.
‎I also have a favor…
‎No.
‎I have a condition.
‎Release Sung Han-soo and Park Jin-cheol.
‎ISOLATION ROOM
‎DETENTION ROOM
‎You evil bastards!
‎What the hell did I do wrong, you jerks?
‎You didn't have to gag me!
‎You think I bite?
‎Do you?
‎Man, I'm hungry.
‎I'm so hungry.
‎I'm starving.
‎Excuse me.
‎Kim's co-worker
‎and Mr. Dry Cleaner.
‎I don't do jailbreaks.
‎How could I possibly do that?
‎Can you at least ungag me?
‎Please?
‎Please, I'm begging you.
‎Mr. Park Jin-cheol, you'll be transferred.
‎Where am I going?
‎Military prison?
‎We're going to sedate you
‎for the transfer.
‎We're following protocol,
‎so please cooperate.
‎Wait!
‎It's too dangerous.
‎Let's do it from out here.
‎How?
‎A tranquilizer gun.
‎A tranquilizer gun?
‎Yeah, a tranquilizer gun.
‎Will you stand still? You'll get hurt!
‎Please cooperate.
‎We're following protocol!
‎What are you going to do to me
‎when I'm under?
‎I'm not some animal that escaped the zoo.
‎Let me try.
‎I already told you it's no use.
‎Damn it!
‎Hey, you can't throw at the same time…
‎Not a chance, you punks!
‎You'll never…
‎Finally.
‎Not a chance, you punks!
‎-Not a chance.
‎-Two more left.
‎-Stop!
‎-We've already exceeded the lethal dose.
‎A single shot is usually enough
‎to take down a cow.
‎Not a chance, you punks!
‎-Let's shoot all of them.
‎-That's enough.
‎Just use them all up!
‎Shoot.
‎Stop. That's enough.
‎Enough…
‎Enough already.
‎Don't do it.
‎Not… Not a chance, you punks.
‎Not a chance.
‎Not a chance…
‎Hey!
‎You can't just dump us out here!
‎That damn Mole Cricket.
‎He sure does hold a grudge, doesn't he?
‎He could've just let us go nicely.
‎This is obviously his way
‎of getting revenge.
‎They're SMD agents.
‎They shouldn't let personal feelings
‎get in the way.
‎Look at how they tossed the keys.
‎Those bastards.
‎I should report them
‎to the Human Rights Commission.
‎What am I, a dog?
‎Hey.
‎Get up.
‎Oh jeez.
‎Why are his eyes open? That's scary.
‎Looking at you now, I can see why
‎the SMD guys were so pissed off.
‎Undo them yourself, man.
‎Where are we anyway?
‎Where am I?
‎Han-soo?
‎Han-soo!
‎Was that just a dream?
‎BUS STOP
‎Excuse me.
‎-Yeah.
‎-Is anyone here?
‎Yeah?
‎Hello, ma'am.
‎Can I ask you a question?
‎Where exactly am I?
‎In a store.
‎Right, a store.
‎Are we far from Seoul?
‎-Some people say it's a little far.
‎-Right.
‎But everywhere in Korea
‎is just a hop, skip, and a jump away.
‎-Right.
‎-We're in Haenam.
‎Oh, Haenam.
‎Haenam?
‎Are you talking about the Haenam I know?
‎Not some neighborhood
‎near Seoul called Haenam,
‎but the actual Haenam
‎at the southernmost tip of Korea?
‎Why do you keep asking?
‎If you're not going to buy anything,
‎just go.
‎I want to watch TV.
‎Okay.
‎Haenam…
‎Haenam?
‎Haenam?!
‎He must be crazy.
‎Haenam?
‎They actually drove all the way here
‎just to dump us?
‎Just to screw us over?
‎Seriously?
‎Was it really necessary to go this far?!
‎-Damn you, Mole Rat!
‎-Han-soo!
‎Han-soo!
‎Oh jeez. Hey, Han-soo.
‎Hey, man!
‎Goodness gracious.
‎I'm so hungry
‎that I can't even take this off.
‎Why did you take off alone?
‎Your beard looks ridiculous.
‎You can't just leave me like that, man.
‎I don't have the money to get home.
‎Jeez, I'm hungry.
‎Does it look like I have money?
‎Don't lie.
‎Thank goodness I still have this.
‎Let's recharge and start walking.
‎Come on, let's walk.
‎We'll just walk.
‎Do you know where we are?
‎Who cares? We're somewhere in Korea.
‎All right.
‎Where are we?
‎Haenam.
‎What?
‎Stop messing with me.
‎Haenam?
‎Haenam?!
‎I apologize
‎on behalf of Hye-ri.
‎How about lunch
‎at the halfway house tomorrow?
‎-Great shot!
‎Nice.
‎Good one!
‎Goodness.
‎Thank you.
‎This way, sir.
‎Jeez, I can't find my swing today.
‎It's been too long.
‎Hey, bring us some beer.
‎Goodness.
‎Your game is a bit off too, Chairman Ju.
‎You don't seem well today.
‎Or are you not having fun playing with me?
‎Of course not.
‎I just had trouble sleeping last night.
‎I wonder why.
‎Oh, I see.
‎You must be worried about
‎welcoming our guests from the North.
‎What's there to worry about?
‎It's for the good of our country.
‎You're a true patriot, Chairman Ju.
‎Right.
‎Thanks to your resort being chosen
‎to host the North Korean delegation,
‎things have gotten
‎a lot easier for me too.
‎It's all thanks to you, sir.
‎Not at all.
‎Once they agree to establish
‎a free-trade zone at these talks,
‎Juhak Construction will break ground on…
‎I almost forgot.
‎You haven't heard from the police, right?
‎-Not yet.
‎-After you called me,
‎I looked into the matter on my end.
‎But the father and daughter you mentioned
‎don't exist in our country.
‎What I'm saying is that
‎they didn't die or emigrate.
‎There's no record of them to begin with.
‎If there's no victim,
‎then nothing happened.
‎That's what you say all the time, right?
‎That was a bad joke.
‎Hey, bring us two more beers.
‎Finally.
‎I'm almost there.
‎I can't give up now.
‎Da-bin…
‎Goodness, I'm sorry.
‎I'm sorry.
‎Get it together.
‎You're almost there.
‎Jin-cheol, you're almost home.
‎Da-bin…
‎Oh, my house.
‎I'm home.
‎How've you been?
‎Have you been well?
‎Thank you.
‎Thank you so much.
‎Thank you, Buddha. Thank you, God.
‎Da-bin.
‎I'm home.
‎I didn't know you'd left.
‎What?
‎Da-bin.
‎Do you have…
‎Do you have any idea
‎how long I've been gone?
‎Is that all you have to say?
‎Didn't you miss me?
‎Didn't you worry about me?
‎I LOVE MY DAUGHTER
‎That's so embarrassing!
‎Stop wearing that around!
‎Seriously!
‎Da-bin.
‎-Da-bin.
‎-Don't wear it!
‎-Wait.
‎-If you don't throw that away,
‎I'm going to run away from home.
‎But…
‎Da-bin!
‎You barely come home anyway.
‎You barely come home…
‎That's why I made this T-shirt.
‎I'm so hungry.
‎Da-bin.
‎What do you want for a late-night…
‎Honey.
‎You're back.
‎Honey, I missed you.
‎-You're home.
‎-Honey.
‎-Stay where you are.
‎-I'm hungry.
‎Don't come closer.
‎-Honey, give me some food.
‎-Stay away.
‎-I need a home-cooked meal.
‎-Goodness gracious!
‎-Hold on!
‎Honey!
‎Ji-yeong!
‎This isn't right!
‎I didn't walk all this way
‎to be treated like this…
‎I'll make you food after you shower.
‎Can I shower tomorrow?
‎INTERNATIONAL WATERS OFF THE WEST COAST
‎OF THE REPUBLIC OF KOREA
‎They'll be arriving shortly, so get ready.
‎Take them to the safe house
‎as soon as they arrive.
‎You're acting alone in this mission,
‎and the government
‎has nothing to do with it,
‎same as always.
‎We're heading out now.
‎Please fasten your seat belt.
‎It's been a while, 66.
‎Oh, that's right.
‎You were Number 73 in the North.
‎It's even better
‎seeing you here in the South.
‎How did you…
‎Why do you look so surprised?
‎I'm the one
‎who asked the South Korean authorities
‎to assign you to me.
‎When it comes to my safety,
‎it should be entrusted
‎to the finest warrior, right?
‎It was you?
‎The inter-Korean talks
‎are just around the corner,
‎and you sent an assassin?
‎Have you lost your mind?
‎I was trying to eliminate
‎a traitor to the regime.
‎Your unilateral actions
‎have disgraced the Party.
‎It appears you've all grown soft
‎from peacetime and playing it safe.
‎What a pathetic sight.
‎-What?
‎-What did you say?
‎I'm the director general of intelligence
‎in charge of operations against the South.
‎I make the call on eliminating traitors,
‎so don't get in my way.
‎Then shouldn't we eliminate
‎the traitor in our ranks first?
‎We received
‎some interesting intel recently.
‎About 20 years ago,
‎our operatives were annihilated
‎during an infiltration mission
‎to the South.
‎I was told a traitor in our ranks
‎leaked intel about the mission
‎to the South,
‎which led to the removal
‎of the former director general.
‎Who do you think that traitor is,
‎Comrade Director General?
‎I'll…
‎look into that.
‎There's no need.
‎The Party will investigate this matter.
‎What are you doing?
‎You can't go in there!
‎What do you think you're doing?!
‎How dare you barge into
‎the director general's room?
‎Ri Eung Ryeong.
‎You're under arrest for anti-Party
‎and counterrevolutionary crimes.
‎-What?
‎-Take him.
‎It'll be a long journey,
‎so I'll need my coat.
‎What are you waiting for?
‎Shouldn't you take this asylum seeker
‎to a safe place and protect him?
‎Come on now.
‎Don't look at me like that.
‎I'm a very important guest,
‎one that South Korean authorities
‎welcome with open arms.
‎Ri Eung Ryeong,
‎Director General of Intelligence
‎of the Korean People's Army.
‎The regime's ballistic missile information
‎is all in here.
‎Now, escort me safely.
‎Good work.
‎South Korean bastards sure don't know
‎how to treat a VIP, do they?
‎Are you here on vacation?
‎Hurry up and lead the way.
‎Please follow me.
‎At least you're finally out.
‎How's Min-ji?
‎She should be on her way to the SMD.
‎Let's go inside.
‎Where are we going?
‎Somewhere safe.
‎We're going to protect you,
‎-so don't worry too--
‎-What about my dad?
‎Where is he?
‎Is he okay?
‎What happened to him?
‎Please tell me.
‎I'm sorry, Min-ji.
‎We can't tell you anything right now.
‎He's alive.
‎You might see him again,
‎so hang in there for a few days.
‎Really?
‎When?
‎When can I see him again?
‎That depends on him.
‎My whole body aches,
‎so I need to get some good sleep.
‎Don't wake me up under any circumstances.
‎I'm talking about Ri Eung Ryeong.
‎Thanks to your comrades
‎getting annihilated,
‎the director general was cut loose,
‎and Ri Eung Ryeong swooped in to take it.
‎I'm okay. I promise.
‎I'll be brave and wait for you on my own.
‎If you complete this mission,
‎you'll become free again.
‎Your daughter will too.
‎You'll have new identities.
‎The head of the North Korean delegation
‎will stay on this floor.
‎We plan to clear and secure
‎the entire resort during their visit.
‎The facility isn't bad overall.
‎But why was this place chosen
‎for their accommodations?
‎It's rather far
‎from the venue for the talks.
‎This place best meets
‎the North's requirements.
‎They wanted it to be
‎as close to Imjingak as possible,
‎civilian access
‎had to be strictly prohibited,
‎and there couldn't be any buildings
‎taller than the accommodations
‎within a 2-km radius.
‎That's very particular.
‎Let's look at the suite.
‎This way, please.
‎These days,
‎I can hardly sleep because I'm so angry.
‎When I think about the humiliation
‎he put me through…
‎I'm telling you this because I'm prepared
‎to step down as vice minister.
‎You'll have a nice retirement gift
‎waiting for you.
‎Don't worry.
‎He's known as
‎Codename 66.
‎He's a tier-one wanted fugitive
‎and a former elite North Korean operative.
‎He kept his identity hidden
‎for a long time
‎before he stirred up major trouble
‎this time.
‎In exchange for a pardon,
‎he's been assigned to protect
‎a high-profile North Korean asylum seeker.
‎He's a major figure,
‎and with the high-level talks
‎just around the corner,
‎they're handling it discreetly.
‎So where is he right now?
‎I guess I really should retire.
‎That really hits the spot.
‎I was craving this like crazy
‎during my walk from Haenam.
‎Whoever invented beer
‎deserves a Nobel Prize, don't you think?
‎Nobel Prize in Alcohol, if you will.
‎Why are you so late?
‎I'm really curious, so I have to ask.
‎Is that the only outfit you own?
‎Want me to buy you one?
‎Yeah, buy me one.
‎Buy me one, you jerk.
‎I'm wearing this
‎because I came straight here
‎after handing out flyers.
‎Buy me one.
‎Flyers?
‎I'm about to become homeless.
‎Apparently, word got around among the moms
‎that I got into it
‎with the SMD guys at my studio,
‎and all the students quit.
‎They call me the violent master.
‎Man.
‎You're screwed, huh?
‎I'm screwed too.
‎The Cheonsan Unit guys barged in
‎and took all of my guns.
‎They took every last one of my boys.
‎You can't do this!
‎Where are you taking my kids?
‎Jackson!
‎Tommy!
‎I went through so much
‎to collect those guys.
‎Is the country allowed to confiscate
‎the property of an innocent citizen?
‎How is a person who owns guns in Korea
‎an innocent citizen?
‎It finally feels like my taxes
‎are being put to good use.
‎This is all because of Kim.
‎Damn it, Kim.
‎He's on his own from now on.
‎Rock and roll.
‎I wonder what happened to him.
‎Why do you worry about stuff like that?
‎Worrying about Kim and celebrities
‎is the biggest waste of time.
‎Ma'am, can we get
‎four more bottles of beer?
‎Hello, Violent Master speaking.
‎This is the Yujeong Substation.
‎Are you Sung Tae-hun's guardian?
‎Yes, I am. What happened?
‎Sorry?
‎How bad are the injuries?
‎Okay, I'll be right there.
‎I have to go.
‎What happened?
‎Tae-hun got into a fight with some kids
‎from another school.
‎Did he get beaten up badly?
‎No, he beat them up badly.
‎Man.
‎I guess that's the tough part
‎about having sons.
‎Daughters are definitely better.
‎I wonder what my daughter is up to.
‎The person you are trying to reach
‎is unavailable.
‎You will be redirected to voicemail…
‎She's fine.
‎She's doing just fine.
‎Let's drink!
‎I'm so lonely.
‎Thank you.
‎I'll make sure this never happens again.
‎-All right.
‎-Goodbye.
‎YUJEONG SUBSTATION
‎Say goodbye.
‎-I'm sorry.
‎-Bye, Mr. 18-against-1!
‎I'll be off then.
‎Have a good night.
‎Are you hurt?
‎No.
‎So you're fine, right?
‎Yes.
‎Then follow me.
‎Where to?
‎Put your headgear on.
‎PURE TAEKWONDO
‎You think you're the strongest person
‎in the world, don't you?
‎Well, I mean…
‎Not necessarily.
‎It certainly seems like it.
‎That's why you just throw punches first
‎without thinking, no?
‎Actually, I kick first.
‎Come on, Dad. I'm just kidding.
‎It was a joke.
‎It's my fault.
‎It's my fault as a father
‎for teaching you how to fight.
‎And it's my fault as a master
‎for not teaching you
‎discipline and moral integrity.
‎So starting right now,
‎I want you to hit me.
‎-What?
‎-I'll hit you too.
‎Dad, what's the matter with you?
‎Do you feel the pain
‎of the person getting hit?
‎No.
‎Not really.
‎Is that so?
‎Then let's continue until you do.
‎Father.
‎Father!
‎Does it hurt a lot?
‎That's the pain of the people
‎who were hit by you.
‎Got it?
‎You need to feel it too.
‎How dare you hit your dad?!
‎But you told me to.
‎You little jerk! Come here!
‎Get over here!
‎You told me to hit you!
‎Come here!
‎INPUT SIGNAL LOST
‎What's this?
‎One of them is out.
‎-A historic moment is about to unfold.
‎-Darn it.
‎Today, the official visit
‎of the high-level North Korean delegation
‎will take place here.
‎-You should come watch this too.
‎-As this could be a turning point‎…
‎You should witness the historic moment
‎of a bunch of commies
‎entering the free South Korea.
‎Hey, comrade.
‎Come sit down.
‎We should get along as fellow defectors.
‎I'm nothing like you.
‎Is that so?
‎How are we any different?
‎Hey.
‎Comrade, why don't you tell me?
‎I'm going to check the perimeter.
‎HIGH-LEVEL NORTH KOREAN DELEGATION
‎INCLUDES DIPLOMATIC OFFICIALS
‎Oh, that's right.
‎There is one difference.
‎I'm a defector
‎who came here of my own free will,
‎and you're a traitor
‎who got caught by the South
‎and begged for your life.
‎This can only be crossed
‎upon inter-Korean agreement, correct?
‎That's right.
‎It is sad to think that this single line
‎has kept our people divided
‎-for over half a century.
‎-Agreed.
‎The North Korean delegation
‎is finally crossing the bridge.
‎-Yes, this is truly a historic moment.
‎-The real game starts now.
‎-Twelve vehicles carrying the delegation
‎-Behave yourself if you want to live.
‎are heading towards Imjingak.
‎The North Korean delegation
‎will now proceed to Juhak Heritage,
‎which is 15 km away,
‎to attend a welcome banquet.
‎WE WELCOME THE NORTH KOREAN DELEGATION
‎TO JUHAK HERITAGE RESORT
‎Thank you for making
‎the long journey here.
‎Shall we go inside?
‎HIGH-LEVEL INTER-KOREAN TALKS
‎This is Chairman Ju Gang-chan,
‎who provided your accommodations.
‎He has been very eager to contribute
‎to the joint venture.
‎It's an honor to have you here.
‎I'm Ju Gang-chan.
‎HIGH-LEVEL INTER-KOREAN TALKS
‎NORTH KOREAN DELEGATION WELCOME BANQUET
‎-Shall we have a drink?
‎-Sure.
‎Where would you like to see
‎the free-trade zone?
‎Have you given any thought to a location?
‎PRIME MINISTER OF THE REPUBLIC OF KOREA
‎The talks haven't even started yet.
‎-Let's discuss that later.
‎-Right.
‎I guess I got a little ahead of myself.
‎I haven't even adjusted
‎to the time difference yet.
‎Time difference, you say?
‎That's a good one.
‎We just received intel from China.
‎They say Ri Eung Ryeong is in the South.
‎What's the matter?
‎You don't look well.
‎I'm fine.
‎Please continue your meal.
‎But…
‎It appears the South Koreans
‎have already secured him.
‎Those rat bastards.
‎-Track him down.
‎-Yes, sir.
‎Excuse me.
‎May I have a moment of your time?
‎Director General Ri Eung Ryeong.
‎You're looking for him, right?
‎How did you know?
‎The person he's with right now
‎is someone I'm very well acquainted with.
‎They call him 66.
‎Come to my room.
‎I only want one thing.
‎Let me be the one…
‎to finish him off.
‎Agent Kim.
‎SHUTDOWN CODE
‎CAM 10
‎What's going on?
‎We need to hurry.
‎They spotted us.
‎Go outside!
‎Over here!
‎Hold your fire.
‎We can't kill him.
‎Hurry!
‎After them!
‎Man, that was intense.
‎I think we pulled it off.
‎Jeez, it stinks.
‎Come out.
‎Those SMD comrades
‎are pretty impressive, aren't they?
‎I thought they were just here
‎to play servant,
‎but they turned out to be pretty useful.
‎Why are they trying to take you alive?
‎What do you mean?
‎They had plenty of chances.
‎But they didn't shoot at the car,
‎or at Sang-a, who was disguised as you.
‎That's because I have
‎the ballistic missile information--
‎But if they kill you,
‎that information will disappear too.
‎I think we lost them.
‎I think they stopped
‎now that we're closer to the city.
‎Right, it'd be a problem
‎if there are too many people.
‎They can't open fire or anything.
‎-I'll find out where Agent Kim is.
‎-Okay.
‎Sang-a.
‎How did it go?
‎We're on the move.
‎That's good to hear.
‎I'll report to the SMD
‎and secure a hideout.
‎No, don't.
‎-What?
‎-They found the safe house too quickly.
‎I think there's a mole.
‎Don't say anything to anyone
‎until I call you back.
‎Not the SMD,
‎and not General Jang.
‎What's wrong? What did he say?
‎It's nothing.
‎How did it go?
‎They had to pull back for now
‎because he fled into a civilian area.
‎What?
‎Is that what you're here to report?
‎You gave them orders
‎to capture Ri Eung Ryeong alive, so--
‎Tell them to track him down immediately!
‎Understood, sir.
‎What will you do after you track him down?
‎You're not going to cause a scene
‎in front of civilians
‎in broad daylight, are you?
‎I have a better idea.
‎I'm listening.
‎Why don't we stir things up even more?
‎Contact General Jang right now.
‎Yes, sir.
‎SPECIAL MISSIONS DIRECTORATE
‎Understood, sir.
‎Track Kim's location.
‎SEOUL STATION
‎Hey, isn't this Seoul?
‎Tell me what you're up to.
‎We're in the same boat
‎until the guys from the North leave.
‎I need to know what you're planning
‎so I can cooperate.
‎It's safer to stay in the city
‎during the day
‎since they can't move around as easily.
‎We'll relocate to the outskirts
‎when it gets dark.
‎Wait here.
‎ONCE A MARINE, ALWAYS A MARINE
‎Move in slowly.
‎Now turn left.
‎You see that?
‎That's how you open a door.
‎You don't kick it down.
‎What a waste of time.
‎There really is no reason
‎to worry about Kim.
‎It's been a while.
‎-Hey, you really--
‎-Drop it.
‎Take a seat.
‎You're here now, so it's all good.
‎What the hell?
‎Well, look who it is.
‎The regime's enemies.
‎You bastards used to be
‎such a pain in the ass back in the day.
‎But seeing you in the South
‎makes me feel a lot more secure.
‎Well, this is just great.
‎The three of you
‎could easily take on
‎an entire North Korean unit, right?
‎Is the country unified now?
‎What's this old man doing here?
‎This is your last mission, right?
‎General Jang already called.
‎He called and begged us to help you out,
‎but then he got turned down immediately.
‎By Han-soo, that is.
‎Right? You turned him down, remember?
‎You made the right call.
‎We'll leave once it gets dark.
‎Don't worry about us.
‎Have you eaten yet?
‎Good timing. I was getting hungry.
‎Hurry up and order.
‎I hear that it's very convenient
‎to order food delivery in the South.
‎You really can't read the room, can you?
‎Do you have South Korean money?
‎We're splitting the bill.
‎You think he can even afford it?
‎I'm only ordering for three.
‎Okay.
‎You want ‎jjajangmyeon‎, right?
‎Extra portion?
‎Hey, who is it?
‎The SMD.
‎Did you request backup?
‎Jeez, you're really something else.
‎Why did you bring them here?
‎What do you think you're doing?
‎Put down those guns right now!
‎Wow, I see we have two North Koreans here.
‎What is this, the unified Korean team?
‎You should get ready.
‎You'll be returning to your country.
‎What?
‎You Haenam Ass Cricket.
‎What are you doing?
‎What do you think?
‎I'm taking down the commies.
‎I never liked it from the start.
‎Not this mission
‎and not you.
‎Don't even think about it.
‎Don't forget…
‎who has your daughter.
‎Min-ji.
‎That little…
‎I thought you should say
‎your final goodbye to her.
‎You failed…
‎your mission.
‎AGENT KIM REACTIVATED
‎We're turning 66 and Ri Eung Ryeong
‎over to the North.
‎He'll do anything
‎to see his daughter again.
‎The condition is very simple.
‎Let's make a deal.
‎If we fail, you die.
‎-Then while you escape,
‎-Neighbors from up north!
‎-we'll keep them distracted.
‎-Rock and roll!
‎You took a hit,
‎so it's only right you return the favor.
‎Ready, sir.
‎If you so much as lay a finger on me,
‎your kids are dead.
‎Subtitle translation by: