[Natsuki Takemiya]
Huh?
What did you just say?
Let's break up.
Why?
[Natsuki's girlfriend, Sakura Nagai]
Because Natsuki, you don't really love me.
I do love you, Sakura.
You said this summer we'd go to the beach,
see fireworks, go to festivals...
Natsuki, you don't need me to be with you
to do all those things.
- That's not true.
- Bye.
Wait!
I'm sorry.
Just before summer break,
I got dumped by my girlfriend
of three months.
Why?
[MULTI MART]
[Refreshing Choco Mint]
- Here you go.
- Huh?
You're getting the usual, right, Natsuki?
Yeah. Thanks!
You're so consistent.
I'm having this.
Natsuki!
[Neighboring kindergartener, Riku Yanagi]
Riku?
Aren't you getting me ice cream?
Welcome!
- Why?
- You're crying.
No way! I wouldn't cry
over something like that.
Then why are you crying?
There are lots of things
you have to deal with as an adult.
Huh? Why? Why were you crying?
I got dumped.
What does "dumped" mean?
You'll understand someday.
I want to know now.
- It doesn't have to be now.
- Why not?
Hey, why not? Why not, why not?
"Getting dumped" means,
being told by someone you like
that they don't like you.
Huh?
Is that so? You sound like a teacher!
Really?
Cheer up, Natsuki.
Riku, what we talked about just now,
don't tell Grandpa.
Got it! Bye-bye.
Grandpa!
[Former musician, Eiichi Yanagi]
Did I say too much?
Not really.
I'm sorry.
It's just that the "why, why" questions
seemed endless.
You could at least say that in a proper way.
Anyway, try to cheer up.
I can't stand this.
I heard that Natsuki got dumped.
I told you not to tell!
Natsuki.
Yes?
[Nothing is permanent!]
Nothing is permanent!
Huh?
Everything is always in flux. Good luck!
Good luck!
[Episode 1]
Everything is always in flux.
[Everything is always in flux]
I guess nothing lasts forever, does it?
Did you come to comfort me?
[Takemiya family's dog, Rock]
You're so kind, Rock.
Sorry to keep you waiting,
[Natsuki's mother, Towako Takemiya]
I forgot the recipe.
- I left it behind.
- Okay.
- Towako, is this okay?
- Let me see.
- With this?
- Did you add a little of this?
Towako, we're out of olive oil.
Huh? Oh.
Yes?
Please wait a moment.
- Yes.
- Got it.
Okay.
[Cooking class student, Mayumi Tachibana]
Natsuki seems a bit down.
I wonder what's wrong?
[Cooking class student, Kaoru Kimijima]
- Excuse me.
- Hi.
Natsuki... I heard he got dumped.
- What?
Why did you have to say that?
- He got dumped?
- Natsuki?
By Sakura?
I don't know her name.
Wasn't she the soccer team's manager?
Yes, that's right. She lives
in the same apartment as Mr. Gotou.
Oh, the one on 2nd Street.
Excuse me, I can hear you guys
loud and clear here.
Sorry.
Well, it's because
you don't say anything, Natsuki.
You wouldn't report this
to my parents, right?
It's okay, Natsuki. You don't have to worry.
That's right, heartbreak is something
that everyone goes through.
We've been through it so many times.
I haven't, though.
Really? Is that so?
You'll find someone better, Natsuki.
That's right. There are lots of people who'd
be happy to know that you're single, Natsuki.
There are plenty.
- You think so?
- Yes, absolutely.
- They're already posting about it over there.
- No way!
- Going for a love hat-trick, maybe?
- Come on.
Mayumi, Kaoru,
you're both so sweet with Natsuki.
- That's because we're Natsuki's fandom, right?
- Right?
What's a fandom?
It means a group of fans.
I see.
I used to have one too.
Well, can I ask you something?
What is it?
My...
- What are my good qualities?
- Your looks.
- Great body.
- Yeah.
Thanks, but that's too much praise.
What about personality-wise?
You're kind. Friendly.
A pure boy.
Do you mean that I have
an unpretentious personality?
- Yeah, exactly.
- You're saying it yourself.
I'm home.
Welcome back.
The noisy one is back.
[Natsuki's sister, Riyo Takemiya]
- I'm home. - Welcome back.
- Welcome back.
Come on, come on in.
Excuse me for intruding.
[Riyo's boyfriend, Souta Kobayakawa]
This is Souta Kobayakawa.
My boyfriend.
- Welcome.
- Nice to meet you.
Oh, thanks for earlier.
- What? Does everyone know each other?
- No!
We ran into each other
at the convenience store earlier.
So could it be...
The high schooler crying
at the convenience store
- was Natsuki?
- Yes, exactly.
- Hang on a sec.
- Okay.
So, Towako, what shall we do today?
Oh, Mr. Yanagi,
aren't you enthusiastic today?
Thanks.
- So your name is Souta?
- Yes.
How did you get acquainted with Riyo?
A dating app?
No, we go to the same university.
Is that so? You're so talented.
Thank you.
He really is such an unlikable guy.
I knew you'd get dumped.
It was really only a matter of time.
Why?
Because you're so insensitive, Natsuki.
No, I'm actually quite sensitive.
People who are actually sensitive
don't say things like that.
- That's not true.
- See? You don't understand.
- Huh?
- You're nowhere near ready for romance.
- I don't want to hear that coming from you.
- Why not?
Because your relationships never last long.
What? Are you picking a fight?
You started it, didn't you?
- Look...
- Will everything be okay with them?
No need to worry.
It's always like this.
Right?
Is that so?
Unbelievable.
That's why you're like this.
Sorry, Rock.
We're not fighting.
Sorry.
You know, whenever someone's fighting,
Rock always steps in to mediate.
That's impressive.
- Do you want to go for a walk?
- Want to go for a walk with me?
Aren't you hot, Rock?
I see.
That's good.
I want to go to the beach.
I got dumped.
Let's go, Rock!
I'm home.
Natsuki, come here for a moment.
Did I do something wrong?
Well...
[Senior Year National College Choice Exam
(2nd Round) Individual Score Report]
Why is it here?
You said the mock exam results
weren't out yet, didn't you?
Well...
[Natsuki and Riyo's father, Gorou Takemiya]
I've never seen an E rating before.
Right? It's surprising.
But why is it here?
I went into your room
thinking I'd borrow a T-shirt,
and found that in the trash bin.
You shouldn't just pick it up.
Hiding it because
you thought you'd get scolded.
It's like you haven't matured at all
since elementary school.
You used to do that a lot.
You thought you'd hidden it well,
but actually, you hadn't.
- Rock's shocked too.
- No, that's not true.
You're on my side, right, Rock?
You scored 12 points on math.
Seriously, how did you manage
to get a score like that?
I really wonder.
Natsuki, are you planning
to take the entrance exam?
Yes, I want to take it.
I want to go to college.
- Which school?
- Which department?
I'm still thinking about it.
Well, there's still time.
That's unacceptable!
It's already July.
Just so you know,
college entrance exams aren't that easy.
I can do it if I try.
That's true. You're amazing
when you're focused, Natsuki.
Right?
But it doesn't last.
You quickly become
engrossed in chatting with Rock.
Riyo, why don't you teach him math?
- Absolutely not!
- No way!
Because she'll throw an eraser
the moment I don't understand something.
Because you immediately give up
when you don't understand something.
Your teaching methods are terrible.
Maybe it's just because you are stupid.
- I'm not stupid!
- Huh?
Anyway, Natsuki,
if you get an E rating on the next mock exam,
you can just give up on
the college entrance exam.
Huh?
Right.
That's right.
I'll do my best.
[Sakura: Yeah]
Natsuki has difficulty getting focused.
Maybe it's because he doesn't have
a clear goal for college, right?
Wanting to become
an aircraft engineer like you did,
I don't think many people
get into school with a clear goal like that.
But even Riyo, she chose to study languages.
That's true.
Wanting to travel the world
is also a valid goal.
Unlike the two of you,
I just wanted to leave the countryside,
so I went to a junior college.
I see.
So I can relate to Natsuki's feelings.
I have a feeling that he'll find something
if he goes to college.
Something...
[Math Workbook]
Nice job.
Who could that be?
[Takemiya]
Huh?
Hi.
But my sister isn't home.
Yeah, I know.
Then, did she forget something?
I've been asked to tutor.
Tutor? Tutor whom?
Me?
What?
Why did you just arrange that
without asking me?
Since Souta is good at math and science,
I thought he'd be a perfect tutor.
I find him a bit uncomfortable to be around,
and really unlikable.
Really unlikable?
That's funny. You've been reading
those Yankee comics, haven't you?
They're pretty popular
among people my age right now.
But don't worry,
even if you think he's unlikable now,
the more you get to know him,
the more you'll like him.
I don't need to like him.
Souta has tutoring experience,
and he's kind, so his teaching style is good.
I can't handle one-on-one lessons.
Natsuki, are you really okay
with how things are now?
If you go to university,
I don't think your life
will definitely change,
but university could still be a catalyst
for some kind of change.
That's true.
Oh, over here, over here!
Good job.
Make sure you do your best
to learn from Souta.
If you try to skip out,
I'll break your phone.
Are you not very good with dogs?
No, not at all.
Seems like he's afraid of you, Rock.
Even though you're such a good boy.
- I'm not scared...
- Go, Rock!
See? You are scared.
No, I was just surprised.
All right, Rock, that's enough for now.
What did Riyo say?
She said that if I skip our
tutoring sessions, she'd break my phone.
She seems like someone
who might actually do that.
So, let's just leave it at that for today.
Let's do this!
Where's your room, Natsuki?
Well, right here!
Please, right here.
I'm not about to let someone
I don't know into my room.
Just do what you can.
Well...
Or is it that you can't do any of this?
I see.
That means that this workbook
isn't suitable for you.
Then...
How about this?
Give it a try.
It's hard for me to work while being watched.
Then let me know when you're done.
All done.
Let me see.
Oh, so close.
You had it right up until here.
Seriously?
If you do this here, like this,
you'll get the correct answer.
I see.
Nice. All right, next...
Try this one.
Okay, that's all for today.
All done!
You did well.
Stop it.
Sorry, it's just a habit of mine
from teaching elementary school kids.
Don't lump me in with little kids!
By the way...
These are what I give to
elementary school students.
[Great job]
Do you want one?
Maybe.
You want it.
If I collect ten of these,
I get something, right?
Oh... Yeah. I'll think of something.
- Here.
- Thanks.
[Great job]
What's your first-choice school, Natsuki?
I haven't decided yet.
Just somewhere I can get in.
What's your first-choice school, Natsuki?
Somewhere I can get in.
You're not saying the same university as me?
No way. You're way smarter than me.
I see.
Natsuki?
Huh?
You don't have to have a first-choice school,
but you do need some motivation
for your entrance exams.
Something to keep pushing for.
Motivation, huh? Like what?
After you get into university,
the things you want to do.
I always wrote them down on paper
and kept them where I could always see.
It's kind of like a charm.
A charm.
Like eating a big steak if you pass,
or buying a pair of sneakers you want,
or walking on campus with someone you like.
You're not saying the same university as me?
Natsuki, you don't really love me.
Maybe, with someone you really like,
you'd want to walk on campus together, right?
Probably, right?
Natsuki, you don't need me to be with you
to do all those things.
I see.
Natsuki?
I really am insensitive and awful.
I don't know what you mean,
but you don't have to
put yourself down like that.
Hey.
How can you genuinely
fall in love with someone?
Huh?
That's a very philosophical question
all of a sudden.
I want to know the answer.
There's not just one right answer,
which makes it a difficult area.
So there is no single answer.
I think it might be different
for each person, you know?
I see.
I've decided!
Something you want to do?
This will be my good luck charm, okay?
What did you write?
[Genuinely falling in love]
I'm not telling you.
Come on.
I'll tell you when it comes true.
So, the tutoring,
we'll continue with it like this, right?
Yeah, it's kind of like that.
Please.
All right!
Together in the summer,
love and storminess came to our home.