(Love In Sync)
(Kim Myung Soo)
(Kang Min Ah)
(Love In Sync)
(All people, incidents, and backgrounds...)
(in this drama are fictitious and unrelated to reality.)
(Also, children and animals were filmed under production guidelines.)
Are you really going to close the clinic like this?
There is nothing I can do.
The result of the disciplinary appeal...
won't be out for at least three months.
What will you do in the meantime?
Travelling? Studying?
A side job.
Excuse me?
You know, right?
Having multiple jobs is popular these days.
What kind of side job will you do?
As a manager.
What?
This contract follows the standard manager contract.
Since it is a special situation, I added a few special clauses.
Please check them.
(Exclusive Management Contract)
It's not the place which does cheating,
so you don't need to feel distressed.
Did you read my mind again?
I clearly heard that the pay would be the best in the industry.
I also clearly heard that you had enough money.
I clearly stated the premise that it would not be as much as yours.
But unfortunately,
you would know that it's currently under provisional attachment.
The contract period is exactly three months.
Understood. By then,
I will have successfully returned,
and I won't ask you to stay for me.
Do you have anything else you want to add?
Just one thing.
Please keep it a secret to my family.
Especially to my sister.
That is not difficult,
but why are you so serious?
You are scaring the person receiving the emotional transference.
Indeed.
Here.
What is this?
Did you not read the special agreement?
It says that besides basic manager duties, you need...
to cover my acting skills through emotional transference.
I thought I just had to read the script and...
transfer my emotions to you. Did I understand wrongly?
Does this person think acting only requires emotions?
Emotions, vocalization, physical expression.
Sit here.
Okay.
Even if I receive emotions,
it is important for us to work together...
to give them my best performance, right?
- Yes. - If you make me...
feel the emotions, I will try to match...
the vocalization and physical expression.
Why do I have to do something like this?
Let's not think like that.
It's petty.
Don't just carelessly leak my emotions.
They're mine, after all.
The copyright of emotions belongs to me.
What can I do if I can't help hearing them?
We're doing scene 19, which is in the dance studio.
Hee Joo is packing her bag,
and Yeon Ji is still holding out, not changing her clothes.
If you smile to hide your emotions...
Hee Joo must be packing her things.
With a smile...
You should think if you're smiling because you're happy...
It says here, "with a smile."
- Smiling because you're happy... - What?
Me? Why?
I can't dance.
Well...
So, the male lead's emotion here...
is more like fear than hostility.
Do you understand?
- Yes. - Okay.
Then you understood the male lead's character.
By the way...
What is the range of emotional transference?
I mean, if we are at opposite ends of the Earth,
will emotional transference really work properly?
We need to know the possible range so that even if something urgent...
happens on set, we don't go beyond that distance.
Then let's test the range of emotional transference here.
Shall we start with 1 square, 10 meters?
Yes.
Two.
(Transferential in 10m Range)
Ten.
(Transferential)
Here.
I can't hear you.
(Non-transferential)
(The Maximum Transferential Distance: 50m)
That must be the limit.
That is right. It is not possible up to 60 meters.
It seems to be possible exactly up to 50 meters.
So, even on set, I should not be...
more than 50 meters away.
Then, you just should not be separated from me, Eun Hwan.
Was my peace of mind...
conveyed to you?
Come in.
- Ms. Yu Ji An. - Oh, yes.
I am not really keen on it, but...
our writer and director...
recommended you so much.
I said her acting is better than expected.
Just trust my judgment this one time. Okay?
I'll see if it is worth carrying...
that controversy. Let's see her acting.
I passed the audition.
I said I passed it.
Passed.
- I got cast. - Passed?
Did you pass the audition?
Gosh.
That's great. Congratulations.
To begin my work in earnest,
I guess I'll have to buy a van, right?
No. Should I hire a stylist first?
Which shop should I go to?
Why are you in such a hurry?
It's just one drama casting that's been confirmed.
Let's take it slow.
You don't know what you are talking about.
Soon, there will be magazine shoots, commercial deals,
and even drama appearance offers pouring in.
Excuse me?
How common is an entertainer with star power as hot as mine?
They might have hesitated...
because they were mindful of the public,
but now that the comeback signal has opened up. Then...
(Receive, Reject, Message)
- Hello, this is Cha Eun Hwan. - Are you the person...
in charge of Yu Ji An?
Gosh, yes.
I am Yu Ji An's manager.
I'm calling you to offer a photoshoot.
What?
A photoshoot?
Yes, good. The pose is good now.
Okay, good.
We will go with that.
Oh, that's pretty. Good.
Stay like that.
Oh, nice.
Now, look the other way.
(Kasavia, The Lens Which Makes Your Mellow Eyes)
I am so dumbfounded.
Do you think I am the same as before?
You are mistaken.
I am fine.
It is stranger that you are doing this.
You hurt my pride.
No, I'm saying this...
- because I misunderstood your... - There is no need for that.
Do I really have to come out in this freezing cold...
just to tell you that?
("Yu Ji An Stars In 'Season of God,' a New Drama Made By...")
("Writer Oh Jin Hee and Director Lee Dong Myeong")
A character like Hee Joo,
who always considers others' feelings first,
would not readily get angry in this situation.
So, even in that situation, she would unknowingly...
just let out an awkward laugh.
I see.
Can you understand that?
Yes.
But how do you know...
other people's emotions so well?
Because I am a psychological counsellor, after all?
Is that empathy innate?
Or is it something you can learn?
It is both innate and learned.
My father was...
that kind of person.
Always putting others before himself.
He passed away, right?
I can feel that you are sad.
Oh, yes.
It was an accident in elementary school.
That must have been hard.
I didn't even deserve it.
It was all because of me.
It was just out of curiosity.
I played with it out of curiosity and forgot.
Don't cause trouble while Dad is working.
Just give him the lottery ticket and leave.
Understood?
I said I got it.
I said there was no problem, so let's proceed.
Well, I'm telling you it's dangerous.
No, the space is already cramped, and there's no ventilation.
What if it rains later?
I know, I know.
It's not easy to stop filming here either.
Director.
Oh, well.
Eun Hwan and Song Hwan.
- What are you doing here? - Dad.
Yes.
What about your art competition?
I couldn't go because of him.
What are you doing there? Give it to him quickly.
What is it?
Eun Hwan was looking for toys in your room.
The director is looking for you.
Oh, really?
Dad will be right back.
Let's go.
Take care of Eun Hwan.
Dad, Dad.
Dad, take this.
No, Eun Hwan.
I went to give it to him.
Then the accident happened.
Since that day, I always thought.
If only I had not touched my father's respirator...
No, if only I...
If I had gone to give it to him alone...
If only I had not...
let go of my sister's hand at that moment,
all this misfortune...
would have avoided us.
I am the one who made the biggest mistake.
Why am I the only one...
who is fine?
But what right do I have to be struggling?
How dare I.
I am not that sad.
Why are you crying so much?
That emotional transference is malfunctioning.
Tomorrow is the first shoot,
and your eyes will be swollen because of me.
Shall I tell you...
a secret?
If you make eye contact with me like this,
the emotional transference stops.
It is mine.
How embarrassing.
A kiss? What did I do to him?
Should I just say it was a drunken mistake?
Oh, I only drink sparkling water.
What should I do?
Gosh, I don't care anymore.
I will just ignore it.
Good morning.
What was that?
That sound just now?
(To the actress with such controversy...)
("Planning to Come Back Despite of The Controversy?")
("Top Celebrity Yu Ji An's Moral Issue Is Reigniting")
All right, we will get ready.
All right.
Ready.
(Season of God)
Action.
- What is wrong with her? - Did she forget her lines?
Should we show her the script?
What is she doing?
Is she sick?
What's going on?
Nothing at all... No emotions are conveyed.
Yes, I am all ready.
Don't rush at the kids too obviously.
Give it some time.
Rich kids should do it sincerely, right?
Yes.
(The article has been posted.)
("Comeback Without Any Apology?")
("Yu Ji An's New Controversy About Deceiving The Public")
(You should have done at least the self-reflection.)
(Where is her conscience?)
What do you mean? We are not supporting the bullying issue.
Currently, the facts have not been confirmed.
Hey, call them over right now.
They are filming right now.
Is filming the problem?
The real problem is that it can't be aired.
Yes, I understand.
I am fine.
I think...
- I think I endured this much well. - Cut.
No, I said that's not the emotion.
Oh, come on. Seriously.
All right, again.
Ready, action.
I am fine.
- I think I endured this much well. - Cut.
Cut, cut.
All right, again.
You can do it.
Come on.
Oh, how many times has it been?
Is her condition not good?
Gosh. Why is she like that today?
- Let me go home. - All right.
Action.
What should I do?
What is it?
Gosh, is the heater wind this strong?
Why is the chair moving on its own?
Can we take a short break from filming?
Ji An had indigestion before she came.
It seems like she is not feeling well.
I think she will be fine after a short break.
No.
Director Lee, you need to come up for a moment.
We are filming right now.
- Gosh. - Well, that...
The director knew about her.
What?
Oh, this is really too much.
Gosh.
- You arrange that. - Okay.
We will take a short break from filming.
You read the script, and conveyed the emotions to me, right?
You didn't do it half-heartedly, right?
You did it properly, right?
I did it properly.
Just like we have always done.
Then why do I not feel any emotion?
No emotion was conveyed at all.
Could it be that the emotional transference...
has stopped now?
I think it has changed, not stopped.
It's like the person who conveys emotions...
and the person who receives them have been swapped.
So, like a reversal.
A reversal?
Simply put, now,
you can't feel my feelings,
but I'm starting to hear your feelings.
Today's filming has been cancelled.
You can go home.
Removed from the show?
I'm sorry. That's just how it turned out.
Even so, notifying her of being removed...
so suddenly is a bit much.
I wouldn't do this unless I had no choice.
Look at this.
After the article came out,
the message boards and phones...
Gosh.
The biggest headache is...
If she's not removed, the advertisers will pull all the PPL.
They say the product image will plummet.
But in this situation, how can I care Ji An?
It had to be a controversy about bullying.
I'm sorry, Ji An.
Director Lee, it's still just a controversy.
Nothing has been confirmed.
Understood.
I will quit.
- Ji An. - You don't need to worry...
because of me.
Ji An.
Gosh, even in this situation,
her pride is still there, I guess.
You should not leave like this.
Are you really going to quit?
Yu Ji An.
What if I don't?
Should I throw a tantrum?
Should I cry and beg?
If that had worked, I wouldn't have...
fallen into this abyss from the start.
You said you were desperate and had to make a comeback.
But you are giving up for this little thing?
They said they don't want me.
Everyone wants me to disappear from their sight.
What else can I do?
If you just quit like this, it will be like...
admitting to the controversy.
Are you okay with being known as an actress...
who abused your power for the rest of your life?
Everyone already thinks that now anyway.
So it is not like it would be any worse.
That is a lie.
Did you forget?
That your feelings are now...
being transferred to me.
Before you worry about my lack of manners,
you should fix your incompetent business sense, Mr. Kim.
If a group can disband just because one member leaves,
doesn't that mean you are all hopelessly incompetent?
But you don't have to worry about me.
I have no intention of being cast...
in your film, Director.
You should have lived a kinder life.
I was such a son of a gun.
Ji An, you need to be someone who doesn't...
have to be kind to other people.
That way, everyone in the world...
will be kind to you.
("Yu Ji An's Comeback Has Been Failed")
Anyway, she is so shameless.
It hasn't been that long since the controversy broke out,
and she is already returning?
She has no shame.
Do you go around talking about me so carelessly somewhere else?
Oh, no.
What is there to criticize about you?
When will the director be back?
Why? She is on a business trip.
When she comes back, please tell her something for me.
Tell her to change my hair stylist.
What?
Oh, is this also power abuse?
("Yu Ji An's Comeback Has Been Failed")
Are you sure you want to go this far?
No, your original plan was to use the power abuse controversy...
as an excuse to renegotiate the contract.
It was to scare Ji An and bring her down a peg...
before the renewal of the contract. Wasn't it?
I thought that was your intention.
But if you damage her image this much,
even for a star like Yu Ji An,
her marketability after her comeback won't be the same.
- Your question is my question. - Yes?
Get out.
I have to report something even though I can't understand it.
You are the CEO, but who are you reporting to?
I have someone who is...
Hey!
Who are you to pry so much?
Are you my stalking fan?
Get out.
I am sorry.
At that time, honestly,
there was nothing we could do to respond.
Mi Jeong posted about the power abuse, and...
articles poured out within minutes, as if they were waiting.
Gosh, public opinion was so heated that she was almost immediately...
removed from the show and went into self-reflection.
Such a large agency...
was so sloppy?
No, I don't understand their response method.
In such cases, don't they usually ascertain the truth first?
If it is false, they take legal action.
Even if it is true, they somehow reach...
an agreement with the victim and use media play to protect the celebrity.
Because a lot of money is involved.
Especially a top star like Ji An.
You are smart.
You are right.
But that is...
First, because Mi Jeong went into hiding after the revelation,
we couldn't make contact with her.
And since her contract had ended, it was legally ambiguous.
Contract ended?
Yes. Her contract...
with her current agency ended,
and before she met a new agency,
the incident happened during that period.
Gosh, so all the circumstances were just bad luck.
And above all...
What did they say?
Was it fabricated, right?
Did they say it was edited, right?
Technically, it doesn't seem like...
the video has been manipulated.
Knowing the video was the original,
she completely lost her will to fight.
She does not remember it, but the video exists.
She seemed to collapse at the thought that...
she might have actually done such a thing.
But actually, even though she acts tough,
she's a very tenderhearted person.
She's really not the type to do that, but how did it happen?
The woman named Mi Jeong, who claimed to be the victim,
is still out of contact?
Yes, that is what I heard.
I wonder what Ji An is doing right now.
She must be opening a sparkling water.
(Manager Cha)
I am just curious.
Do your family know you act like this?
Oh my, look at her.
- Are you crying? - You didn't see it, did you?
Yes, Ji An must be devastated.
It won't be easy for her to accept.
That's right.
Taking something away after giving it is the cruellest thing.
Being fired at the show? That's terrible.
The fact that there is someone seeing through my heart...
is more terrible than you think.
It took me some time to accept it too.
What the hell are you talking about?
Woof woof, happy now?
You crazy jerk.
So, Ji An did...
abuse her power, right?
Like that?
Gosh, I didn't think so.
How can someone with such an angelic face do that?
Hey, even though I was a former fan club president,
this power abuse is...
I can't defend it.
Just because the video wasn't manipulated,
it doesn't mean the whole situation is true, right?
Oh, look.
Most people in such an emotional outburst...
tend to lose control of their language.
So, when they get angry, they can't form structured sentences...
What? What's the problem?
As a friend, not a therapist,
explain it simply.
- Okay. - Yes.
So, when people get angry,
they just blurt out words randomly.
They say this and that.
Sometimes they repeat...
the same words. And the word order...
Their words are all jumbled and don't make sense.
You understand this much, right?
But even when she was angry, her sentence structure was perfect.
She didn't waste a single particle.
It's not easy to do that.
Especially for someone like Ji An,
who lacks emotional control.
Isn't it just because she's acted for a long time?
It might become a habit for her to speak as if reciting lines.
Exactly.
I am just curious.
Do your family know you act like this?
She's getting angry as if she's memorizing lines.
Are you crying?
Hey, why are you crying?
Why are you crying?
(Just And Kind Police For The Public)
Detective.
– How have you been? – How have you been, Mr. Cha?
I'm fine. I am sorry.
I have another shameless favour to ask.
If you ask something, it is always a go.
What is it this time?
Please find someone for me.
Someone?
(Shin Mi Jeong, Female, 26 years old)
Auntie said Mom would be here.
Why are you here?
Can I go to the playground?
– Playground? – Dad said I have to...
get Mom's permission from now on.
Did he?
Then, will you go with Dad when he comes later?
Why?
I always go to the playground alone.
I see.
Okay, then go ahead.
Don't be too late.
Yes, I will be back.
(Cheer up, Ji An. You got this!)
I believe in you.
You got this!
(Cheer up, Ji An. You got this!)
I have a mom too.
That is a lie.
You don't have a mom.
Yes, I do. I told you I have a mom.
If you have a mom, why do you play alone...
at the playground every day?
That is because my mom is...
My mom is...
That is because my mom is sick.
See, she is a liar.
She's an orphan.
I am not an orphan.
I am not a liar.
Hey, did you...
Hey.
You can't fight...
in this sacred playground, kids.
Who are you, ma'am?
Ma'am again?
– Hey, I am not a ma'am. – She is my mom.
Me?
Oh, right.
I am Ha Yul's mother.
Who bothered Ha Yul?
Was it you?
Little one, aren't you going home?
Hey, it's late.
If you don't go home again, your mother will worry herself...
to death, thinking you might have been in an accident.
My mother does not worry about me.
Because she does not love me.
No, there is no mother in the world...
who does not love her child.
You are lying.
Yes, that's right.
That's a lie.
There are mothers who love...
themselves more than their children.
Like someone.
Gosh.
It's okay.
I don't love my mom either.
You are lying too.
There are mothers in this world...
who don't love their children,
but there is no seven-year-old...
who does not love their mother.
I'm well aware of it.
I am depressed and want to cook.
Would you like to go to my place and eat tteokbokki?
Are you happy? Let's go.
You are cold, aren't you?
Come here. Let's go.
It's freezing.
Ha Yul.
It is Dad.
Ha Yul, let's eat tteokbokki next time.
Why? Can't we eat with Dad?
No, we can't. See you next time then.
Little kid next door.
Ha Yul, where did you go with the aunt next door?
We met at the playground.
Dad, did you fight with her?
No, why?
She ran away when she saw you.
Really?
Ha Yul, do you want to have dinner...
with Mom and the auntie today?
What about Dad?
Dad will have to go make up with her, right?
Ji An, please open the door.
Ji An. Ji An.
Why? What?
What?
Why aren't you answering your phone?
You made me worry.
You were worried about me?
If my celebrity is out of contact,
wouldn't the manager worry?
That's dereliction of duty.
Now that you've confirmed the celebrity is alive,
- you can go, Manager Cha. - What?
Are you angry right now?
No, I'm not angry.
I think you are. I can feel it.
I said I'm not angry.
Why have you been looking at me like that?
You are scaring me.
Shall I tell you a secret?
If you make eye contact with me like this,
the emotional transference stops.
You mean because of that?
To stop the emotional transference?
Gosh, that is really petty.
You just let my emotions transfer to you without permission,
but you are doing this...
because you are afraid your emotions will transfer?
So that is why you avoided my calls.
Since you realise it, will you please leave?
No, I won't.
Come on. Let me go in.
I knew this would happen.
How much did you drink?
Are you addicted to sparkling water?
It is none of your business.
I am not just anyone. I am your manager.
Cook for me.
Is this a restaurant? Why me?
You said you feel better...
when someone eats something delicious in front of you.
So what?
To make me feel better?
What nonsense.
Oh, hurry up.
Will just one cup of tea be enough?
I am used to it, so it is fine. In a disaster like this,
I must maintain my beauty.
I think you would be pretty even when you gain weight.
It is not a heart-fluttering moment, but a thud.
How can someone with such poor aesthetic taste...
be my manager? What should I do?
This way.
Let's say that's true.
So this is what it feels like for someone else to know my feelings.
So you know...
how uncomfortable I've been, right?
And you know what a great sacrifice it was for me...
to step up and be your manager despite that uncomfortableness.
You're making a big deal out of it.
You know I can hear everything.
And you must also know that...
I feel sorry for you.
Are you really going to...
give up to come back?
You chased me around, begging for help with your comeback.
I never chased you.
It was just an active proposal.
What?
They said they don't want me.
It's not about my acting skills.
They say they hate my very existence.
How can I make a comeback under that kind of reputation?
And I won't be able to make a comeback for a while.
If you try once like this,
and then get forced out by public opinion,
everyone plays it safe.
What if I help you make a comeback?
Within the three months as Ji An's manager,
I will do whatever it takes to help Ji An make a comeback.
And I will do that successfully.
Just as I believe in myself this much,
Ji An, you should also believe in yourself.
Nothing has been revealed yet.
(Leadership To Persuade Actors, Fans, And The Production Crew)
Right, there is only one reason we gather here.
To help Ji An make a successful comeback.
After strategising all night...
- Excuse me. - Yes, please speak.
But why do we have to help her?
Even Ha Yul and I.
Of course. Yes, we must help her.
- Yes, of course. - This will be fun.
How exciting.
Nice.
The first strategy...
for her comeback is...
Take one each.
Here.
Look.
(The Project For Yu Ji An's Comeback)
A donation to the paediatric cancer ward five years ago.
How did you find this?
It was anonymous.
I looked through Ji An's old records and...
even interviews of hospital staff.
You have quite a few donation records.
There are many things I don't even remember.
From now on, our job is to bring the...
buried truth to the surface.
We need to make people remember Ji An's true self,
which they had forgotten or didn't know well.
Shall we begin?
Through various social media,
creating natural buzz about Ji An...
and favourable public opinion is the first step...
to a successful comeback.
Ji An's good deeds should be naturally...
spread on social media.
Will public opinion really change?
We will make it change gradually.
What are all these problems after recruiting a wrong person?
Are you saying this video might not be true?
The video itself was not manipulated.
However, I will prove...
that the video does not show Yu Ji An's power abuse.
It will take more time to prove that,
but please trust me just this once.
All right.
If you are so confident,
let's go with the sole suspicion.
Honestly, if it hadn't been for you back then,
I would not have been able to continue working as a reporter.
It seems it is my turn to repay that debt.
Thank you.
I will make sure you never regret that choice.
Let's see.
That's right.
Yes. Last time, almost all of them were insults,
but now it's half and half.
Look.
There are not many posts speaking ill of her anymore.
Right?
Check this out.
(I hope she didn't do such things.)
(Moon Gyeong Sik)
So, Mr. Cha is...
Yu Ji An's new manager?
Yes, that is how it turned out.
No, how did that happen?
A counsellor and a manager don't seem related at all.
Well, if I were to explain, it's a...
bit of a long story.
I think it will be difficult.
Of course, I promised Mr. Cha,
and I'm also ambitious about the actress Yu Ji An.
But in this situation, even if I am the director,
it's hard to push it unilaterally.
You seem to have misunderstood something.
I'm not asking you to cast Ji An unconditionally...
with your authority as director.
Just give her one chance.
Let her audition for a supporting role.
An audition?
If Ji An earns the role through her skills at the audition,
please ensure she can film without being removed...
from the production, no matter what.
That is all I ask.
You want me to protect Yu Ji An with my authority?
If she passes with her skills,
I can take responsibility as the director.
Anyway, last time,
I let go of her too easily.
I also feel sorry for that.
But will Ji An audition for it?
She was the top star...
in Korea.
Are you crazy? Even though I dropped out, I was...
the original lead in that movie.
But you want me to audition for a supporting role?
No. I won't do it.
The drama you filmed before was also a supporting role.
That is true, but...
Then why do you think it's so embarrassing...
and hurt your pride about this?
It is not that I am embarrassed or hurt my pride.
It's that feeling. I can feel it.
Because the female lead of the movie is Han Yi Jin?
Is that so important?
It is important. Since my debut, I have never...
been pushed aside by her.
- Then, get pushed aside this time. - What?
Just because you haven't been pushed aside until now...
doesn't mean you never will be.
Look, Cha Eun Hwan.
You have to experience being pushed aside and rejected.
It will enrich your emotions.
You said you want to act well.
But how can you act well...
if you don't even know such emotions?
The role is good.
I may not know about movies, but I know emotions well.
Although it is a supporting role, there are many emotions...
that can be expressed. If I convey the emotions to you,
and Ji An expresses them well,
I think you can be recognised by the public for your acting skills.
You wanted to be a talented actress.
Okay.
This is as far as persuasion goes.
I won't force you.
How can I pass the audition without your emotional transference?
Did you forget? The reversal?
(The Note About The Days Of Emotional Transference)
There must be some kind of rule...
or reason we don't know about.
But there is nothing in common between the day...
the first emotional transference happened...
and the day the reversal happened.
The date, weather, time,
place, situation... Nothing is the same.
Why? Is there anything you can think of?
Oh, no.
Your face says otherwise.
What is it? Tell me.
Then listen without misunderstanding.
- A kiss. - What?
I said a kiss.
The day the emotional transference began and...
the day the reverse transference occurred,
the only thing we had in common was a kiss.
Gosh, that's not it.
What did you hear?
Where is this guy trying to pull a trick?
- No. - My choice of words...
was not that vulgar.
Then do I look like I would not think that?
You are lying in this urgent situation...
- to kiss me once. - Lying?
Do you think I am a fool?
Well,
I admit to the second one,
but we didn't kiss the first one.
I lost my mind for a moment, but did I lose my memory?
To forget that kiss.
We did. We kissed.
What?
When you collapsed.
I am sorry.
We did.
We kissed.
Then why did you run away when I kissed you?
No, I didn't do the first one on purpose.
I was just catching someone who was falling.
What should we do now?
Let's do it again then.
Let's do it. The kiss.
How can you suggest a kiss so easily?
You don't know my profession?
I am an actress.
I am famous for filming kiss scenes well.
All other male actors who filmed with me...
are known as kiss masters in the algorithm.
Yes, yes. You are so good at it.
You are amazing.
Of course. It means I am professional.
How can you be good at kiss scenes but not other acting?
So let's do it. The kiss. Like a business.
Why me? I am not an actor.
You are my manager.
For my acting career,
you will actively cooperate. Did you forget?
If you feel it is unfair, then you can...
think of it as practising acting together.
If you run away this time, you are dead.
It is work, just work.