[alarm beeps]
[theme music playing]
THIS IS A WORK OF FICTION
CHILD ACTORS WERE FILMED SAFELY
WITH SUPERVISION
[breezy music playing]
[panting]
[groaning]
Is it too much for you?
Yes.
This is why you're getting tired
so quickly.
This won't do.
Let's run together more often.
Give me a piggyback ride.
[scoffs]
[chuckles]
-[Ji-yoon grunts]
-[Si-woo sighs]
It's on you if my knees blow out.
Ah, that's right.
You said a fall at our age
can mean broken bones, right?
Yeah, but you're obviously
not planning to get down.
[sighs]
[romantic music plays]
[breezy music continues]
[phone buzzes]
[music fades]
He left his cell phone here.
[sighs]
All right, then.
I'll reach out to him later.
[Ji-yoon] No.
Don't do it, Cha Ji-yoon. Stop.
[sighs]
[taps feet]
Yeah, why should
I demean myself like that?
If I'm curious, I can just ask him. Hmm.
But I ordered a soda, didn't I?
[grunts]
Sugary drinks after a workout
will make you thirstier.
Drink water.
[scoffs] Could you please respect
my taste too?
I'll give in to everything else,
but not on your health.
Are you really that worried I'll get sick?
Yes.
-Then I couldn't put you--
-Then you couldn't put me to work?
[laughs]
Oh, your phone was ringing before.
It's Senior Associate Lee.
He says he'll be back at work next week.
-[breezy music playing]
-I hope everything gets sorted out
as soon as Mr. Lee comes back
to the office.
Let's stay hopeful.
He definitely has
the expertise to pull it off.
Hmm.
I'm a little jealous, though.
Why?
You'll always be my top pick,
Senior Associate Cha.
[chuckles]
When does practice finish today?
Hmm. Around 5:00.
-I'll come pick you up.
-Okay.
Okay, since you've rested enough,
wanna run again?
Again?
Winner gets ice cream.
[Ji-yoon yelps, chuckles]
EPISODE 8 - HELD BACK
BY MY PAST, STILL CLOCKING IN!
[music fades]
[moans]
Mmm!
I knew it. Nothing beats young radish.
Maybe just a touch more sesame oil?
Well, that's new.
You used to freak out
over having any kind of oil.
Your little sister will start focusing
on what she wants to do,
instead of what she shouldn't.
Hmm.
My little sister's all grown up.
[phone buzzes]
[Jae-in] Are you still mad at me?
[sighs]
-Why aren't you checking it?
-I don't need to.
-Is it Kim Goo-won?
-[groans] No!
Then why won't you check it? Let me see.
[groans] I said it's not him!
-"Hey No-ah, let's hang out."
-[groaning]
-Give it back. Geez.
-"Are you still mad at me?"
Just give it back already!
Why would you read my text? Seriously.
Who is this guy?
Some guy who's just
as shallow as they come.
[sighs]
YOON NO-AH
Seung-jun, am I shallow?
[inhales sharply]
You are a bit of a lightweight.
-Not physically.
-Why?
Someone called you shallow?
Mmm.
[exhales deeply]
You're not exactly shallow.
You've just never had to struggle
for anything.
What does that mean?
I mean that you've never had to pine
for anything.
For an item, looks, or talent.
Well, you're wrong.
I want something so bad it's killing me.
What?
Muscles?
-[sighs]
-[chuckles]
No-ah.
No-ah?
What's that?
[Ga-eul] I'm off.
Where are you going?
Wedding song practice.
You're singing at a wedding?
Mm-hmm.
I promised my college friends I'd do it,
so I want to keep my word.
Come on, you're only doing it
'cause you get to see Ji-yoon.
It's not like that.
It's over between us.
Dude, so then why were your eyes glued
to Ji-yoon the whole time, huh?
[scoffs]
Were they?
I should be more careful.
She must've felt uncomfortable.
Later.
[Jae-in] Bye.
See ya.
[sighs heavily]
Do I make No-ah uncomfortable too?
Hye-ji.
Hmm? What?
What is it?
Well, Mr. Kang and I…
we're dating.
You said you wouldn't.
You told me not to worry.
I know. It just turned out that way.
You said his ex-wife was your mentor.
You're gonna keep
running into her at work.
You really want to deal with that?
To be honest, it really bothers me.
Seeing them at work together
ruins my mood for no reason.
Think about what comes next, please.
Getting married means
becoming a family.
It's something
you haven't experienced yet.
It's a lot harder than you think,
and there'll be so much for you
to accept and understand.
I understand. I guess you're right.
You're smiling?
Hey…
I'm honestly so happy these days Hye-ji.
[groans]
[groans] You're driving me nuts.
[sighs] Whatever. Fine.
You've already made up your mind,
so I can't stop you now.
So please stop worrying so much,
and show me some support.
[sighs heavily]
Then just bring him to the wedding,
so I can at least see his face.
[chuckles]
You know, he's super good-looking.
I know.
How would you know that?
You only go for a pretty face.
-[scoffs]
-Geez!
Yeah, I do.
[sighs]
Ji-yoon!
Come with us.
We're all having dinner together.
I have plans.
Can't you just relax around me?
Like with Seung-jun.
Just treat me like an old college friend.
I told you that I--
Ji-yoon.
Mr. Kang.
We meet again.
I'm Kang Si-woo.
KANG SI-WOO
MANAGER
Oh, you're Ji-yoon's boss
from back then, right?
Hello.
But what brings you here?
Mr. Kang, let's go.
Ji-yoon.
-I didn't mean to keep it from you.
-[Si-woo] No.
I feel like I interrupted you two.
If you need to talk more, please go ahead.
Go on now. I'll wait here.
Then I'll just be a minute, okay?
Ji-yoon, what's going on? Why is he…
He's my boyfriend, Ga-eul.
What?
Since when, though?
It hasn't been long.
So I'd appreciate it
if you didn't contact me anymore, please.
[breathes deeply]
I'll see you at the wedding.
[sighs]
I regretted it immediately.
Thank you so much.
[peaceful music playing]
I'm really sorry I didn't tell you sooner.
He joined so suddenly.
And I didn't want you to worry
over nothing.
I saw Cho Ga-eul walking in
when I dropped you off last time.
And why didn't you say anything?
I was waiting for you
to bring it up first.
Oh.
So is this how it feels for you
when you see me with Ms. Choi
at the office?
How does it feel?
I know there's nothing between you two,
but it still bothers me.
Yeah.
Things between her and me ended
a very long time ago.
I don't have any feelings left for her.
I feel the same way.
I just hope he has a good life.
Right.
Oh, my friend, Hye-ji, told me
to bring you to her wedding.
Does that mean
I finally get to see your drum skills?
Yes.
Then I can't miss it.
So I better practice harder.
-[mellow music playing on speakers]
-[Hye-ji sighs]
Must've been a shock running into them.
It's weird, right?
Why did it never even occur to me that
there could be someone else
by Ji-yoon's side?
Well, that's because
you've never had to experience it.
She liked you all throughout college,
she wouldn't even look at anyone else.
[Hye-ji] Yeah, you have to accept it now.
-[sighs]
-[Seung-jun sighs]
Hey, back in college,
you knew how she felt,
so why did you pretend you didn't notice?
'Cause I wanted her to stay in my life.
I was scared that if we dated
and then broke up,
we'd lose our friendship.
Well,
I guess that's how things ended.
[Hye-ji sighs] Listen, Ga-eul,
you just need to keep thriving
like you are now.
That's what's best for Ji-yoon too.
She already has a lot on her mind,
so don't make things harder for her.
What do you mean?
Is something going on with her?
No.
I mean, we all have a lot on our minds.
You, me, and Seung-jun too.
No, not me.
What is it?
Tell me. Something's up with her, right?
No, no, no, no.
Come on, spill it!
Hello. I am the newest member
of the task force, Lee Young-hun.
-[Kee-tae] Nice to meet you.
-[Na-ri] Nice to meet you!
Welcome to the team, Mr. Lee.
Thanks.
We can skip the pleasantries.
Let's all get to work.
Should I book a meeting room?
No need. We'll be heading
to the product showroom today.
-[Na-ri] The product showroom?
-[Kee-tae] Let's go.
[futuristic music playing]
Whoa.
What is all this?
We'll start using this space
as our Home-AI Lab now.
This is where we'll test inter-device
connectivity and the AI experience.
[chuckling] No way.
It's nicer than my home.
[secretary] The President is here.
-President Han? Oh! Oh, gosh…
-[Na-ri stammers]
Hello.
[U-jin chuckles]
Seeing you freeze up
makes me feel like an unwelcome guest.
Please, you can relax.
-Yes, ma'am.
-[U-jin chuckles softly]
Uh…
Well, the upcoming demo
will be held right here
in the product showroom.
Given the nature of this project,
I felt a more private setting
would be appropriate,
which is why we chose this space.
Just trust Manager Kang Si-woo
and follow his lead.
[Kee-tae] Yes, ma'am.
[U-jin] So,
that being said,
be extra vigilant about security.
It would be a shame to have your hard work
stolen by someone else,
-wouldn't it?
-[Kee-tae] Yes, ma'am.
All right, then.
I'll look forward to a stellar demo.
Ah…
You did the new product release
presentation, right?
Yes. I'm Senior Associate Cha Ji-yoon.
All right.
I'm also counting on you for this demo.
Sure.
All right, then.
Thank you, ma'am.
[music fades]
You look like you have a lot of questions.
Is there anything else we don't know?
Yes.
So, you're going to keep
dropping surprises on us?
-Yes.
-But why?
Because, like the President said,
security is key.
[chuckles]
[Young-hun sighs]
[inhales sharply]
With this kind of approach,
even ten cameras
won't really work, you know?
Then what should we do?
Well, how about this?
-[dynamic music playing]
-Say you reach in with an ingredient
and pull your hand out empty.
Or the opposite, you reach in empty-handed
and bring it out holding an ingredient.
We can teach it these actions patterns
to track exactly what's coming in
and out of the refrigerator.
Then it can identify
the specific ingredient too, right?
Of course.
It'll recognize
whether you're putting in or taking out
a banana, an apple, or broccoli,
and it will even generate
an inventory list.
And it can also recommend
dishes and recipes
based on what's
in the refrigerator, right?
Yes.
Amazing.
However… Hmm…
We will probably have to switch
to a better camera.
Right.
-[Kee-tae] Mr. Young-hun.
-Yes?
Could you take a look at this?
Ah. Give me a moment.
Looks like things are going well.
Yes.
I think Mr. Young-hun
is totally our relief pitcher.
[chuckles]
[music fades]
[Ji-yoon] Someone has to crack this
once and for all.
It's basically a race to see
who lands on the moon first.
[sighs]
[door opens]
It's the new version. That's interesting.
[No-ah] You're here.
Oh, sit, sit, sit. Thank you.
-Have you been waiting long?
-[No-ah] Not at all.
What did you want to ask me?
It's about the remote-controlled
induction cooktop.
I would like to revisit it.
Well, I told you, we can't do that.
It is, uh, specifically written
into the regulations.
And what if we use a regulatory sandbox?
If the results are good,
it just might change the regulations.
-[upbeat music playing]
-That's right. A regulatory…
A SYSTEM GRANTING TEMPORARY EXEMPTIONS
FOR MARKET TESTING OF NEW TECHNOLOGY
Wait, how'd you come up with that? Wow.
I'm seeing you in a whole new light now.
Thank you, sir.
Apply for the regulatory sandbox.
And let's do this together.
Yes! [chuckles]
-[sighs]
-[phone buzzes]
[music fades]
[person] Is this No-ah's number?
I'm Jae-in's girlfriend.
We met the other day.
Can we meet?
[scoffs]
Wow.
I didn't see this twist coming at all.
-Oh, thank you.
-Sure.
Oh, yeah. Thanks.
-Yeah.
-[Young-hun] Here.
-Oh, thank you.
-[Kee-tae] Here you go, Mr. Lee.
[chuckles]
Hmm.
-Yeah, it is good. [chuckles]
-[Young-hun] Ah, thanks.
[Na-ri sighs]
This one's yours.
-Here you go.
-Ah, yes. Thank you.
[Na-ri] Thank you.
Thank you.
Mr. Kang, you've changed a lot
since I last saw you.
[server] Here's your order.
-[Kee-tae] Wow. It's kimchi stew.
-Looks delicious.
-[Kee-tae] Kimchi stew.
-Thank you.
[Kee-tae, Na-ri] Thank you!
-[Young-hun] Enjoy your meal.
-[Kee-tae] Enjoy your meal.
[sighs]
What? Wh-What is it?
-What did I do? What? Tell me.
-[awkward music playing]
-What?
-That wasn't you?
Was what?
Oh, I'm sorry, sir. Right. [clears throat]
Wow, Mr. Kang.
Uh, if you keep doing this…
[stammers]
[clears throat]
If you do this for me too,
that's true love right there.
-[chuckles]
The thing is,
you're not at that level yet.
-[Young-hun chuckles]
-I'm sorry, sir.
[task force members chuckling]
[Young-hun] Want me
to peel that apart for you?
[Kee-tae] Hey, now I'm offended.
-[chuckling] I'm just kidding.
-[Young-hun] All right.
You should know that I'm married.
-[Kee-tae] So am I.
-[Young-hun] Oh, I see.
[music ends]
And where is Mr. Lee?
R&D building.
-[elevator chimes]
-[sighs]
Uh, excuse me. We're getting off.
Excuse us, please.
[rock music playing]
Oh. Oh? Whoa, hey!
[task force members exclaiming]
-[gasps]
-[chuckles]
[gasps]
Looks like we're really
becoming a team, Mr. Kang!
Well, anyway,
I'll be eating alone tomorrow.
No! We were just starting to bond!
You have to eat with us.
-[chuckling]
-Aw. Come on, Mr. Kang!
[music ends]
-[tranquil music playing on speakers]
-[No-ah sighs]
Sorry for making you come all this way.
It's just that I'm still on the clock.
It's okay.
I'm the one who asked to see you.
Why did you want to see me?
Well, I could ask you the same thing.
Honestly, you could've
just ignored my text.
I figured meeting up
would at least ease your mind a bit.
I was the one who suggested we break up.
My ego took a hit
because it felt like Jae-in
didn't really like me that much.
I thought if I suggested we break up,
Jae-in would beg me to stay with him.
But he didn't do that.
Instead, he said,
"Okay. What can we do
if the feelings aren't there anymore?"
The feelings weren't there anymore.
So it wasn't Jae-in
who no longer had feelings?
He might look like a player,
but he's sincere deep down.
He might seem to do whatever he wants,
but he never lies.
[No-ah sighs]
I know it wasn't because of you.
To be honest, our relationship
was practically over a long time ago.
You came all this way
just to tell me that?
You could've just looked the other way,
you know?
The moment
I saw Jae-in run out after you that day,
I realized he must really like you.
I've never seen him do
anything like that before.
[emotional music playing]
Whether you accept him or not
is entirely up to you,
but I didn't want you
to get the wrong idea.
Besides, I have no intention
of going back with him.
And that's really all.
[exhales sharply]
[music fades]
I guess I'll just wait here a bit.
Huh? Why is he…
[dramatic music playing]
[sighs]
-[music continues]
-[no audible dialogue]
[exhales deeply]
[music fades]
[sighs]
I ran into some people from the office
on the way here.
And did you run into anyone also?
No.
Ah.
Thank goodness.
You said Seochon, right?
Yes.
You must've been really on edge,
forgetting your seat belt like this.
Yes, I guess I was.
Well, let's get going.
-[brother] ♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
-[clapping]
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
♪ Happy birthday, dear Mom ♪
[exclaims]
[gentle music playing on speakers]
Happy birthday, Mom.
Oh, and I bought the cake for you.
-Thank you, son. Thanks.
-[chuckles]
Lady Nam Hye-gyeong…
Happy birthday, Mom.
Thank you, honey.
I'll put it to good use.
Dad, you should say something too.
[Yeong-mook] Mm-hmm.
Happy birthday.
You're empty-handed yet again this year.
Well, I'm footing the bill.
We've done it this way every year.
It's nothing new.
-Mmm.
-[Yeong-mook] Mmm.
Eating a meal with you
is basically an annual event now.
[sighs, clears throat]
[server] Please, excuse me.
Enjoy your meal.
Wow, looks good.
-Doesn't it, Mom?
-Yes. Let's eat.
Yeah, eat up.
[combative music playing]
[Yeong-mook grunts]
-[music ends]
-What? You like sweet and sour pork.
[chuckles]
That was only what I craved
while I was pregnant
with Joon-su.
I like stir-fried seafood
and Chinese meatballs too.
[carousel turns]
[sighs]
[Yeong-mook sniffs]
But how would you know what I like anyway?
You might as well be a stranger.
I barely see you.
Hey, Mom.
If you have something to say, say it.
I'm listening.
Fine.
Well… [sighs]
When I kicked you up to the attic
in a fit of anger,
you went up there
like you'd been waiting for it.
You said you couldn't sleep.
So I did it so you could
sleep comfortably.
Then you could've come home early
instead of coming in late
and rustling around!
Do you honestly think I called you
because I was scared
of bugs or burglars?
Who on earth comes home
only to head right back out?
And you think buying dinner is enough?
How can you come empty-handed
this year again!
Okay, well…
Is there something that you want?
What is this?
MARRIAGE GRADUATION AGREEMENT
Mom, what is this?
I would like for you
to sign that document.
[Joon-su] Mom, you were serious
about graduating from marriage?
[Hye-gyeong] We stay legally married,
but we live our lives separately.
[Joon-su] Then how is that
any different from now?
[Hye-gyeong] It's different to me!
Read it over,
and then we'll go see a lawyer together.
This is still a contract,
so we should do it properly.
[sighs]
[sentimental music playing]
You should have gone home
with Mom, you know?
I still have work.
[groans] Even I wouldn't want
a stone statue like you.
You're so sweet to us,
so how can you do that to Mom?
Because I'm afraid.
Of what?
With your children, it's a bond
that's meant to last through time.
But the relationship with your spouse
can end at any moment.
True.
Plenty of people get married
and then divorced.
Well, to me…
it feels like walking through a minefield.
A minefield?
I'd say something without thinking,
and if it struck a nerve with your mom,
"Ah, I shouldn't bring that up again."
So I avoid that topic next time.
And then,
I'd struck another nerve and think,
"This is a mine too.
I should avoid this as well."
After doing everything I can to avoid it,
I ended up clamming up entirely.
I was just trying to keep
your mom's mind at ease,
and it turned into a habit.
So what now?
What are you going to do, Dad?
I don't think Mom was just saying that.
It's a separation, not a divorce.
That means I still have hope, right?
[groans]
Come on, Dad.
For someone who looks so pessimistic,
your thoughts are wildly optimistic.
Is that an insult or a compliment?
[scoffs]
[both chuckling]
Geez.
Well, for now,
I'll just do what your mom wants
and try to make it up to her.
I'll buy her flowers
and get her presents too.
Did she say she likes palbochae?
[chuckles] Mmm.
[inhales sharply]
Then I'll treat her to that too.
And you, Dad?
Have you ever wanted to separate from Mom
since you got married?
Sure, I have.
On days when being together
feels even lonelier
than if you were really alone,
I definitely do.
But my conclusion's always the same.
I can't live without your mother.
-[chuckles]
-[scoffs]
[automated voice]
Bus number 38 is arriving soon.
Mmm. I'm leaving. My bus is here now.
Okay. Get home safe.
Mmm.
Oh.
Is the cassette player working okay?
Yeah, it's working fine.
Good.
That guy sure does solid work.
[chuckles]
I'm off.
[Ji-yoon]
Why did you get divorced, Mr. Kang?
-[sentimental music continues]
-Was it because you were lonely?
Or because you made her lonely?
Whatever the reason,
is it something
that I'll be able to handle?
[sighs heavily]
[music fades]
Hold on, let me get this straight.
You're dating now?
You told me to.
But you said it'd be wrong.
Well, I guess I must like
Ms. Ji-yoon enough to cross that line.
[chuckles] "Ms. Ji-yoon"?
Why are you so surprised?
I'm just jealous, that's all.
[mellow music playing on speakers]
You like her that much?
Mmm.
She's just too good for me.
Hey. Why do you keep going on
about how it's wrong
and she's too good?
What, is being divorced a crime now?
No, it's not a crime,
but definitely a flaw.
She probably needed a lot more
contemplating and courage than I did.
When I think about that,
I can't afford to mess up.
I don't want to hurt her at all.
Kang Si-woo has finally become a man.
And what was I all this time?
A work machine.
[scoffs]
By the way, does Ms. Ji-yoon
know it's Soo-jin?
Mmm.
[Seong-min] You're right.
You really can't afford to mess this up.
[chuckles]
[intriguing music playing]
[sighs] No matter how much I look at it,
I can't get used to this new design.
[Kee-tae] It might seem strange at first,
but it gets prettier the more you look.
What're you, the proud doting father?
Of course.
My kid might have a bit of a giant head,
but it's super smart.
You can schedule it
for when you get off work,
and it'll handle all the washing
and drying entirely on its own.
It even sorts out
different fabric types effortlessly.
[sighs] And boy,
does my kid spin fast. Mmm.
Just take a short break,
and the whole wash-to-dry cycle is done.
Oh!
And our marketing angles,
that's all of them!
I don't really know
what the right call is.
[music fades]
What do you mean by that?
Functionality or aesthetics,
which one should come first?
There's no definitive standard.
We can only refine our instincts
through experience.
The problem is that
aesthetics is highly subjective.
Look how divided our opinions are
over one appliance.
Then you must prioritize
universal consumer-centric values.
If we're always led by consumers,
then when will we ever lead the market?
Oh! The refrigerator's here. [chuckles]
[dolly rattling]
Oh!
The screen is smaller,
just like Ms. Cha suggested.
-Yeah, and did you know about this?
-I didn't.
Did you know about it, Mr. Kang?
I knew the Design Team
held another meeting
right after hearing
your feedback, Ms. Cha.
Hmm. It looks brilliant design-wise too.
[Si-woo] Yes, it's much better
than the first mock-up.
-[phone beeps]
-[line rings]
Yes, Counselor.
Oh, well, if we leave now,
then we will arrive within an hour.
[chuckles]
I came to his shop
to make sure we go together.
Well, he's willing to hear
what graduating from marriage means.
Yes, yes, I'll do that.
Okay.
[exhales deeply]
-[thudding]
-[Yeong-mook groans]
-[screams]
-[groans]
[Hye-gyeong] Honey!
-Are you okay? Where does it hurt? Huh?
-[groans]
-[gasps]
-Is it your ankle?
-Your ankle? Huh?
-[groans]
[sighs]
[phone buzzing]
Hi, Dad.
What's up at this hour?
[Yeong-mook] Well,
I took a little tumble down the stairs.
What?
And are you hurt?
No.
Uh, it's just a hairline fracture,
so I got a cast.
Thing is, a customer's coming
to pick up something this evening.
So maybe you can go and hand it to them.
Then, on the door,
put a sign saying "Temporarily Closed."
Okay, sure. Don't worry about that.
Where are you right now?
Are you alone up in the attic?
Me? No.
Your mom says if I try to go up there,
I would need surgery.
[whispers] She was making
such a fuss about it.
So I'm down in the living room right now.
[tray slams]
[whimsical music playing]
Ji-yoon,
I'd probably be better off
crawling up there, don't you think?
No, Dad.
This is a blessing in disguise.
Turn a crisis into an opportunity?
Mmm.
Take this chance to rest up
and focus on Mom,
got it?
Okay.
[gasps, sighs]
Just my luck.
Of course my plan would backfire on me.
[screams]
[Yeong-mook sighs deeply]
[music ends]
Is everything okay with Mr. Cha?
Yes, he fractured his leg.
Is he all right?
Yes.
Uh, I need to stop by the store for him,
so I'll be leaving early today.
[sighs softly]
-Do--
-May I please come with you?
[tender music playing]
Yes.
I have something I'd like to ask you too.
All right. We can talk on the way.
[Si-woo inhales deeply]
[music continues]
You seem like you've been
in a bad mood all day.
Well, my boss is giving me a hard time.
[chuckles]
He must be a mean boss,
making things tough for you.
You had something to say.
Was it to trash-talk your boss?
Yes.
Vent all you want.
I'll join in with you on the trash talk.
Last night--
[phone ringing]
MANAGER CHOI SOO-JIN
[music fades]
[ringing continues]
You should take it.
[ringing stops]
Hello there, Ms. Choi Soo-jin?
[person] Si-woo.
Si-woo, how close are you?
[Soo-jin] Mom!
-Sorry. I'm hanging up now.
-[phone beeps]
CALL ENDED
[emotional music playing]
TEMPORARILY CLOSED
Was that Ms. Choi's mother?
-Yes.
-[music fades]
Is that why
you two were in your car last night?
The both of you looked
so serious in there,
it felt uncomfortable saying hello.
So I prodded you like a coward.
I get it.
It seems that I've lied to you.
Yes.
It bothered me all day long.
I kept wanting to ask
what you two talked about.
[sighs] But I had no idea
you'd still be in touch with her family.
It was the first time actually.
I guess I just have to
take your word for it, right?
[Si-woo sighs]
She has dementia.
[melancholic music playing]
In her mind, she's still
ten years in the past.
When we came back from the honeymoon,
she looked at my husband…
and asked me who he was.
Then she asked me where you were.
My mom's time is frozen
right at the moment after we got married.
I feel sorry for my husband.
If she could just see you one last time,
and say a final goodbye,
I think she'll finally
stop looking for you.
I know it's too much,
but it's just one last favor.
-[music continues]
-Why didn't you tell me from the start?
Because I said no.
And I didn't think
sharing such deeply personal stories
would be respectful
to the people involved.
That means if I hadn't gotten
in your car today,
I would've never known the truth.
That's what I had hoped.
Why?
Is that your idea
of being considerate to me?
Yes.
Even if I could go back in time,
I wouldn't tell you.
Because that's just my way
of showing you I care.
[sighs heavily]
I don't know.
I think I would've hated it anyway…
but I don't like knowing now either.
Whatever decision that I make,
trust me,
it will be for your sake.
Well, then please don't go.
-Okay.
-[music fades]
[emotional music playing]
[Ji-yoon] If you were me,
what would you have done?
If you were me…
[Si-woo] Then you should go and find out.
Once you stop running from it,
you'll understand what you really feel.
If you need to talk more, please go ahead.
I'll wait here.
[Ji-yoon] …you would have
told me to go, right?
You would've let me go,
saying you'd be waiting,
never wavering.
[panting]
But…
it's not that easy for me.
[sighs]
[phone buzzes]
Hello, Ji-yoon.
[sighs] You should go.
Ji-yoon.
The thing is, if you don't go,
she might reach out to you again.
I'd really hate that.
So go and settle it once and for all.
However,
there's no next time.
All right.
Thank you.
As for Hye-ji's wedding…
I'll make sure I'm not late.
Okay.
I'll be waiting for you.
[sighs]
You're really done with group blind dates?
Mm-hmm.
I'm tired of going there, trying to find
a safe middle ground with them.
And I hate saying things
I don't even mean too.
So what kind of person
do you want to date?
Hmm…
Someone I can be completely real with
and still feel truly safe.
[cries]
[Jae-in] Excuse me.
But I've fallen for your daughter
at first sight.
It's about riding the rolling waves
and having fun.
Doing what you want without being scared,
isn't that enjoying life?
You are Goo-won's cousin, right?
Hi, I'm Lee Jae-in.
No-ah's new best, uh…
boyfriend.
[in French] Would you be my boyfriend?
Oh, yes, I'd like that.
[chuckles]
[in English] What?
You've already met that person.
Haven't you?
[Na-ri sighs]
Have you been to that new restaurant
right out front?
No.
Apparently, it's amazing.
People line up all through lunch.
-Did you see the guy with the purple hair?
-Yeah, I did. He's so cute, it's crazy.
Do you think he has a girlfriend?
What is it?
[gasps]
Yikes.
I should get going.
-Bye.
-Uh.
Why did you suddenly cut off contact?
I thought I made you uncomfortable.
Then why show up out of nowhere now?
I couldn't bear it any longer.
[sighs]
Did you really mean it
when you asked me out?
Mmm.
I still can't trust you yet.
Let me earn your trust.
And you're too young.
I can't do anything about that.
I'm going to nag you
if you get hard to reach.
I don't want you getting friendly
with other girls either.
Yeah.
I'll stay easy to reach.
And I won't get close to any other girls.
[in French] Would you be my boyfriend?
[sighs]
[in English] Why aren't you answering?
Mmm.
Are you crying?
[Jae-in breathes shakily]
[gasps] Wh-Why are you crying?
I don't know. I'm just so happy.
I was super scared
I might never see you again.
[chuckles]
Look, if you don't respect me,
then I won't respect you either.
Mmm.
In a relationship,
I'm still going to put myself first.
[inhales sharply]
Mmm.
If your love fades away…
I will leave without forgiving you.
Mmm.
That's how I'll love you.
I hope you'll do the same for me.
Mmm.
[chuckles]
[joyful music playing]
[singing in French]
[song ends]
Oh. Uh. [chuckles]
-[in English] Hi.
-[Young-hun chuckles]
Mr. Lee, what brings you
into the office on the weekend?
Uh, I thought we should expand
the range of identifiable ingredients.
And you, you work weekends?
I have flexible working hours.
I left early yesterday to pick up my kids.
-[chuckles]
-Got your hands full, huh? [chuckles]
I'll just grab some files
and head to the product showroom.
-Carry on.
-Yeah. Good luck.
[Young-hun] Good luck.
Okay.
-[chuckles] Good luck.
-Right.
-[exclaims, laughs]
-[chuckles]
HANKUK UNIVERSITY START-UP "NIKKE"!
[ominous music playing]
KANG SI-WOO, LEE SEONG-MIN,
JIN SEUNG-HYEON, PARK BEOM-SU
LEE SEONG-MIN
[music fades]
CHECK THE ONE ITEM REMOVED
[sighs]
CHECK THE INGREDIENTS INSIDE
ADDED (1), REMOVED (0)
[chuckles] This is fun.
-[ominous music resumes]
-That may be a good enough software bug.
What should I tweak next?
Ah.
CHECK THE INGREDIENTS INSIDE
ADDED (1), REMOVED (0)
[music fades]
Mom.
Mom,
Si-woo's here.
[sighs, chuckles]
Si-woo!
Have you been well?
Yeah.
-Soo-jin.
-Hmm?
Go get Si-woo a nice warm cup of tea.
Sure.
Have a seat.
Thank you.
Why is your mom so hard to get a hold of?
Did something happen?
No, nothing happened.
Then what is it?
Did I upset her somehow?
You see, you kids need to start preparing
for your studies abroad.
Maybe she missed your call
because she's busy preparing all that.
[chuckles]
I still find it amazing.
Your mom and I promised to become in-laws
ever since you two were little kids,
and that's exactly what happened.
What are the odds that two best friends
from the same high school
would have children
raise them together, and later in life
walk down the aisle together
-as in-laws? [chuckles]
-[melancholic music playing]
It truly felt like a dream.
And Si-woo, darling, you looked so handso…
And who are you?
Mother?
I must really resemble…
your mother quite a lot.
[music ends]
-I'll see you later. Okay.
-Bye!
Hye-ji looks so beautiful today,
don't you think?
-Right?
-I can't wait for the wedding.
[Ji-yoon] Are you on your way?
[camera shutter clicking]
[Hye-ji] Ji-yoon.
PARK BEOM-SU
[inhales deeply, sighs]
[intriguing music playing]
-Huh?
-[Beom-su] College sweethearts,
married and studying abroad.
Are you enjoying life?
If you're jealous, you lose, but…
What's this?
[Soo-jin] Thank you.
-[music fades]
-It must've been hard for you to do this.
I guess she feels like she…
she owes you emotionally.
Mmm.
Once she moves into the care facility,
I won't need to contact you.
Though Mom will probably ask
about you. [chuckles]
I don't think I can do this again either.
I want to do right by the person
I'm seeing right now.
Oh, so you're seeing someone?
I had no idea.
Gosh, I'm sorry.
She'd be upset if she found out.
I told her earlier.
That's good.
Kang Si-woo, you've really changed.
The old you would've tried
to solve everything all on your own.
Is she the reason for this sudden change?
Mmm.
I wonder what kind of girl she is.
[footsteps running]
The woman you were with just collapsed!
[Soo-jin gasps]
You look so pretty.
Hey. Where's your boyfriend?
He's still not here?
Ah. He's running a little late.
Why?
Something came up at work.
Oh. Make sure I meet him before you leave.
Mmm.
[sighs] My friend,
you're officially a grown-up, huh?
-You're a mom…
-[exclaims]
…and now you're getting married too.
-This is crazy.
I'm actually super nervous right now.
This small wedding isn't small at all.
Uh-uh-uh.
[sighs] Maybe I shouldn't have
agreed to this.
What's this?
Lee Hye-ji is actually nervous?
[Hye-ji sighing]
Ji-yoon.
Mm-hmm?
I told Ga-eul about it the other day.
What?
Your boyfriend's past.
I'm sorry. I'm so, so sorry.
[groans] I made a terrible mistake.
It's okay.
It's the truth,
and I never intended to hide it anyway.
Hey, you have to stop
if it ever gets too hard, okay?
Please don't think about anyone else.
Focus on yourself.
Mmm. Okay.
But now, you're the star of the day,
so I'll say that to you.
-Hmm?
-Hye-ji,
your happiness always comes first.
Before your husband or your baby. Got it?
-[chuckles] Are you crying?
-No, I can't! [laughs]
-Hey, don't make me cry.
-[chuckles]
I can't cry already.
-[both laugh]
-[MC] Next up,
the bride's friends will be performing
the wedding song.
Please give them a warm round of applause.
-You said Ji-yoon's boyfriend was coming.
-I guess he's running late.
Because he's so busy, right?
[sighs]
Just pretend you don't know, will you?
[Ga-eul] Hye-ji,
-congrats on your wedding!
-[Seung-jun] Congrats, Hye-ji.
[slow music playing]
[Ga-eul, in Korean]
♪ Maybe, back at the very beginning ♪
♪ It was as if time had stopped ♪
♪ It was like you had walked ♪
♪ From a place in an unknown land ♪
♪ Like the welcome snow ♪
♪ At the dawn of early winter ♪
♪ That hurried into autumn ♪
♪ You came to me ♪
♪ Your bright smile ♪
♪ Is exactly what I love ♪
♪ But sometimes ♪
♪ The sad look I see in your eyes ♪
♪ Weighs on my heart ♪
♪ I want to know ♪
♪ Everything about you
Even the smallest things ♪
♪ But for some reason ♪
♪ You don't ever tell me ♪
♪ If that's the case ♪
♪ I will visit you in your dreams
When you're asleep at night ♪
♪ And quietly listen to your story ♪
♪ Quietly listen to ♪
♪ Your story ♪
[music fades]
[foot tapping]
[tense music playing]
[Young-sam, in English] Dig into
Kang Si-woo and find his weakness.
[sighs]
[Kee-tae] I need you to be
my secret confidante.
This is too heavy to keep to myself.
-[music fades]
-[Ga-eul] Ji-yoon!
What's wrong? Did something happen?
No, nothing.
Is it because of him?
What are you trying to do?
I just want you to be happy,
but right now you don't look happy at all.
I heard he was married once.
And to the mentor you always talked about.
So what?
You chose to leave me,
so choose someone better.
He'll only make your life difficult.
Why choose such a difficult path?
Hey, Cho Ga-eul.
I'm not trying to get back together.
I just…
I just want you to stop seeing him.
Hey, watch what you're saying.
You're being incredibly rude.
You're crossing the line, Mr. Cho Ga-eul.
You're not good enough for Ji-yoon.
She deserves
to be with someone much better.
That's for Ms. Ji-yoon to decide.
Besides, you have no right to say that.
I do have the right.
I am her…
longtime friend.
No.
If this is your idea of being friends,
I won't do it.
Never.
[breathes shakily]
[tender music playing]
You said you were
going to be here on time.
Yes, but something came up.
In that case,
you shouldn't have come at all.
You just ended up
hearing things
that you really didn't need to hear.
Don't worry, I'm fine.
It just upsets me that you had to
listen to such things.
[sighs] Today,
I saw an old photo of the two of you.
You were smiling so beautifully…
and I hated that.
I know it was a long time ago,
and it has nothing to do with me now,
but it still broke my heart.
Ji-yoon.
I thought that I would be able
to handle this well…
but I guess I was just fooling myself.
Please don't keep it to yourself
and imagine things.
Tell me whatever
is making it hard for you.
Yes.
It is hard.
Seeing you with Ms. Choi
having meetings at work,
or waiting for you
while you meet with her family,
and not being able to properly tell anyone
that we're together, is very difficult.
But the hardest part is
that I walked into all of this
knowing everything,
so I'm the only one to blame.
I'm sorry.
The choices I made
have ended up affecting you, Ji-yoon.
I'm deeply sorry about that.
[Ji-yoon] I can't believe
the first sorry I hear from Mr. Kang
is something like this.
I knew it.
-I just hate love.
-[sighs]
[music continues]
You're offering me an apology
for something I can't forgive.
But all you can give is forgiveness.
[inhales sharply]
[sighs]
It would've been better
to know nothing from the start.
If I hadn't known,
I could've just liked you
without any worries
and let it run its course.
[Ji-yoon] I hurt him with words
I should not say,
hoping that they cut
as painfully as possible
in that very moment.
The thing is that the more I like you,
the smaller I become,
you know what I mean?
Tell me, how come I have to bear
the weight of your past too?
[Ji-yoon] Back then, and even now,
the one who wears me out the most…
I'm sorry…
I'm sorry that
I'm not as strong as you are.
[Ji-yoon] …has always been…
me.
SPECIAL THANKS TO NAM KEE-AE
[tender music continues]
[Seong-min] You need to be
a little different than usual.
[Na-ri] Doesn't Mr. Kang look
totally handsome today?
Did you find the answer?
[Si-woo] I can't change the past,
but I can change the present,
don't you think?
Ah!
[Jae-in] Don't treat me like a child.
About the guy
who fixed my cassette player…
He's a good kid. And a lonely one too.
Can you tell me why you and Ms. Choi
decided to divorce?
[Kee-tae] There's something
between these two.
[Young-sam] Found it.
[Young-hun] Ruining the demo would…
[Ji-yoon] What on earth is all this?
Did someone hack the system?