Maybe I'm trying a little too hard.
But then again, this one feels too plain.
Wait, why am I overthinking?
Just be normal. Normal is fine!
I've never even thought
about what Kazumi likes before.
This doesn't look like
I'm trying too hard, right?
It's just Kazumi. Just Kazumi.
So there's nothing to worry about.
Himari!
Damn it. Why does Kazumi
have to look so cool?
Hey there.
- Did you wait for long?
- Not at all.
You look cute today.
Oh, thank you.
I heard the pasta here is famous.
This is their specialty.
Wow, it looks delicious.
What are you getting?
Let's see...
How about we order
different ones and share?
Or we could get a pizza too.
That sounds good.
Then let's do that.
Excuse me.
You know, now that I'm paying attention,
Kazumi's taking the lead so naturally.
I was so used to it
that I never even noticed.
Why is this happening?
He's shining.
Himari?
For some reason, I can barely eat my pasta.
My heart's racing.
Seriously? You're overthinking it.
Don't laugh at me!
I know it's the same old you that I'm with.
Sorry, sorry.
I see.
You make such cute faces on dates.
Could you stop teasing me?
I'm not teasing you.
I'm flirting.
Don't look at me.
It's beautiful!
You love plants and flowers, right, Himari?
I figured you could use some relaxation
after all the work stress.
You know your stuff.
I've known you for years, you know.
Hey, aren't you embarrassed saying that?
Not at all.
Come here.
It smells so nice here.
What? Is there something on my face?
You just look like you're having fun.
You're right. I haven't had
a day off like this in a while.
By the way, do you remember
that flower bed back in college?
Of course I do.
We talked about everything there, didn't we?
About assignments, the future...
Or when to add soy sauce
to your raw egg over rice.
Or asking me
to come on roller coasters with you
because no one else would.
No one else would ride
five or six times like you would.
And I'd listen to you vent for hours on end.
I don't just vent to anyone, you know.
But I think all of that
is why we're so close now.
Back then we were friends,
but now we're a couple.
Hey, aren't you embarrassed saying that?
Not at all.
Since we're here, let's take a photo.
Sure.
- Here?
- Yeah.
Is this angle good?
- Ready?
- Would you like me to take one for you?
Huh? Are you sure?
Of course.
- Thank you.
- Hold my bag, dear.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
Of course.
Leave it to me.
- Thank you very much.
- Thank you.
- Just hold still.
- Okay.
How's this?
Pull back a bit more,
- and try lowering the camera.
- Okay.
Like this? Oh, that looks nice.
- Okay, I'll take it now.
- Okay.
Say cheese.
How is it? Does it look okay?
- Oh, it looks great! Thank you so much.
- Thank you.
I'm so glad.
When I saw you two,
it reminded me of my husband and me
when we were young.
My heart fluttered.
Thank you.
We used to go on dates in places like this.
- Really?
- I see.
That was 30 years ago now.
30 years! You've been together all this time!
Thank you. I'm sure you two will be the same.
You make such a lovely couple.
- Thank you so much.
- Thank you.
Goodbye then.
She said we'll be like them.
Let's go.
Wow, it's so beautiful!
Yeah, the whole place is lit up.
Right?
Himari.
How did it feel,
spending the whole day together as lovers?
Right.
If you don't have an answer yet,
you can tell me later.
If it's hard to say face-to-face,
a text is fine too.
Take it at your own pace.
He's always been this way.
He always says what I want to hear,
and he always asks what I want to do.
I don't think this relationship will change
even if we become a couple.
I don't need to be afraid at all.
Kazumi.
I...
I like you too.
I want us to be together forever.
That means...
Yeah.
I'll be in your care.
Himari.
This is... so embarrassing.
Yeah.
Whatever you want me to do, I'll do it.
So can you tell me, for my sake?
I know he's saying this
so I'll be honest with him.
You really are adorable, Himari.
Kazumi's words melt my thoughts into a haze.
His every gesture fills my heart completely.
Kazumi makes faces like this too?
I can't tell where my body ends
and his begins,
or which part belongs to who.
We're completely entangled.
I never knew how fulfilling it was to give in
without any worries.
I don't know how to put
this feeling into words.
I feel like sprinting right now,
or clinging to her and crying.
I felt like I shouldn't touch her
with these dirty hands.
But that's not right.
If someone else is going to pluck you,
I'd rather you bloom by my side.
As long as I have you,
I don't need anything else in life.
Good morning, Himari.
Morning.
I feel kinda shy right now.
There are flowers here.
I never noticed.
This one's from that flower bed.
They let me have it,
and I've cared for it ever since.
I see.
So it's been by your side all this time, huh?
Now that I take a closer look,
his room is really tidy.
I've never seen this before.
His mom is so beautiful,
and his dad seems so refined.
His little brother is so cute too.
His mom.
[Mom]
I wonder what Kazumi's family is like.
Wait, am I going to be okay?
What if they tell me
I'm not good enough for Kazumi?
What's wrong?
Oh, nothing.
Your mom called earlier.
You should call her.
Thanks. But don't worry about it.
I'll call her later.
You should go shower too.
Sure, I'll take one then.
[Vextos]
Got a cold?
No, I'm fine.
Maybe I dressed too lightly yesterday
at Kazumi's place.
Shibasaki, are you dating Hojo?
Huh?
We're not dating!
We're just close.
Sure.
Phew, that was close! Did he believe me?
About Hojo...
I bet he's from a wealthy family.
Why's that?
Well, he just hasn't talked about them much.
He was born in Tokyo, I think.
Where in Tokyo?
That's...
Actually, I don't know.
I don't know where Kazumi was born,
what school he went to,
or what kind of kid he was...
You don't know?
I guess I never
really asked about that stuff.
After being friends for so long?
Hojo gets along with everyone,
but I guess he's got secrets, huh?
Well, I'm not sure.
I just feel some distance from him.
Like he's hiding his real self.
I don't think so, but...
Isn't your cold getting worse?
Huh?
It definitely is.
I'm fine, I'm fine.
I'll just...
Whoa!
You should lie down for a bit.
Follow me.
You're right.
Don't push yourself.
- Are you okay?
- I'm fine.
Sorry, Nihei...
I told Hojo too.
You don't seem like the type
to ask for a break yourself.
Thank you.
You're really kind, Nihei.
Huh?
Th-That's not true.
I'm really sorry for troubling you.
But you can go now.
Don't worry about it.
You always do
this kind of thing for everyone.
Sorry if I'm overstepping.
You're such a good person.
I'll go grab some water.
Just stay put and rest.
Thanks.
Nihei, how's Shibasaki doing?
She seems to have a fever.
She's sleeping now.
I see. Thanks.
I called a taxi. It should be here soon.
You can head back to work now.
Okay, thank you.
Thank you for looking out for her.
Not at all.
I heard you've been friends since college.
That's right.
We've known each other a long time now.
And yet, you haven't told her much
about yourself, huh?
What do you mean?
I'll be blunt.
I don't think how long
you've known someone really matters.
It's hard to get along with someone
if they have too many secrets.
If it were me, I'd tell her everything.
It's been a while
since I've had a fever this bad.
Yeah, I was in elementary school.
When I got sick,
my dad had to take time off work,
so I didn't want to be a bother,
and pretended I was fine on my own.
[Vextos]
Fukuoka?
Yes, the Fukuoka branch
needs extra help on short notice.
I was wondering if you could
take on the assignment.
You're good at controlling people,
aren't you, Hojo?
You make me sound like some kind of villain.
Your parents must be wonderful people too.
It's because I like you.
What?
Have I always been this jealous?