Okkhun Wisanwaja.
Get down!
(Bangkok, 2026)
What happened?
He lost control of his motorcycle,
crashing a pillar.
Now he’s unconscious,
unresponsive,
and has bruises on his chest.
Thank you.
What’s the vital signs?
The vital signs BP is 80/60.
O₂ Sat is 80%.
Start two IV lines.
Draw pre-op labs.
And prepare 4 PRC blood units.
Yes.
Sir.
He is unconscious.
Keep holding the ambu bag.
Prepare for intubation. Size 7.5.
He may have pneumothorax.
Prepare the ICD
and the ventilator.
Yes.
Follow up on the X-ray.
And get an ultrasound machine.
Yes.
The patient is ready.
Intubation completed.
O₂ Sat is 87%.
BP is 60/30.
Bleeding in the right chest cavity.
Oxygen at 100%.
Prepare for thoracotomy.
Blade.
O₂ Sat is 70%.
BP is 60/30.
Blood pressure is still dropping.
Extend the thoracotomy.
Continue suction.
Bleeding from the fractured right ribs.
It punctured the lung.
Clamp here.
Insert the chest tube.
Doctor, his heart has stopped.
Hold it there.
Start internal cardiac massage.
Adrenaline 1 milligram IV stat.
No heart rate.
Time of death.
11:50 p.m.
Doctor.
How is my son?
He’s safe now, right?
I’m sorry for your loss.
He lost a lot of blood.
His heart stopped during surgery.
Doctor.
This isn't true, right?
Could you try to save my son again?
Please try one more time, please.
I'm begging you.
Give it some thought.
I won't approve the resignation letter yet.
Just take a break for now.
Take as long as you need.
And come back when you’re ready.
Get plenty of rest.
We’ll always be waiting for you, Dr. Great.
Hi, P’O.
Oh, hey.
How have you been?
It's been a while.
Why do you look so stressed?
Something happened at the hospital.
Really?
The hospital?
Anything to drink?
I’ll have the usual.
The usual.
Okay.
As you wish.
Here.
Same as always.
Thank you.
Hey, guys.
There's just one table left.
You can go home first.
I’ll take care of the rest.
Go on, drive safely.
Hello?
Fine, fine.
I’ll get it for you.
Hey.
Can you watch the shop for a bit?
Only that table is left.
I’m going upstairs to get my wife’s stuff.
I'll leave it to you.
Alright.
Okay.
Sir.
The shop is closed.
None of my business.
Over there.
If you hadn’t read my boss’s fortune like that,
he wouldn’t have lost the auction.
It was not me.
It was your boss’s fate.
Hey!
Stop!
F*ck off!
Officer.
There’s a fight at my shop.
Please come right away.
It’s urgent.
Is this yours?
Yes, thank you.
Can I repay you by reading your fortune?
I’m pretty accurate.
I don’t believe in fortune telling.
The Death?
It’s obvious then.
It's not about death.
It means the change of fate.
Meeting and parting.
In other words,
you’re about to face...
the biggest change of your life.
What are you doing, Grandma?
Oh, my.
Why didn’t you go to work today?
Uh…
Is something wrong?
I’m on vacation leave.
I see.
That’s good.
You’ve been working hard for months.
It’s good to take a break.
You had to open a recipe book?
12 Thai Desserts.
By Thao Thong Kip Ma.
Who is that?
What a funny name.
Hey.
Don’t make fun of her.
She was the head of the royal dessert kitchen
for King Narai.
Her original name was Maria Guyomar.
But the name Thao Thong Kip Ma
was granted by King Narai.
And the desserts I make, thong yip, thong yod, and foi thong,
all came from her recipes.
Okay.
Khun Nualsipang.
Yes.
Enough for Thao Thong Kip Ma,
let’s talk about your health.
The doctor is here.
Hello, Grandma.
Hello.
Please come inside.
Sure.
I’m perfectly fine.
Why are you making such a fuss?
You refused to get a health checkup at the hospital,
so I asked the doctor to examine you here.
It’s a bit too much, though.
I’m going to check your blood pressure.
What’s your name?
It's Lalana.
You can call me Jeab.
Okay.
You and…
Great…
Are you two…?
-No.
-No, grandma.
We're not.
Oh.
Really?
Uh…
Your blood pressure is high.
Oh.
I was stressed earlier.
Normally, it’s not…
Khun Nualsipang.
Please don’t argue with the doctor.
Alright.
You need to take good care of yourself.
Thank you, dear.
Next week,
you have an X-ray appointment.
If you refuse to go,
I’ll ask Dr. Jeab
to park an X-ray truck right here.
This grandson!
Thank you.
Now I’ll draw some blood to check your sugar levels.
You eat a lot of sweets, right?
Will it hurt?
It’s like an ant bite.
Ant bites hurt, you know.
It won’t hurt.
(chanting)
Grandma.
Yes?
I’ll be right back.
What’s up, Rit?
Alright.
I’ll help out.
(Ayutthaya, year 1036 of Thai minor era)
Come live with us, Gaew.
Jumpa and I
will raise you
as if you were our own child.
Yes, sir.
You poor thing.
Losing your parents at such a young age.
Make yourself at home here.
Your mother,
Pudjeeb,
was my younger cousin.
And your father
was my fellow disciple.
You’re not a stranger to us.
Thank you very much.
Gaew.
That’s Si
and Dech,
your older cousins.
P’Si.
P’Dech.
Greetings.
Dech.
Si.
From now on,
Gaew...
is your younger brother.
Yes, sir.
Gaew.
Come here.
Dech, you too.
Hold out your hands.
From this day on,
you two are true friends.
Cherish this friendship
and don’t abandon each other.
May the gods watch over this friendship
and let it last
until the end of time.
Yay!
Woo!
Yam.
Is Thongkam ready for me?
Yes, Lord Gaew.
Today
is the day I get even with them.
Thongkam, go!
Go!
Damn it!
My rooster lost.
Then yours should die too!
Don’t you dare touch it!
Then I’ll touch you.
Hey!
Saen, you…!
Get up.
This way, my lord.
Stop this instant!
P’Dech, don't meddle!
This is between me, Wat, and Saen.
Stop while I’m still asking nicely.
You bastard.
What the hell?
Hey, hey.
You're being nosy, P’Dech.
Ow!
When we're home,
you’re in big trouble.
Go, go.
Get out.
Yam, we’re leaving!
Gaew.
I’m not done with you yet.
Haven’t you done enough?
You’re acting like a street thug.
You can’t speak to me like this!
Why can’t I?
Father told me to look after you.
You’re like my younger brother.
So when you do wrong,
I have to punish you!
I’m the son of a high lord.
What can you do to me?
How about a few lashes?
Let go.
Let go!
My lord!
My lord.
Ow!
Stop!
Someone as shameless as you
has to be punished.
If not you,
then your servant!
If you want to punish,
punish me!
Pin.
Let’s go back.
Yes, sir.
P’Muen crossed the line,
I’ll make him pay no matter what.
My lord.
Please don’t do anything bad.
Yam.
Get ready.
Tomorrow,
I heard that P’Muen...
is going to run an errand for Aunt Jumpa.
Go sink his boat.
Please don’t.
He can’t swim.
What if he falls
into the water?
P’Muen won’t die that easily.
I just want to teach him a lesson.
Someone will help him.
He humiliated me in front of Wat.
Pure disrespect!
I still don’t dare.
So I have to do it?
But…
Are you going on your own,
or do I have to kick you off?
I understand.
Go!
I’m going.
Huh?
What happened?
What is this?
My lady.
My lady!
Lady Jumpa fell into the water!
Hey, you!
My lady!
My lord.
It wasn’t Lord Dech on the boat.
It was...
Lady Jumpa.
What?
My lady.
Is anyone else still in the water?
Noi.
Noi disappeared.
She hasn’t come back up.
Noi?
Waen.
Search everywhere for her!
Yes, ma’am.
Khiao.
Yes?
Tell people at the house
to come help right now!
-Yes, ma’am.
-Go!
Juang.
Yes?
How are you?
I’m fine.
Stay strong.
Someone deliberately sank my boat!
You still haven’t found Noi yet?
No.
Maybe…
she’s already dead.
She might have drifted to shore.
The servants are searching.
We should hear something soon.
Prik.
Stop crying.
Noi will be fine.
Yes.
Duang.
Yes, sir.
Report this to the police.
My lord.
What is it, Waen?
I’m certain
this wasn’t an accident.
But...
someone intentionally
sank my lady’s boat.
Which bastard
dared to sink my boat?
My lord.
Why are you panicking?
Aren’t you scared?
Shut your mouth, Yam.
Why should I be scared?
You sank Aunt Jumpa’s boat.
Not me.
I didn’t do it.
I’m innocent.
Gaew.
What are you two doing here?
Uh…
I’m going to look for
the one who sank Aunt Jumpa’s boat.
I haven’t said that
my mother’s boat sank.
How did you know?
The servants are talking
about aunt’s boat sinking.
Yam.
What did you do?
Why are you soaking wet?
You ordered Yam to sink the boat,
didn’t you?
Tell us the truth.
Don’t try to hide it!
I didn’t do it!
Even if Yam did,
I don’t know anything.
If you didn’t give the order,
how would he dare?
Biting the hand that feeds you!
You
and your master
are wicked to the core!
Prik!
You wanted me dead,
but Noi took the fall instead.
She drowned,
no clue if she’s dead or alive.
Whip him!
Yes, ma’am.
Stop it, Prik!
P’Hora
Look at him.
Dech heard it clearly,
but he still refuses.
Not even a shred of gratitude,
after everything she's done for you.
Trying to kill her like this.
How rotten are you?!
Yam.
Go back!
Gaew.
Stop.
I said stop!
Look at that.
Walking away as he pleased.
He has no respect for us.
P’Hora,
you have to make him confess
that he is the culprit.
Calm down, Jumpa.
We don’t have proof
that Gaew did it.
Proof?
Do you have to find my dead body first
before it counts as proof?
He almost got me killed.
Luckily,
milady has accumulated great merit,
so she survived.
I understand you.
But we must be careful
not to let hatred blind us.
I can’t wait any longer.
Dech.
Help me.
Use the Krishna Kali spell on him!
Jumpa.
Dech.
I…
I don’t want to do this either.
But seeing Mother
almost die…
If I sit back and do nothing,
that would make me ungrateful.
And we all know that
Gaew did it without a doubt.
But if Gaew
didn’t do anything evil,
then this spell can’t harm him.
And he
will be cleared of all suspicion.
They’re using the Krishna Kali spell on me!
It seems P’Muen and I
can’t live under the same sky.
My lord.
Please don’t do evil.
I’m the son of a high lord!
How could I remain still
when they show me such contempt?
Yam.
I can’t breathe.
Help me.
Take this medicine, sir.
Medicine.
My lord.
-My lord!
-I can’t breathe!
Yam.
I don’t want to die!
Yes, Grandma.
I’m on my way home.
Alright, Great.
Drive safely.
I will.
See you soon.
I don’t want to die.
Yam.
I don’t want to die!
My lord!
My lord.
My lord! My lord!
Ah!
Help!
Please save Lord Gaew!
What’s wrong, Yam?
Please save Lord Gaew.
He’s not breathing anymore.
See?
Do you believe me now?
I was right.
Gaew is the culprit.
I’ll go see him.
Gaew.
No matter how much we hate each other,
I never wanted you to die.
Gaew.
What?
Just now, I…
I’m on my way home.
Alright, Great.
Drive safely.
I will.
See you soon.
What’s going on?
A Thai traditional house.
The scent of incense.
A man wearing Chong Kraben.
What’s happening?
Great.
Get a grip.
Calm down.
If I think logically,
this could be a hallucination
caused by post-traumatic stress.
Or am I in a coma?
That’s right!
The lightning strike!
My brain might lack oxygen.
Or…
is this an immersive hallucination?
Gaew, calm down.
Pull yourself together.
Am I dead?
The muscles are firm.
The body temperature is normal.
And the pulse is still beating.
If this isn’t a hallucination,
then is this person real?
You’re talking nonsense
like a lunatic.
My lord!
What the hell is going on?
Prik.
Didn’t he stop breathing?
Is he a ghost?
You’re alright.
Great.
Why is your dream so vivid?
Wake up already.
Wake up!
Wake up, Great!
What are you talking about?
I can’t make sense of what you’re saying.
What a weirdo.
Speaking weirdly.
You’re the weird one.
What’s wrong with you?
What the hell?
I can’t stay here.
Rit!