Thailand was such a dream.
It was awesome.
Let's go together next time.
Sounds great.
Pinky promise?
But first,
let's survive today's presentation.
Oh, right.
You ready?
Yeah.
Let's go.
Now, shall we start with Team 5's presentation?
Two, three...
- Hello.
Our team, unlike the others,
is a combination of Korean and Thai.
At first,
we couldn't understand each other at all.
It was hard to say the least.
As we were figuring out what to do,
we decided to take
our own experience into account...
and to focus on international marriage
between Korea and Thailand.
We'll now present
how we came to understand our differences
and made the decision to marry.
That American producer seems pretty talented.
- We might reach America after all.
- Could we go there?
Why not?
Let's do it.
[Next Stage Final Scores]
Director Park. Hurry up.
Yes, sir.
Interesting.
Oh, Hyun Jae.
Good evening, sir.
You're here early.
- Have a seat.
- Hello, sir.
I noticed that you and Soo An
weren't on the best of terms.
Did you two have a lovers' quarrel?
No, sir.
I've straightened myself out since then.
Really?
Good thinking, Hyun Jae.
That's what's best for Soo An as well.
Think of Jae Min.
That's what happens when there's a scandal.
With an idol, no less!
I'll keep that in mind, sir.
Hyun Jae, we're in the same boat.
If either of us screws up
and sinks this boat, we both drown.
If it works out, we both survive.
Got it?
Yes, sir, I do.
You even had to rig the chart for me.
[All recordings]
I was so clueless back then.
I'm sorry, sir.
Well, you know now. That's good enough.
Don't worry about PD Lee.
He only cares about money.
Director Park told me
that you've been working hard lately.
He really is.
Of course, as I should.
In fact, I'm going to work myself to death.
Good.
That kind of toughness...
is the only way you can survive in this field.
I don't cheap out on my people.
And I mean it.
And lastly,
Soo An, in this incident...
is the biggest victim.
Which is why I ask...
another opportunity be given to him.
All the punishment for this...
should be directed to me.
That is all.
Kim Hyun Jae, you bastard.
Why are you trying to take full responsibility?
Did you seriously think
I'd be happy about this?
I swear, I will hate you.
I'll hate you my whole life.
[Idol Survival Program Officials Prosecuted
CEO and officials accused of bribery]
[Kim Hyun Jae, Ex-member of Wakers,
Disappears After Exposing the Truth]
[One year later]
Cut. Good job, everyone.
Let's wrap this up.
Good work!
Tired?
I'm fine.
You must be more tired than I am.
I'm actually thrilled to see you on stage.
Considering what Unicorn did to you...
This is what you call a blessing in disguise.
Thanks to what happened to PNJS,
you can move on to greener pastures.
You'll receive better care,
and a better road to your debut.
Thank you.
For...
having my back even at my lowest.
Hyun Jae.
Where on earth are you?
I hated that you disappeared at first...
but now I just feel so sorry.
I've been thinking...
and realized that I know nothing about you.
So, after you left...
Bit by bit...
I've been figuring you out.
[Kim Hyun Jae's fan account]
[Waiting for his return!]
[cafe-class liked your post]
Are you ready?
Hello, everyone. Hello.
Thank you for waiting for me.
I hope I can make it up to you today.
Before we start, however...
I'm not here alone.
This person gave me so much strength.
Strength to return to you guys.
Hello, my name is Shin Jae Min.
I'm from Korea.
I'm currently learning Thai.
So bear with me.
Well, then.
Shall we?
You know what?
My wish came true.
Mine, too.
We've fought due to differences
in our background and culture.
But, through those experiences,
we learned about each other,
and grew closer than ever.
As our relationship grew,
we realized that nationality didn't matter.
Because we wanted to know each other,
we would study each other's languages,
or learn about each other's country.
Love has changed so much about us.
We grew mature through those times.
We learned that in marriage,
we share sadness and happiness.
We have to marry someone
whom we love so dearly,
so that we can stand strong
against any hardship thrown at us.
We also learned that two different people,
from different countries,
can become family through marriage.
In conclusion...
marriage, which allows two people
in love to spend their whole lives together...
is the greatest blessing
that one could possibly choose.
This is our humble opinion.
This was Team 5, and we are...
Khun.
And Shin Jae Min. Thank you.
Thank you.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
My apologies.
Just a minute.
What do you need?
An Americano.
It's hot out, isn't it?
This'll cool you down.
Actually, no.
I'll take it hot.
[Thank you for your love for Love Class 3]