This
It's not a dream, is it?
I can't believe it
How many years has it been?
- You suddenly disappeared when you said you were going to the U.S
in your second year of high school,
Is this the first time I've seen you in 5 years?
That's right
How have you been?
Did you come back from the United States?
Or did you come to Korea for a moment?
Changing my number and not using social media
Hey, where do you think you're going to cut off all contact like that?
Hey~ one at a time
The one who evaporated suddenly appears
Do you really look like that?
I am attending school in the United States
I'm going to Korea University as an exchange student this semester
Korea University?
Oh! I'm at Korea University!
Really?
Oh!
Why? Don't you believe it?
Um... I guess?
I studied hard when I was in my senior year of high school
I told you
I'm smart, but I didn't do it
If I do it, I will do it
Why, teacher?
The grades are out
Because of you, our class average has dropped, you know!
You're the last in our class, the very last!
What should I do with you?
Oh, what can I say this time?
I was startled because you called me out of the blue
What are you scared of, dude?
Do you have something to hide or what?
That's not it
Did the teacher call you?
Oh Jaewon, you're the bottom of our class starting today
- Kim Dojin, take responsibility for your grades and improve them
What?
Do-jin is moving his seat next to Jae-won from today
What? I don't like the front seat
Ah, why am I talking about Kim Do-jin?
If Kim Do-jin's grades improve, you'll have to do your special activities
Add extra time for self-study
I'll take care of the volunteer work too
- Please
Class president, top of the school
Oh, teacher
Study
It's time to rest
Solve this
Oh, really?
If you get the first question of level 1 right, I won't wake you up
A?
Yeah
You think I can't do
this either?
Hey
Can't you solve this too?
Oh, just wait a bit
It's not going to work out
if you see it that way
Are you stupid?
Hey
It's just that I didn't do it
I'm smart, you know?
If you can't even memorize formulas,
that's a problem with your intelligence
It's just that I didn't do it
I'll catch up soon
Hurry up and try it
Show me
I told you to wait
Where are you going?
You know the English assignment is due today, right?
Yes
Are you done?
Almost all
I didn't do it
Come here
Hold on a second
I'll quickly go to the snack shop
What snack shop?
Hurry up and follow me,
I'll be back really quickly
I have to do it by today
Oh, just one more minute
- Oh, seriously, just one more minute
I'll be back soon
Follow along when I speak nicely
Kim Do-jin
Oh, I see
What major are you in?
Me? Business management
Oh, I went to a good place
Hey, I also have a share in your acceptance to Korea University Business School
I acknowledge that
My grades have improved a lot since I partnered with you
It's nice to see you after a long time
I missed you