Of all things, why fall on your face?
It's fine
It's nothing. Why put medicine on it?
Hold still. You'll get a scar
Ah...
Such a baby
- I dreamt about Lee Jaewon again
- My first love at 18
- still hasn't faded
- Dojin
Hello
Oh... yeah...
Hi, Hayeon
It's Kim Hayeong
I know, Hayeong
We even sat next to each other
at the freshman welcome party
Not knowing my name is a bit harsh
Oh... I know
You didn't forget you promised to buy me drinks, right?
Huh?
Did I say that?
Wow
Don't tell me you forgot
Sorry
Hey,
you forget that, of all things?
You should buy her a drink today
Well...
Oh...
I guess you don't feel comfortable
having drinks alone with me
Then,
the three of us can drink together
I'm fine with that
What about you, Dojin?
Yeah, let's drink today
I'll come after class ends,
so go ahead and wait for me
Yay!
Hayeong, where's Minje?
Oh
Well...
He said something urgent came up, so he left first
Seriously, Kim Minje
We can just drink by ourselves
I already ordered some snacks, too
Oh,
okay
Take it easy
I can hold my drinks well
How much can you drink?
Um... two bottles?
But if I'm drinking with someone handsome,
maybe three!
I'll make it three for tonight
So how's school life?
Hmm
Being a college student is so great
Final year of high school was really tough
Yeah?
As a freshman, just keep having fun
I thought once I became a college student,
I'd drink, go clubbing, travel abroad,
and finally start dating
Those hopes helped me endure high school
So how many of those have you actually done?
Hmm...
Drinking, clubbing
Oh, I'm planning to travel abroad during break
I haven't dated anyone, either
That's surprising
I thought you'd be popular
I didn't say I wasn't
What's your ideal type?
- Hmm...
- Eyes with deep double eyelids
- A high nose bridge, and looks pretty
Someone cute, sincere, and is considerate
Someone who hands me tissues right when I need them,
and refills my water glass when it's empty
Someone warm and thoughtful like that
You seem to have a clear preference
What about you?
Me?
I don't really have a type
They say people with no type are the pickiest
Well... I'm not that picky
You know what they say about you?
They said they've never seen you date anyone
True...
Why can't I date, huh?
- I can't because I'm still holding onto my first love
- like an idiot...
I heard people asked you out a few times,
but you turned them all down
Where do you hear all this stuff?
Since you reject them all,
there's even a rumor you like guys
It's not... true, is it?
Hmm
I do like a handsome guy
- What he's up to,
- whether he's even alive,
- I just want to know how he's doing...
- I miss him
What... what time is it?
What?
I have a presentation today
I'm in trouble!
I'm sorry
- Are you okay?
Lee Jewon?
Kim Dojin?