Hello.
I'm Kim Hyun Jae.
Why are you calling so early?
Yeah.
Thanks for handling it.
Who's calling?
I terminated my contract with PNJS.
Why?
Because...
I wanted to be with you.
How did you pull that off?
It couldn't have been easy.
The termination fee.
I paid a freaking fortune.
Hyun Jae.
Yes.
You're going solo this time.
What?
Khun's walking out on us too,
and all we're left with is dead weight.
This group doesn't stand a chance.
It isn't fair to make you carry everyone.
I don't mind.
We've all worked hard together for months,
and Soo An and I have fans waiting for us.
Wouldn't debuting as a group make more sense?
"Make more sense?"
I thought you were smart enough
to keep business and pleasure separate.
I teamed you two up for better performance...
but apparently, you've been dating.
How many times did I tell you...
to be careful because everyone's watching?
Look at you.
You have no street smarts.
After watching what happened to Jae Min,
you still haven't learned anything?
How do I know you and Soo An
won't end up in a scandal too?
And you're still not thinking straight.
Were you spying on me this whole time?
You think I wanted to?
I can't let my product get damaged,
but you kept getting distracted,
so I had to take drastic measures.
The only reason you didn't end up like Jae Min
is because I've been protecting you.
Director Park.
[Kim Hyun Jae's Text Logs]
Hyun Jae,
I don't like doing this either,
but you keep acting recklessly.
What else am I supposed to do?
You brought this on yourself.
Sir.
I can't work like this.
You people put on a little makeup
and start thinking you're a big shot.
Hey, Kim Hyun Jae!
You thought you made it
because you're talented, didn't you?
Where is it?
Kim Hyun Jae.
Want to see something funny?
[Next Stage Final Scores]
See whose spot you took.
[6th Place, Yoon Soo An]
[7th Place, Kim Hyun Jae]
Congratulations, Kim Hyun Jae.
Congratulations, Hyun Jae.
Be grateful to the CEO, you hear me?
Fate works in mysterious ways, isn't that so?
You're pretty unfortunate.
Look, Hyun Jae.
Has listening to me ever hurt you?
No one cares about you as much as I do.
So from now on, just do what I tell you.
Got it?
Just look pretty, dance, and sing.
You don't even have to think. How easy is that?
As long as you do exactly what I say,
I'll give you the best of everything.
So...
Don't get any ideas.
Just keep doing what you've been doing.
Okay?
The song's so good, right?
Because I really want to debut
with you this time.
What happened?
What do you think?
Didn't you hear?
You knew about this, didn't you?
You knew!
This isn't new for us.
It's not the first time this has happened.
It's nice out.
After living somewhere this warm,
spending winter in Korea won't be easy.
Is it that cold?
Yeah. Really cold.
That's a problem.
It isn't all bad, though.
This keeps us warm.
Excuse me.
You're Khun, right?
Who are you?
I'm a longtime fan.
Your voice sounded familiar, so I glanced over,
but I was surprised to hear
a language I didn't recognize.
What language was that?
Korean.
I didn't know you spoke Korean.
You look happy.
I know you've retired,
but someday,
I'd love to hear you sing again.
Well...
I hope you're always this happy,
just like you are today.
Wait.
Yes?
Thank you.
Let's go.
Where?
I just thought of somewhere I want to go.
Make a wish too, Jae Min.
Wishes made here always come true.
Really?
Yeah.
Tourists don't really know about it,
but it's famous among locals.
What did you wish for?
It's a secret.
What about you?
Mine's a secret, too.
I'll tell you when it comes true.
This is the last time you'll see me on camera
as singer Kim Hyun Jae.
To all the fans who've shown me so much love,
thank you from the bottom of my heart.
We'll now present
how we came to understand our differences
and made the decision to marry.
Hyun Jae, where on earth are you?
Hyun Jae, we're in the same boat.
If either of us screws up
and sinks this boat, we both drown.
If it works out, we both survive.
[Next Stage Final Scores]
Got it?
Director Park. Hurry up.
Yes, sir.
Interesting.