♪The world keeps changing♪
♪A thousand years pass
in the blink of an eye♪
♪Shoulder to shoulder♪
♪We stand above the world♪
♪Our identities switch♪
♪The world turns upside down♪
♪Watch me♪
♪Stir up a storm♪
♪Let's time-travel, bro♪
♪Our blood is boiling♪
♪The genius emperor plots
with brilliant strategy♪
♪The slacker general
is unmatched in battle♪
♪The business world is in turmoil♪
♪The court is rife with intrigue♪
♪We will conquer the world♪
♪There's no escape for the traitors♪
=No Way! My Bro Is the Emperor=
=Episode 2=
♪The♪
♪Boundless♪
♪Horizon♪
♪Is♪
♪Where♪
♪My love♪
♪Lies♪
♪At the foot of the rolling hills♪
♪The flowers♪
♪Bloom♪
Why do you sing
exactly like my bro,
Xiao Dashuai?
You...
You know me?
Who are you?
I'm Fei!
Gu Fei?
How dare you
disrespect His Majesty!
Guards!
Seize him.
Back off.
Dismissed.
- Yes, Your Majesty.
Hurry up!
This is insane!
Bro,
why are you here?
You rascal!
You tested me.
Wait.
You threatened me.
I didn't.
You even tried to execute me.
I'm going to kill you.
Hold on.
Let's talk business first.
Go on.
Got
any cigarettes?
We both got sent back in time.
How come you look so cool?
Not bad yourself.
Way better than that smug face
you used to have.
When I got here three years ago,
I was just a frontier soldier,
getting baked by the sun every day.
How come you show up
and become the Emperor?
Jealous?
Why you?
You know nothing at all.
You were roasting on the frontier,
while I was walking on eggshells
in court.
For three years,
I've played cat and mouse with them,
plotted against them,
and sometimes
acted like a madman
to scare them.
Only then did I manage
to purge some of their spies.
There's still more to deal with.
Everything's finally in place.
After this palace examination,
we'll be able to
(Palace)
bring Xiao Ce down.
Over the years,
he has rooted out
(Sun Beiming)
every spy we planted
(Commander of the Imperial Guards of Jing)
by his side.
Then he has one to blame
when I make my move.
Don't worry, General Sun.
(Lu Ding, Vice Minister of War of Jing)
Our men have already made their move.
I remember I only traveled through time
after I died.
How did you get here?
On graduation day,
everyone got drunk.
You fell into the water,
and I jumped in to save you.
Are you nuts?
You can't swim,
and you jumped in to save me?
I guess I was.
I was drunk.
Maybe I wasn't thinking straight.
But I do think
life here isn't so bad.
I don't have to look for a job
and work like a corporate slave.
I finally get to show what I can do.
Maybe I can become
the greatest emperor.
Is that how smart students think?
Now you've got wealth
and beautiful women.
Go ahead and enjoy your life.
Isn't that good?
I can't.
If I sit on this throne,
I have to shoulder its responsibilities.
The treasury is empty.
The court is in turmoil.
General Sun commands the army
and is watching my every move.
If I do nothing,
you think only the people suffer?
I'd be killed by him in no time.
You know?
You died saving me
in our last life.
In this life,
I'll help you.
The court is a mess.
You should go back to the frontier.
My bro's the Emperor.
As long as you keep the throne,
my dream of living an easy life
will be within reach soon.
Until everything is under control,
I've got your back.
We'll be the strongest
political-business duo.
You'll be the Emperor
of the legitimate world.
I'll be the Emperor of the underworld.
Your Majesty!
Your Majesty,
this is bad!
Chancellor Hu is waiting outside.
He says
all the officials are rebelling.
What do you mean
by "all the officials are rebelling"?
You're saying
that General Sun Beijing
took advantage of everyone
being in Taiji Hall for an exam
and kidnapped their families?
Yes.
Did anyone know you
entered the palace to meet me?
Your Majesty,
(Hu Wenyuan, Grand Chancellor of Jing)
No one knows about it.
Good.
That puts the enemy in the open
and us in the shadows.
Tomorrow in court,
I'll pretend I know nothing
and stall for some time.
Right now,
we can't openly mobilize troops.
Gu Bei.
Take Eunuch Xu
and leave the palace immediately.
Find a chance
to rescue the officials' families.
Well...
I need one more person.
Any leads?
The people of the plains
grow up on horseback.
Reading hoofprints, catching
a horse's scent, and tracking people
are our specialties.
Just now, I followed the trail
from every official's residence.
It all leads here.
Xu,
what place is that?
The charity granary outside the city.
It's an open area.
Apart from the workers
guarding the granary,
hardly anyone goes there.
There are very few soldiers
stationed there.
It's a perfect place to hide captives.
General,
the officials have learned
that their families are missing.
They all understand
that they have to obey you
to keep their families safe.
There aren't many guards,
but they're
all General Sun's trusted men.
We can't charge in.
Of course not.
We'll need
this.
What is this?
Wow.
Amazing.
You actually built a bomb?
I've survived
countless assassination attempts
over the past three years.
If I hadn't made a few hidden weapons,
I'd have been dead long ago.
Watch this.
Mind you.
Don't cover your ears.
You stay here.
You're too old,
and you don't know martial arts.
Cover our retreat.
Right.
You'd only slow us down.
But I...
Your Majesty,
we have a memorial.
Speak.
Guanzhong has suffered
three months of drought.
Meanwhile, the Yellow River
has flooded again.
The Astronomical Bureau...
Get to the point.
Efficiency.
Since Your Majesty ascended the throne
six years ago,
you have favored the wicked
and alienated the worthy,
bringing corruption to the court
and ruin to the laws...
Enough.
Memorizing all that
must've taken a lot of effort.
Are you trying
to depose me?
Move.
Hurry.
♪Let's time-travel, bro♪
♪Our spirit soars to the skies♪
♪The brainy emperor plots the strategy♪
♪The slacker general leads the charge♪
♪Swords clash and warhorses thunder♪
♪Let the history judge our deeds♪
♪Our brotherhood is priceless♪
♪Peace across the land, carefree at last♪
♪Funny moments never stop♪
♪Silly blunders never cease♪
♪Yet through every up and down♪
♪We create miracles♪
♪From naive youths♪
♪To legendary heroes♪
♪This journey♪
♪Is one we'll be proud of♪
♪Let's time-travel, bro♪
♪Let's create♪
♪A legend of our own♪