♪The world keeps changing♪
♪A thousand years pass
in the blink of an eye♪
♪Shoulder to shoulder♪
♪We stand above the world♪
♪Our identities switch♪
♪The world turns upside down♪
♪Watch me♪
♪Stir up a storm♪
♪Let's time-travel, bro♪
♪Our blood is boiling♪
♪The genius emperor
plots with brilliant strategy♪
♪The slacker general
is unmatched in battle♪
♪The business
world is in turmoil♪
♪The court is
rife with intrigue♪
♪We will conquer the world♪
♪There's no escape
for the traitors♪
=No Way! My Bro Is the Emperor=
=Episode 3=
Officials,
what's decided here
concerns your entire families.
You should
think twice.
Uh.
What do we do?
Our families' lives are at stake.
Right.
General Sun is right.
I
second the motion.
I second the motion.
- I second the motion!
You all...
This is outrageous.
Obviously, this is the will
of the officials and the army.
If Your Majesty refuses...
Sun Beiming.
You think
kidnapping their families
will force me to abdicate?
This empire
isn't yours
for the taking.
(Bei Gu,)
(I'm betting my life on you.)
(If you don't back soon, it'll be over.)
If unrest breaks out in the army,
I'm afraid
I won't be able
to keep Your Majesty alive.
Is everything okay?
Who says I can't fight?
Grandfather!
Official Liu,
don't you think it's a coincidence?
I happened to be outside the palace
and found this child who had gotten lost.
Turns out
he's your grandson.
Boy,
is everyone in the family
fine?
Some bad guys wouldn't let us go home.
Thanks to this mister.
He chases them away.
Official Guo,
Official Gao,
Official Zhou.
Your families
asked me to pass along a message.
Head home early
when the court is dismissed.
Who do you think you are?
Who let you into the hall?
Guards!
Throw him out!
I'd like to see you try.
Gu Bei, step forward.
I hereby appoint you
Fourth-Rank Cavalry General.
You have the right to attend court.
Your Majesty,
General Sun's remarks
were an insult to the throne.
He deserves to die.
What are you waiting for?
Drag this traitor
out and execute him.
Wait.
General Sun
committed no crime.
Instead, he rendered a great service.
(No backup.)
(Can't take him on.)
(Got it.)
(Watch this.)
His Majesty is right.
If you want progress,
you need differing opinions.
You need people who dare to disagree.
General Sun's advice
was meant to spur His Majesty on,
to keep him vigilant
and never complacent.
It was not defiance.
General Gu has a point.
General Sun
risked his life to speak up.
He deserves a reward.
General Sun,
kneel and accept His Majesty's reward.
Has His Majesty's army arrived?
They will be here soon.
I
thank Your Majesty.
These two characters
are my expectations of you.
I bestow them upon you.
Ministers,
the court is dismissed.
(You moron.)
What is His Majesty
trying to get at?
(Honor Learning and Confucianism)
That was the perfect chance.
Why didn't you kill
that scoundrel?
His men are outside the palace.
If we fight head-on,
we'll lose.
We have to lie low for now.
We need a plan
to get rid of that Sun fellow
(Gu Nan, Consort of Jing)
Brother!
Brother, you've been on the frontier
for three years.
I finally get to see you again.
Bro...
ther?
(Right.)
(Gu Bei had a younger sister.)
Nan,
I've never amounted to much,
but I spent all my savings
to buy you this silver hairpin.
(After I left for the frontier,)
(she entered the palace as a consort.)
(I'll look after her)
(for the original Gu Bei.)
You're hitting on women in the palace?
Gu Nan.
Gu Bei.
My sister.
Princess Hulv,
you're a heroine.
Thanks to you for protecting me.
What reward do you want?
Emperor of Jing,
I followed Gu Bei here because I want
to take him back to the plains
to run Xiaoyao Pavilion.
Well...
Gu Bei is my trusted aide.
For now,
I can't let him leave.
How about this?
I'll fund
a Xiaoyao Pavilion branch in the plains.
How's that?
You'll pay
to open one for me?
That's a great deal.
With Xiaoyao Pavilion,
we can foster trade
between Jing and the plains.
The two nations can live in peace.
Wouldn't that be better?
We make money through trade
and enjoy ourselves at Xiaoyao Pavilion.
Who would want to go to war?
Deal.
I'll write to my father right away.
You.
Are you not coming back with me?
His Majesty wants me to stay.
I can't
defy an imperial decree.
If you're not coming back,
I'll stay.
First, I can learn
how to run Xiaoyao Pavilion.
Second, if you get into trouble again,
you'll need someone watching your back.
Hulv.
Thanks.
Don't mention it.
Granted.
Your Majesty, tonight...
Didn't I tell you?
No consorts.
Don't ask again.
Yes, Your Majesty.
You have so many beauties in the harem,
and you don't touch a single one.
What a waste of being Emperor.
Tell me,
who can you really trust?
Sure.
Eunuch Xu.
A few shadow guards.
And now you.
That's all?
Not even ten people.
And you're against over three thousand.
No wonder that old geezer is so cocky.
Gu Bei,
you don't have to
stay in this mess with me.
I'll let you leave tomorrow.
Go back to the frontier
and live an easy life.
Let me ask you.
What are we?
Father and son.
Grandfather and grandson.
Brothers.
That's right.
After all those years
you let me copy your final exams,
there's no way I'm leaving you now.
I've got a plan.
We...
He sure has gone all out
planting spies around me.
Now tell me.
Besides making grenades,
what else have you built?
♪Let's time-travel, bro♪
♪Our spirit soars to the skies♪
♪The brainy emperor plots the strategy♪
♪The slacker general leads the charge♪
♪Swords clash and warhorses thunder♪
♪Let the history judge our deeds♪
♪Our brotherhood is priceless♪
♪Peace across the land, carefree at last♪
♪Funny moments never stop♪
♪Silly blunders never cease♪
♪Yet through every up and down♪
♪We create miracles♪
♪From naive youths♪
♪To legendary heroes♪
♪This journey♪
♪Is one we'll be proud of♪
♪Let's time-travel, bro♪
♪Let's create♪
♪A legend of our own♪