♪The world keeps changing♪
♪A thousand years pass
in the blink of an eye♪
♪Shoulder to shoulder♪
♪We stand above the world♪
♪Our identities switch♪
♪The world turns upside down♪
♪Watch me♪
♪Stir up a storm♪
♪Let's time-travel, bro♪
♪Our blood is boiling♪
♪The genius emperor plots
with brilliant strategy♪
♪The slacker general
is unmatched in battle♪
♪The business world is in turmoil♪
♪The court is rife with intrigue♪
♪We will conquer the world♪
♪There's no escape for the traitors♪
=No Way! My Bro Is the Emperor=
=Episode 4=
Whoa.
Elite Agent?
I've been busy with state affairs,
so I haven't built much.
But I've drawn a lot of designs.
What's this?
Electromagnetic induction.
Using magnets to generate electricity.
If we could make electricity in ancient times,
it'd greatly boost productivity
and improve people's lives.
You've even got planes and cannons.
Tanks!
Bro,
are you planning to rule the world?
They're just sketches.
This era doesn't have the industry.
Everything we can make is here.
I'm not an inventor.
I'm not as smart as you.
But
I have another idea.
I'll take this.
Xiao, look at this.
(Imperial Palace)
The Imperial Palace
and the General's Residence
are separated by one street.
I'm planning to open a Xiaoyao Pavilion
on that street.
You want to use Xiaoyao Pavilion
as our base?
You caught on right away.
I've already picked the location.
Right here.
We can keep an eye on the palace,
and at the same time
monitor the General's Residence.
Sun Beiming's influence
runs deep in the court.
We can't rush this.
That's exactly the reason
We'll make money
while exposing him.
With one hand, I'll cut off his money.
With the other, I'll take his army.
Those history classes
actually paid off.
What are you writing now?
Getting some work done.
Tonight,
I'll finish the business plan
for Xiaoyao Pavilion.
Forget it.
Relax, please.
Just enjoy tonight.
Eat and drink
all we want.
Tomorrow morning,
you and I will leave the palace
to buy the land.
(Yunqi Restaurant)
Let's go.
There's no need
for Your Majesty
to handle this personally.
Watch me.
(Yunqi Restaurant)
I already paid the deposit.
How can you sell it to someone else?
You have no power.
They have powerful people backing them.
In the capital, connections are everything.
It's all about who backs you.
Cause any more trouble,
and I'll throw you in prison.
Just wait.
I'll go talk to them.
What's going on?
Didn't you tell them who you are?
I did.
Every country has its laws.
Every trade has its rules.
According to Jing's Commercial Code,
anyone who breaks a contract
is fined fifty taels
and given twenty strokes.
Who are you supposed to be?
(Token)
This is the Imperial Dragon Token.
I
am the Emperor.
See these?
(Token)
This one is from the Imperial Guards.
Court of Judicial Review.
Ministry of Justice.
(Imperial Palace Token)
Yours is the least convincing.
Throw him out.
Wait!
Out of the way!
Sir.
This way, please.
Lu Ding?
Do you know him?
Vice Minister of War.
One of Sun Beiming's men.
What's he doing here?
Don't tell me he's the buyer.
That snake went back on his word.
Pay for it.
Buy the whole street.
I have no money.
The court is corrupt.
I spent everything from my private treasury
helping Hulv open Xiaoyao Pavilion.
Fine.
I'll transfer funds
from the frontier headquarters.
There has to be a way.
Still, it can't solve our problem here.
Gu Bei.
I have a younger sister.
Before our late father passed,
he entrusted
Princess Xiao Ling with the treasury.
All of Jing's wealth is in her hands.
Marry your sister?
You want me as your brother-in-law?
Trying to pull rank on me?
That's not it.
Sun Beiming has repeatedly petitioned
for Xiao Ling to marry
into the Sun family.
If he gets her dowry,
he'll surely raise a private army.
Then neither of us
will make it out alive.
But I've never even met her.
You can't just arrange my marriage.
What's she like?
How's her personality?
My sister
is fine in every way.
It's just that
she's quite into some arts.
(Xiao Ling'er, Princess of Jing)
Just a little more.
Couldn't you have held on a bit longer?
Your standards are too high.
This painting is perfect.
Nan.
It's been so long since you visited.
I'm here today
to congratulate you on your engagement.
My engagement?
How come I know nothing about it?
His Majesty intends
to marry you to my brother,
Gu Bei.
Gu Bei?
The one who
caused a scene
at court?
That frontier commander?
I'm not marrying
some brute
who only knows how to wield a sword.
Where's my brother?
Eunuch Xu said
His Majesty and my brother
went incognito to inspect the city.
It's dangerous outside!
My brother has never
done anything
so reckless before.
It must be Gu Bei
who influenced him.
Right?
I'm going to find him.
Ling'er.
Take this to Lu Ding.
I'm sure he'll come.
Where is he?
Over there.
Tell me.
Did only the two of them come?
No guards?
Yes, sir.
It's just the two of them.
Guards! Someone's impersonating the Emperor!
Seize him!
Now!
(Xiao Ce,)
(I couldn't touch you inside the palace.
Now you've come right to my doorstep.)
(I might as well)
(have you killed.)
You dare
commit treason?
♪Let's time-travel, bro♪
♪Our spirit soars to the skies♪
♪The brainy emperor plots the strategy♪
♪The slacker general leads the charge♪
♪Swords clash and warhorses thunder♪
♪Let the history judge our deeds♪
♪Our brotherhood is priceless♪
♪Peace across the land, carefree at last♪
♪Funny moments never stop♪
♪Silly blunders never cease♪
♪Yet through every up and down♪
♪We create miracles♪
♪From naive youths♪
♪To legendary heroes♪
♪This journey♪
♪Is one we'll be proud of♪
♪Let's time-travel, bro♪
♪Let's create♪
♪A legend of our own♪