♪The world keeps changing♪
♪A thousand years pass
in the blink of an eye♪
♪Shoulder to shoulder♪
♪We stand above the world♪
♪Our identities switch♪
♪The world turns upside down♪
♪Watch me♪
♪Stir up a storm♪
♪Let's time-travel, bro♪
♪Our blood is boiling♪
♪The genius emperor plots
with brilliant strategy♪
♪The slacker general
is unmatched in battle♪
♪The business world is in turmoil♪
♪The court is rife with intrigue♪
♪We will conquer the world♪
♪There's no escape for the traitors♪
=No Way! My Bro Is the Emperor=
=Episode 1=
(Frontier Fort of Jing)
Gu Bei.
(Left Commander, Northern Plains,
Princess Hulv, Northern Plains)
We've been at war with Jing
(Right Commander, Northern Plains)
for years.
I'm taking our captured warriors
home today.
Get out here.
Commander Gu says
if you wish to see your men again,
(Chuan, Deputy Commander of Jing)
you may come to Xiaoyao Pavilion.
(Xiaoyao Pavilion)
♪What's your dad's dad called?♪
Hello!
Welcome!
I am
(Get Rich)
(Chill)
(Commandant of Proclaimed Might of Jing,
Frontier Fort Commander)
Gu Bei.
(Gu Bei,
Commander of Proclaimed Might of Jing)
What is your intention?
Having such a fine lady
in my humble pavilion,
surely I'll make sure
you have the time of your life.
- General!
Fine brew.
Cheers!
There are no prisoners here.
Only good times.
(I am)
(Gu Bei, a college senior and slacker.)
(Three years ago,
I transmigrated into the body of)
(a low-ranking military officer in Jing)
(commanding just 2,000 soldiers.)
(Without fighting a single battle)
(or losing a single soldier,)
(I built an entertainment business)
(and gained countless allies.)
(At the same time,)
(I shared my ultimate life goal)
(with them.)
(Which is)
(hit the clubs, soak in the tub,)
(and chill forever.)
Whoever
comes to Xiaoyao Pavilion
is guaranteed a carefree good time.
Welcome,
Princess of the Plains,
Hulv.
- Hulv!
Here's a gift for you, Miss Hulv.
Come visit
anytime.
Is this
me
in your eyes?
Of course.
With a beauty like yours,
why hide behind armor
and fight on the battlefield?
Wars and claiming territories
are merely for survival.
I run Xiaoyao Pavilion here
on the frontier
to trade grain and fabrics
for your furs and horses.
How about this?
Be my business partner, Miss Hulv.
Let's open Xiaoyao Pavilion
on the plains.
Sounds great!
From now on, every tribe on the plains
will treat you as if they were treating me.
They'll follow your lead!
- We'll follow your lead, Mr. Gu!
(Gu Bei)
Gu Bei?
Guarded the frontier for three years.
Not an inch of land lost.
Not a single soldier was killed.
Even the people of the plains
have pledged their loyalty to him.
(Xiao Ce, Emperor of Jing)
Interesting.
Come.
(Eunuch Xu,
Personal Eunuch of the Emperor)
Your Majesty.
Go to the frontier
and personally bring
this man back.
Summon
Commander Gu.
(Calm the Mind, Perceive the Dao)
I, Gu Bei,
greet Your Majesty.
Tell me.
You've defended the frontier
for three years without defeat.
How did you do it?
Tell me the truth.
If you answer it well,
I'll reward you handsomely.
If not,
you'll stay in the palace.
As
a eunuch.
(What the heck with him?)
(I thought it was a routine report.
Why am I suddenly getting castrated?)
Your Majesty,
back then,
when fifty thousand enemy troops invaded,
I
charged in alone,
with a long sword,
and cut them down to the last man.
Self-draw win! All of one suit!
Pay up if you have money.
If not, take off your clothes.
They were bawling their eyes out
when they lost.
I've heard
you drove back fifty thousand men
with merely two thousand troops,
without losing a single soldier.
How did you manage that?
That's a rumor.
A rumor.
Actually,
we had four casualties.
I've told you many times.
Don't drink and ride.
Don't ride and drink.
That's drunk riding.
It kills people, you know?
Your Majesty,
I'd like to ask for compensation
for those fallen soldiers.
General Gu, you're truly a talent.
I was
only joking earlier.
I understand.
Stay in the palace tonight.
Tomorrow, you'll join the other officials
for the palace examination.
Palace...
Palace
examination?
Those who perform well
will be
promoted
and handsomely rewarded.
But those who fail
are unworthy of their positions
and will be executed.
The reputedly capable
should give way to the truly worthy.
(Holy crap.)
(Fail the exam and you die?)
(What is the first priority
in ensuring the people's well-being?)
(Who would've thought)
(I'd still have to take exams
after time-traveling?)
(Even the question is written
in classical Chinese.)
(I don't understand a word.)
Candidates,
I'm watching
every move
you have made.
This is just like one of my teachers.
Your Majesty!
I'm not done yet!
Please give me another chance!
Your Majesty!
Spare me, Your Majesty!
(What is the first priority
in ensuring the people's well-being?)
I gave you your chance.
You failed to take it.
Now you'll pay with your life.
Wait.
Your Majesty.
Before I die,
can you grant me
one last wish?
Speak.
Eunuch Xu,
do you mind
getting me a flame stick?
Change when the odd and not when even.
What?
Seriously?
You don't even know that.
Guess you don't have much schooling.
Imperial jade wine.
One for 180.
How does it taste?
Let me brag about it.
You!
Wait...
- You must be one of us!
♪The♪
♪Boundless♪
♪Horizon♪
♪Is♪
♪Where♪
♪My love♪
♪Lies♪
♪At the foot of the rolling hills♪
♪The flowers♪
♪Bloom♪
♪Let's time-travel, bro♪
♪Our spirit soars to the skies♪
♪The brainy emperor plots the strategy♪
♪The slacker general leads the charge♪
♪Swords clash and warhorses thunder♪
♪Let the history judge our deeds♪
♪Our brotherhood is priceless♪
♪Peace across the land, carefree at last♪
♪Funny moments never stop♪
♪Silly blunders never cease♪
♪Yet through every up and down♪
♪We create miracles♪
♪From naive youths♪
♪To legendary heroes♪
♪This journey♪
♪Is one we'll be proud of♪
♪Let's time-travel, bro♪
♪Let's create♪
♪A legend of our own♪