[Episode 19]
Hi. Would you like half a white-cut chicken
or a whole one?
- A whole portion.
- Okay.
And let's have
the Typhoon Shelter Stir-fried Crab.
- And a steamed fish.
- Okay.
See if you'd like to add anything else.
That's enough.
It'd be a waste if we can't finish it.
Sure.
By the way,
when you and Ding picked up the confirmations,
did you make a list?
I already did. It's in my office drawer.
Haoyun's financial accounts
are all with local banks.
Check the local policies later.
Those little details are easy to exploit.
Okay.
Hello.
That's all your dishes. Enjoy.
That's enough.
This is good. You like it. It's sweet.
You two are that close?
But Miao Jing never mentioned you before.
Don't tell me they made you report
your family background when you joined.
No, we didn't.
So it's normal
that she never mentioned it to you.
As her superior, I don't need to know that.
But besides work, we're also exes.
She's pretty cold by nature.
If we didn't work at the same company,
I'd be like the guy before me.
We'd never speak again.
There was someone before him?
I think he was a college classmate.
They met on the swim team, I think.
Our personalities didn't match.
She even cut off her first love.
I guess work is the only reason
that we got together.
First love?
I don't think so.
Eat before it gets cold.
Have some more. It's on me.
Excuse me, check for table 28.
Someone at your table left a card.
The good-looking guy with glasses.
I left the card. Just run it.
She's in the restroom.
A guest is a guest.
Guests shouldn't have to pay.
I said I was treating her to dinner.
No way the plus-one pays.
(Cantonese) How about another table for you?
Come back when you've worked it out.
What does that mean?
The total is 458.
Just charge it, right?
Thanks.
[Intangible Cultural Heritage
Traditional Sugar Figurine Craft of Teng City]
- I'll take you to the hotel first.
- No need. My ride's almost here.
Safe travels.
See you tomorrow, then.
What are you laughing at?
I thought you wouldn't talk to me
until you got home.
I wasn't ignoring you.
You don't like Cen Ye.
I don't know him well.
So it's not about liking him or not.
I thought you'd want to know
what happened between him and me.
But then,
you also think it's tacky and petty to ask
about my former boyfriend.
So all you can do is stew over it alone,
get all worked up, and overthink it.
Some Jiaohai University genius you are.
Those idioms were a mess.
Why are you getting defensive?
I'm mad because he knows more than I do
about your life these past few years.
You're exes anyway.
Then tell me about your exes. I want to know.
What is there to tell?
Just tell me whatever there is.
When did you meet them?
How many were there? What did they do?
We met a long time ago.
What?
Tell me.
Come on. I'll tell you.
It's covered in dust.
Why do you always buy these?
At least get something with some color.
What do you know?
Which one is which?
Here, help me.
Your sister used to keep two pots of daisies
on her office desk.
She loved that kind of color.
Put this here.
Lay this down first.
Okay.
That's about it.
Have some water.
How's business lately?
Not bad.
Not many kids are taking lessons.
The adult classes are busier.
Teaching adults is easier than teaching kids.
Besides, you're still a kid yourself.
How would you have the patience to teach them?
I heard you've been spending a lot
of time with Zhang Bin lately.
Liu Bin Bo?
You know him?
I've heard of him.
He's from Lingang.
Zhang Bin has been in touch with him lately.
They've got big business to discuss.
What exactly did they talk about?
Probably import-export stuff.
I only know Zhang Bin
from playing a few games of pool.
He wouldn't talk business with me.
We'll hold on to this photo for now.
As for Zhang Bin,
the police will keep an eye on him.
Stay out of this.
I'm just an ordinary citizen.
What could I possibly get involved in?
Yi.
Let me remind you of something.
Don't gamble away your future
over what happened in the past.
It's not worth it.
If it were that easy to let go,
then why did you bring me here today?
Bo is moving tomorrow.
I'll go over there and take a look first.
I'm leaving.
Yi.
The spare key is on the shoe cabinet.
Take one with you.
Your Highness, check out our new place.
It's huge.
This way. It's south-facing.
What do you think?
Let's look at the kitchen.
- Is it here?
- Yes.
- The cookware is all ready. So thoughtful
- Everything is ready.
- Let's see the room.
- Over here?
- The nursery.
- That's right.
The bathroom's big too. Is that the bedroom?
Our bedroom.
Do you like it?
I love it. I really do.
Honey.
Don't worry.
I'll make you happy for the rest of your life.
Kang An.
Thank you for giving me such a warm home.
- Moving house like this...
- Careful.
It'll take five years off your life.
That's what you get for not exercising.
Go tidy up the bedroom.
What? Can't I at least have some water?
My legs are killing me.
Sorry to put you through all this, Yi.
It's fine. What else needs bringing up?
Thanks for all the hard work.
How can we live without planning ahead?
- Moving in?
- Yes.
Right here?
- Is this where they're moving?
- Yes.
This young man seems nice.
Mom. Dad. What are you doing here?
Sir. Ma'am,
why didn't you tell me you were coming?
I would've picked you up.
What is this supposed to mean?
We moved into a bigger place than the last one.
It's more comfortable.
And the renovations are better, too.
Qiao will be more comfortable here.
Yeah.
Let's go. Our Qiao isn't living here.
- She's coming home with me.
- Auntie.
- Ma'am.
- Mom.
Li Qiao and I are planning to get married.
Married?
You don't even have a home ready.
How can you talk about marriage?
If Qiao moves in, is this the life she'll have?
Look at this place. It's a total pigsty.
Who did you talk to about getting married?
Who did you talk to?
- Let's go.
Boss.
Boss, are you buying a place?
The quarterly dividends are all paid out.
With a little more cash from elsewhere,
it should cover a down payment, right?
Who's this?
Hello, sir, ma'am. I'm from the pool hall.
I'm here to give Bo a hand.
Chen, come in. Let's talk.
- Come in and talk.
- Bo.
What did you just call him?
"Boss"?
Doesn't he just mind the pool hall?
Bo didn't tell you?
He took over the place this quarter.
Maybe Bo wanted to wait until he got paid
before telling you?
That's right, sir, ma'am.
Once I get paid, I can afford a place.
Qiao and I plan to buy this place.
Exactly. Once he has the money,
he can tell you with confidence, right?
No.
Bo, Yong just mentioned classes starting
at the hall next month.
Why don't you take them to the pool hall?
Of course, sir, ma'am.
If you're free later,
why don't we go have a look?
Yeah, the pool hall! Let's look there first.
The shop is very well-kept. It's a mess here.
- Look at you, sounding like an idiot.
- Let's go to the shop.
The shop is very well-kept. Let's go.
- Is it far?
- Not far.
If I have to climb all those stairs again,
I'm not going.
I'll carry you down.
How can you buy a place like this?
It doesn't even have an elevator.
What will you do later?
Let's keep looking.
Seriously.
- Sir, ma'am...
- He'll carry Mom.
I'll carry you.
- Slow down.
- Watch your step.
Slow down.
This is our pool club.
Hello, boss. Hello, ma'am.
Get back to work. Study or teach.
This place is called Diagonal.
What we mainly do here is training.
It's not some chaotic hangout
full of random people.
And we have coaches here.
They all teach proper classes.
Hello, boss. Hello, ma'am.
Get back to work. Get to class.
Bo.
Look over there. Coach Wang...
Why is it Coach Wang again?
You're an employee. Can't you handle this?
Go handle it. I'm with guests.
- Go get busy.
- No, no, no. I'm not busy.
I'm not a bossy boss.
I get along with the staff like friends.
But when things happen,
I do have real leadership skills.
Isn't Yi our boss...
Yi.
Bo's office is upstairs.
Why don't you go up and take a look?
Right, I have an office on the second floor.
- There's a second floor?
- Let me take you up.
- It's pretty spacious.
- This way.
Yes.
- Watch the stairs.
- Okay, okay.
What happened, Yi?
This is our office.
This is my office.
Yes.
You little punk.
You opened a business behind our backs
and didn't even brag to us?
I was making big moves in silence.
Right.
Okay. Not bad.
Having an office like this is pretty good.
Solid wood, too.
Looks pretty new.
Your desk is completely bare.
So you just sit here looking at photos?
No, I'm hardly ever in this office.
I'm usually out meeting clients.
There are so many clients,
so this desk is brand-new, as you can see.
And I haven't bought much furniture.
Have some water.
Bo is working, honey.
- Don't get in his way.
- Okay.
Let's go.
Well, about the wedding...
Isn't it obvious?
Great.
You're a boss now.
Dress a little more maturely from now on.
It's fine.
- He's young.
- Let me walk you out.
- Alright, not bad at all.
- Uncle, watch your step.
How big is this place?
Not big, but later we...
How much is it per hour?
20 yuan an hour.
- Goodbye.
- 20 yuan. Four tables.
Goodbye.
Four times 20...
- That's 80 yuan.
- I'll give you a ride.
- So if we go by...
- No, thanks.
12 hours a day, that comes to 960...
30 times 960 is 28,800.
Half the revenue goes to costs...
Okay, go on.
Goodbye, sir. Goodbye, ma'am.
You're the best, man.
You're the best, real brother!
You weren't great back there, but you did okay.
You did okay.
Come to my place for dinner tonight.
Let's go.
These are the shop's accounts.
Equipment, revenue, all that.
We have digital copies,
but don't lose the originals.
This is the tax registration certificate.
File the taxes honestly at the tax office.
Wait, Yi. Weren't we just putting on an act?
Just write down what I tell you.
These are the business license
and health permit.
You came with me when we applied for them.
Just go to the business bureau.
Also, don't forget
to pay the insurance premium.
This...
Forget it. I'll make you a list later.
Pay Yong's profit share as usual.
You know he's simple-minded.
Look out for him.
This is the shop's bank card.
This is the key to the safe.
The safe holds the shop's contracts
and certificates.
Do not forget this.
Yi.
I'll consider this money a loan from you.
I'm only watching the shop for you.
You can't just wash your hands of it.
Fine, then count it as a loan from me.
Didn't you always want a stable life
with Li Qiao?
What I said earlier wasn't a joke.
This isn't just to placate Li Qiao's parents.
The pool hall is much cleaner now.
You spend way more time there than I do.
You get along with the coaches and staff.
You're better suited to run the place.
Come on, it's not like I'm never coming back.
When I do, I'll definitely come here.
Otherwise, I won't even have a place to stay.
So, where are you going this time?
Yi.
Just give me a straight answer.
Don't worry.
It's definitely a good place.
- Stop staring at me.
- I'm not staring.
That's gross.
Gross?
Be my best man when I get married.
And drive the lead car.
- Fine.
- Can you be the Master of Ceremonies too?
Save me some money.
Master of Ceremonies?
[Teng City Nancheng District
Industry and Commerce Office]
Sign it. It's not a death warrant.
[Chen Yi, Wang Bo]
- I'm doing it.
- Do it.
[Pool Hall Transfer Agreement]
Stop sighing.
But the data on current assets is too vague.
We can't prepare work papers on guesswork.
We need a workable solution from you.
The inventory records
from these past years are here.
Whenever you ask, we cooperate fully.
But I can't guarantee there are no gaps.
Also, when our audit team inventoried stock,
we found several discrepancies
in outbound records, destinations unknown.
What do you think, Manager Wang?
You must be pretty new here, young lady.
We have so many warehouses, so many fleets.
Do you know how much freight moves every day?
Leaving aside
whether the issue is even a valid point.
Even if it does exist,
it could just be an admin oversight.
That proves nothing.
Watch your language.
The payments for these shipments are missing.
As auditors, we have the right to suspect
someone in your company is embezzling funds.
Your audit team may lack competence,
but you sure have wild imaginations.
Yi, they are in a meeting inside.
It's fine. I'll just take a look.
You're really just a short-sighted woman.
- I can call someone for you.
- I'm just going in to take a look.
Which department are you with?
Ever heard of knocking first?
Hello, everyone. I'm Chen Yi, the new guy.
Mr. Zhang said I'll be handling Mingtong
from now on.
Nice to meet you.
An audit meeting?
Perfect. I'll sit in and learn the process.
What's going on?
Why are you looking at me? Keep going.
We have to follow the procedure, right?
Cen Ye, head of Mingtong's audit team.
Deputy team leader, Miao Jing.
Get on with your meeting.
Go on, Deputy Miao.
Besides the warehouse issue,
we also found some issues with your company's
approval process for some major contracts.
It wasn't always carried out
strictly by company rules.
Do you have any plans
to review and improve
your internal control system?
You speak clearly and logically.
You're good at your job, aren't you?
Supervisor Wang, you said she's short-sighted.
Are you just jealous
because she has more hair than you?
Please let us proceed without interruptions.
Besides that, according to the 2010 records,
your company's accounts receivable turnover
has declined compared with previous years.
Some amounts are long overdue.
Have you taken any measures
to strengthen collections and management?
Those are my three main questions.
Xiao Yu will add the rest.
You may respond to everything
after the audit inquiry concludes.
Seriously? Is your audit process this tedious?
We could settle it with a spreadsheet offline.
In the time you spend on this back-and-forth,
we could draft two sets of work papers.
Manager Chen,
you haven't finished the handover, right?
At least for today's meeting,
Wang is still in charge.
You have no right to interrupt our meeting.
That is my point.
You care more about form than function.
My authority took effect the moment
I joined Haoyun.
If you have an issue, take it up the chain.
Then let's stop wasting time here.
We will stop here for today.
Once you sort out your internal issues,
we can talk again.
Mr. Chen.
I'm the head of Human Resources.
Why don't I show you to your office?
Just tell me where it is.
I want to check in with the audit team.
It is next to the freight department's office.
It's right next to Wang.
Over here, sir.
They call him a manager,
but who knows what business he oversees?
Even if he is just an empty suit,
he was still handpicked by Mr. Zhang.
[Meeting Room]
Sorry about earlier.
I ordered everyone some drinks.
We have milk tea and coffee.
It's okay. You barged into the conference room
without a word just now.
You scared me half to death.
Miao. I need to ask you about something.
Milk tea.
Coffee.
Isn't he the one who picks Jing up every day?
I saw him barge into the conference room
without a word.
He's the project manager. He started today.
He'll be taking over for Wang.
- He'll be our point of contact.
- So it's a "friends and family" deal?
That should make things easier, right?
He looks way better than Wang, doesn't he?
Even if his fashion sense is awful:
a suit, a floral shirt, and sneakers.
What do you know?
- This is the trendy yuppie style.
- I really don't get it.
Handsome guys are roses with thorns.
He doesn't look easy to deal with.
Does this outfit work?
Come here.
Back at Kuangxia, you wore suits all the time.
You were poorer then,
but even more particular than now.
Peak lapels had to go
with a diagonal-striped tie.
So why show up now in sneakers?
I was young back then.
I had to dress older
to make people take me seriously.
I don't need to anymore.
You used to try to look respectable.
Now you're making yourself look shabby.
What,
are you afraid Haoyun will rub off on you?
If that's the case,
why get mixed up in this mess?
Can't I just get a real job?
I'll give you one more chance
to tell me the truth.
I just wanted to surprise you.
You definitely did.
You look very professional.
Does it look good?
You buttoned too many buttons.
I did it on purpose.
Then unbutton it.
Why?
You've been in there for half an hour.
I was afraid you'd pass out.
I'll dry your hair.
After you left today,
Ding Lei from our team kept cursing.
He said you embarrassed him in public.
He thought
that Haoyun didn't respect the audit team.
So, at a time like this,
coming to Haoyun means
you don't respect me either?
I wouldn't dare.
Zhang Bin came to the pool hall
for you so many times.
Why did you say yes this time?
Didn't you say he looked good in a suit?
I wanted to show you I look good, too.
Otherwise, what if you ran off with him?
When did I say he looked good in a suit?
I didn't even say who, and you knew.
So you two must be pretty close.
Don't change the subject.
Are you up to something?
Your nose is bleeding.
I just got overheated from the long shower.
Let's go to the hospital.
No need.
Just buy me some herbal tea downstairs.
What should we eat?
This is the place I was looking at.
- I heard this dish here is really good.
- This one?
There are so many people.
Why don't we eat here?
Sure.
Look, a Qixi Festival discount.
A Qixi set menu.
- Hello, table for two.
- Two?
We need to take a number.
- How long is the wait?
- It's a bit busy right now.
- It might take about an hour.
- Okay.
Are you still getting this?
Sure. Why don't we see which line is shorter?
Then let's figure out what to eat first.
Here.
Xiao, what do you feel like eating?
Braised pork rice.
Qixi's special.
Why don't we get the couple's special?
It's 40 percent off. It's much more
cost-effective than ordering à la carte.
A couple's special isn't right for us.
Didn't see that coming, Ma Yang.
You always seem so laid-back.
I didn't think you'd care about that.
No, I...
I get it.
I know taking advantage sounds bad,
but I did ask you to come out.
I would never tell anyone.
If Miao Jing could pass for a guy,
I wouldn't have dragged you into this.
Then let's get this.
Isn't that Jing?
Who?
Jing.
It really is Jing.
Okay, one second. I'll get your change.
Jing.
Okay.
- Jing.
I knew it was you. Are you here alone?
There was a guy here just now.
- He looked like--
- What are you two doing together?
We're having dinner.
Yeah, dinner.
Do you know what Ma Yang caught Cen doing
when he worked late last night?
What?
- Cen was asking about a bag.
- You look just like--
Aren't you curious?
Don't change the subject.
We're getting to the good part.
Cen was asking a sales associate
about the new women's bag.
Who do you think it was for?
His mom? Her birthday's coming up, right?
You've been broken up for over a year,
and you still remember his mom's birthday?
Why did you buy two herbal teas?
Who's the other one for?
I'm overheated.
I was afraid one cup wouldn't be enough.
You should go eat.
I think they're calling numbers now.
No rush. It's fine.
I'm in a hurry to get home.
All right.
- Then we'll get going.
- Bye, Jing.
- Bye.
- Let's go.
- That's not right.
One of them definitely looked like that...
Really!
You're really not drinking it?
If your nose bleeds again, you're on your own.
You run the second you see people.
Are you afraid of being seen?
I don't want to make things hard for you.
That sounds very considerate of you.
If you don't want to make it hard for me,
then don't join Haoyun.
Are you up to something?
No.
Chen Yi.
Promise me.
Don't be like you were before,
playing petty games to force me out.
Don't leave me behind again, okay?
Then promise me.
Stop doing dangerous things.
Do you hear me?
[Haoyun Logistics]
Eat first, or it'll get cold.
What is it? Is something dirty?
No.
Then what are you looking at?
Just looking.
You do look good in a suit.
I can't keep my hands off you.
We're at the office.
What?
Didn't you say this suit is to make sure
that I'd only look at you?
Well, I'm looking at you now, aren't I?