[Episode 20]
We're at the office.
What?
Didn't you say this suit is to make sure
that I'd only look at you?
Well, I'm looking at you now, aren't I?
You can take your time at home.
Didn't you say auditors, by the rules,
can't get too close to the people they audit?
You go in first. I'll come in later.
Quite the rule-follower.
So what you're saying is,
once we're at work, we're strangers?
I thought you wanted to sneak around
and make it feel a little different.
Miao Jing.
Okay. I won't tease you.
Just keep it appropriate.
[Haoyun Logistics]
Uncle Zhou.
6,000 tons. All routed through Haoyun.
Are you overreacting a bit?
Haoyun is the biggest commercial logistics
company in all of Teng City.
If they don't use Haoyun,
who else would they use?
Honestly, sometimes I think women
can get a little bogged down in details.
They take a tiny issue
and blow it way out of proportion.
Ding, say that in here if you must,
but don't ever say it out there.
Or they'll blame your academic advisers.
What do you mean by that?
That makes it sound like
you never had formal audit training.
Director Cen. Look at this.
6,000 tons.
In theory, six heavy-truck runs are enough.
But they made about 20 runs every month.
Sometimes even more.
20,000 tons?
Does Chengpeng really have that much cargo?
The data shows it's all Chengpeng's cargo.
Heavy truck freight is expensive as it is.
Not only did they fail to cut costs,
but they actually tripled them.
Unless it's on Haoyun's end.
Then let's go check on-site.
Compare the data, and we'll know.
Get Haoyun to cooperate
and reorganize the draft data.
Get someone to match everything up.
And you...
Am I interrupting your meeting?
I was going to wait until you wrapped up
before coming in for a quick word.
But I just heard Haoyun needs to cooperate,
so I figured it'd be easier to say it now.
Not at all. Actually, you're right on time.
We've clarified some related issues already.
It should make everyone's work easier.
Here, please have a seat.
Look at him. Isn't that over the top?
Give him a cup of tea,
and he'll bow to serve the new manager.
Manager Chen, what is this about?
You mentioned last time
that our staffing and processes weren't clear.
So from now on, we'll stay compliant
and follow the proper procedures.
Data requests will need signatures
from relevant people. That'll make it easier.
I didn't get much schooling,
but I know if you follow the rules
and stick to procedure, you can't go wrong.
Follow the rules?
So now, to get even one data file,
- we have to run around getting signatures?
- Handsome but sharp-tongued.
If every data request needs a signature,
how much time is that going to waste?
Haoyun will cover our overtime pay?
I don't see a problem with that.
Haven't you always played by the rules?
Why think they're picking on you now?
- Well, it is a bit...
- You're Manager Ding, right?
Just call me Ding Lei.
I didn't expect you to be so like-minded.
Thank you.
Since no one has any objections,
we'll follow the procedure.
You've done great work at Haoyun,
and you've been so dedicated.
Zhang Bin should've hired you sooner.
Did that hurt?
Don't start that with me.
- I was wrong.
- About what?
You were making things hard for us.
- I was just doing my job.
- Then I'm just doing mine.
Yes, that's the file.
Okay.
I'll send you a copy of the workflow later.
This is our office area.
The freight department sits here.
The business department is over there.
This way.
I hear he targeted the audit team right away.
What was he thinking?
Trying to impress Mr. Zhang, I guess.
Forget it. It's none of our business.
Manager Chen, this office was set up for you.
The lighting is absolutely incredible.
Here, take a look.
I picked out all these decorations for you.
Work is usually pretty relaxed here.
Management mostly just sits in meetings,
reports to the higher-ups,
and assigns tasks to subordinates.
Please, have a seat here.
There's no rush on any of this.
If the audit team asks for data files later,
everything has to be reviewed before release.
The person in charge has to sign off.
Well, Manager Chen.
Why would we take on a thankless job?
Once we sign, we're on the hook.
If we don't, someone else is liable.
If you disagree,
email Mr. Zhang and copy Mr. Tao.
You're the expert at reporting up.
So report what you've learned on this job.
I...
Fine.
We'll do whatever you say.
But if something goes wrong, it has nothing
to do with the freight department.
What could possibly go wrong?
Right, you have the old district warehouse.
You want that warehouse, too?
Even a nepo hire can't go that far.
That's not what I meant.
We've had that warehouse for a long time.
We've never had a problem.
You're asking for it so suddenly.
I'm afraid Mr. Tao won't accept it.
So, if the old district warehouse has issues,
then my request would be reasonable?
Manager Chen, what are you trying to do?
What a nepo hire should do.
What are you going to do?
Mr. Zhang put me in this position,
not to keep a dog that won't bite.
Pick up the phone.
Get up.
Stop sleeping. Get up.
Where is the warehouse guard?
I'm calling him now.
Where is he?
Where did he run off to?
He won't even answer his phone.
What's going on?
If there's a problem, say it.
Keep your hands to yourself.
Mr. Tao. Director Wang.
What are you all doing here?
Why didn't you answer when I called?
What kind of work ethic is that?
Everyone knows I've taken a nap at noon
for years.
You said you called?
It never even rang.
I did call. Look for yourself.
Look.
What's going on?
It just rang now.
You...
Well. Did you change your number?
By the rules, every month
you have to inspect the warehouse.
And you never noticed the phone was dead?
- Well...
- He never came here!
Every time, he sends a couple of kids
to get it over with.
Mr. Tao, that's not true. I really didn't.
You know what kind of man I am.
He was the one who neglected his duty.
- I'll talk to HR tomorrow and have him fired.
- You...
Rot starts at the top.
You think your hands are clean?
You're the one who let it happen.
If you'd owned up, I'd have called you loyal.
If you're selling out your own people now,
what won't you do later?
Keys.
From now on, you're in charge
of the old district warehouses.
Mr. Tao, let me explain.
I'm telling you, he changed his number.
He changed it and never told me.
- It's not that I didn't come.
- Shut your mouth.
It's true, Mr. Tao.
[Haoyun Logistics]
Send me all the drivers' files.
Mark anyone who's driven for over five years
and is bold but careful.
Manager Chen,
Mr. Tao chose everyone on the fleet side.
Should we check with him?
Do you know what connections mean?
What?
It means I do whatever I want.
And you don't get a say.
- Understood.
Understood.
This needs to be done.
Will he need that?
[Driver's Personal Information]
- Here you go.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
- Take care.
One snow fungus soup and one Herbal Jelly.
- I'd like a grass jelly.
- Just a moment.
Sorry to disturb your day off.
It's work. You're not disturbing me.
I need to pick up a confirmation letter.
The factory happens to be near your place.
We asked the freight company
for their inventory list before.
They kept giving us the runaround.
They claim they need a third-party stamp.
So let's get it settled today.
And let's ask the supplier for the inventory
list to make future cross-checks easier.
I ordered you snow fungus soup.
- Thanks for coming in on a weekend.
- Scan my code.
I was planning to come around here anyway.
- Thank you.
- No problem.
- Got a plan?
- Take care. Come again.
Let's go.
For third-party contacts,
you need at least two people.
And leave a paper trail.
[Teng City Chengpeng Steel]
Hello.
Coming.
Hello. How can I help you?
We're with Haoyun.
We have an appointment with Supervisor Liu.
Come in. Register over here.
Okay.
- Thanks.
- Go on in.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Here's the stamped certificate.
I'll keep looking for the release order.
One moment, please.
Thank you.
Release forms, release forms... Here they are.
Right.
The records from the past two years
are all on there.
[Teng City Chengpeng Steel Co., Ltd.
Goods Dispatch Note]
Monthly output is around 6,000 tons.
It takes five truck runs to ship it.
But since the year before last,
you've used Haoyun for all your freight.
Yes. They're cheap.
The rest can be handled by freelance trucks.
Isn't Haoyun Teng City's largest
commercial logistics company?
- Why not give them all your freight?
- Of course, we'd like to.
Look at all those heavy trucks Haoyun has
sitting in the yard.
And they still claim they don't have enough.
My guess is they don't want factory orders.
And those courier stations are actually all
for small-package logistics.
[Teng City Chengpeng Steel]
All done?
What are you doing here?
It's raining. The car can't get in.
Here.
Looks like I picked a bad time today.
It's work. I understand.
Jing and I often hang out on weekends.
A little wait won't hurt.
Where are you headed later, Mr. Cen?
I just got here, so I don't know the area.
Why don't we go together?
It's easy to navigate or get a cab.
Am I intruding?
It's raining. You won't get a cab here.
Let's take shelter up ahead.
Back in high school, I touched the dragon head
and made a wish here.
What did you wish for? Did it come true?
Pretty much.
I wanted to get into a good college.
Then it really worked.
I come back every year to give thanks for her.
Of course, Bogong looks out for her.
So you call the Earth God "Bogong" here.
If Bogong is that powerful,
I want to pray for love, too.
Praying to the Earth God for love?
That's a pretty desperate prayer.
Aren't you an atheist?
We only met because you came to Jiaohai.
Who's to say Bogong didn't bring us together?
Looks like matchmaking isn't his field.
He gave you a chance,
and you still became her ex.
Don't say that in front of him.
We continue with Chapter 44
of Dream of the Red Chamber.
An unexpected turn.
Wang Xi Feng Flies into a Jealous Rage.
Come in.
Manager Chen.
All the documents for the file transfer
are ready. Please take a look.
Mr. Cen, you brought them yourself?
I'm listed as the applicant in the system.
Your company's procedures are thorough.
To avoid wasting unnecessary time,
coming in person is the most efficient way.
You're very thorough, Mr. Cen.
We also want to move this forward quickly.
But I'm booked with meetings all day.
To pull the files,
we'd have to go to the suburbs.
I'm afraid I won't have the time.
So, Manager Chen, you mean...
How about this?
If it's urgent, Mr. Cen,
let's set another time.
I'll find a way to speed things along for you.
Everything is negotiable.
Of course.
Whenever you're free, Manager Chen,
you pick the place.
Friday night.
I haven't played pool in a while.
I wonder if I'm rusty.
Good. I'll set it up.
A buddy of mine has a place.
No need for you to spend money, Mr. Cen.
Thanks for understanding, Manager Chen.
You didn't call me here
just to play a couple of games, did you?
You negotiate very directly, Mr. Cen.
Different clients call for different styles.
You get things done fast,
so there's no need to waste time.
Search the old district warehouse all you want.
I won't interfere.
However...
Miao Jing can't be involved.
This is a normal assignment for our audit team.
You're overstepping.
I'm giving you room to maneuver.
Then give me something in return.
You're keeping Miao Jing
and the company's freight staff out of it.
Looks like Haoyun's warehouse isn't so simple.
Mr. Cen.
That's all I'm saying. Don't get greedy.
How many truckloads yesterday?
I did three yesterday.
Three?
- How about you?
- Five loads.
Good work. Here, have some water, everyone.
- Thank you, Manager Chen.
- Thank you, Manager Chen. Thanks.
Here, Xie.
- Take this and share it with the guys.
- Okay.
Okay, let's go.
Thanks.
- Yi.
- Good work.
Are those trucks with our fleet, too?
They're all headed to the dock. Same old spot.
This job looks pretty good.
It doesn't look too demanding.
Who knows what they're hauling?
Bai.
- Yi, I'll head over first.
- Go ahead.
It's so hot. You didn't have to come.
I could handle it myself.
I wanted to get first-hand data.
It'll be faster with both of us here.
You don't trust me?
I'm not questioning your competence.
Hello.
Who are you?
I'm with Chengpeng Steel.
This is Ms. Miao.
She's in charge of our supply chain.
Chengpeng?
Chengpeng Steel.
- Hello.
We had a shipment go out last month.
But the buyer said the quantity was off.
There definitely wasn't a problem
on our end of the supply chain.
So we wanted to see
if anything happened in logistics.
What does that have to do with logistics?
You packed everything and sent it over.
The warehouse never even touched it.
You mean Haoyun Logistics took your cargo?
- No.
- It's like this.
Our supply chain shipped everything normally.
We were worried
that something went wrong during shipping.
What?
Calm down. We've been long-term partners.
You're reliable, of course.
But the buyer is missing a shipment.
So we wanted to check your inventory records
and the fleet's original logs.
If it does turn out to be on our end,
we'll send another shipment.
Right.
I'll need to ask my manager about this.
We can't just pull the original logs.
Mr. Chen.
I'm with Chengpeng Steel Supply Chain.
My last name is Miao. Just call me Miao.
Miao. Nice to meet you.
Mr. Chen, it's Cen.
Yes, here's the thing.
Last month,
one of our shipments went through Haoyun.
But it went missing.
So we'd like to check the original logs.
Would that be possible?
Pull them up. I'll watch from here.
I'll do it.
I'll do it. You didn't handle it.
Look it up yourselves.
Thank you.
Have a cigarette?
Mr. Chen.
- Let's go. This way.
- Okay.
What are you doing here?
I'm here to help you sort this out.
Once you're done, leave.
Don't hold us up from going home.
The logistics side looks clean, too.
Let's go back and file the loss report.
Thanks, man.
Bye, Mr. Chen.
Manager, I'll get back to work.
Hello.
I know.
Keep an eye on things for me first.
I'll be right over.
Okay.
- Don't be scared.
- What happened?
There was a loud bang just now.
- What's wrong?
- It scared him.
I didn't do anything.
Did that scare you?
It's okay, sweetheart.
No one's breaking down the door.
That thing just fell, right?
You're the bravest little man there is.
No need to be scared.
No need to be scared, right? You're the cutest.
If you had a decent man around,
Bao wouldn't have to be scared of anything.
What are you talking about?
Ms. Tu, I'm only trying to help.
Back when you had a boyfriend,
that guy still kept coming over to scare you.
Now, Bao isn't the only one terrified.
I'm scared to death, too.
Anyway, I'm just an employee.
Anyone who wants a job
that's this much trouble can have it.
I won't be doing it much longer.
Wow, a big bridge!
I'm heading over now. Have Zhang come here.
Come here, baby.
Drink some water.
Good boy.
Ms. Li.
- What's wrong?
- Come here for a second.
Ms. Li, taking care of Bao is hard work.
Starting next month, I'll give you
a 200-yuan raise every month.
But I still need you to look after Bao.
All right. Leave Bao to me.
Sweetie. I'm off to work.
Say bye-bye to Mommy.
Bye-bye, Mommy.
Blow a kiss.
Lovely.
[Li's Nails, Fully Upgraded]
[Skin Care Services Now Available]
Hello.
Right now?
I can't right now. I still have a few ahead.
Nine o'clock. Nine should work.
Are you free at nine?
Okay. Come by at nine, then.
Try this mask.
It's great for hydration. It's new.
I don't feel any irritation at all.
I knew I had to come to you.
I'm getting married next week.
I have to be the most beautiful bride.
Right.
Time really flies.
You and Bo are getting married already.
Congratulations.
Why are you congratulating me now?
You're coming next week, aren't you?
Of course I'm going.
Don't transfer me the money today.
I don't know what to get you anyway.
Consider it a wedding gift.
You're still taking clients at nine?
No date with Yi?
We broke up. Bo didn't tell you?
No.
He never talks about Yi's private life at home.
Now that you two have broken up,
what are you going to do now?
What's there to do?
I'll just keep living my life.
Couples break up and get back together.
It's normal.
True.
You can never count on men.
Why don't you come to our pool hall?
I'll introduce you to a few decent guys.
Maybe some other time.
I'm meeting a client tonight.
Come on. Look.
This guy.
I heard he owns a few skewer places
near Teng City College.
He's also really sweet.
This one has a nice build.
But he's a little wishy-washy.
What do you think? Want to come by?
Come on.
Li, you still haven't gotten over Yi, have you?
There's nothing to get over.
I just...
I don't know.
Maybe I just want to be single for a while.
I'll go change the water.
Let me hold the child.
Who?
Do you want a repeat of last time?
I won't.
Let's keep some distance in public.
Your new shop is up and running now.
We don't have to pretend anymore.
Tu Li, being my girlfriend is just a label.
This is a mutually beneficial arrangement.
[Thank you, Yi]
We agreed not to interfere in
each other's lives.
If you don't want to play along anymore,
I don't care.
[I'm borrowing the car, so just take my gifts.]
[Okay. Come on over.]
You know very well you don't like me.
You just need my help once in a while.
[Yi, he's at the store again.]
[Got it.]
We've been hauling cargo all day.
I'm exhausted.
What's taking them so long?
It's fine. These are minor issues.
They're here.
Come on.
Guys, pick up the pace.
- Hurry up.
- What are you doing?
Give that back.
Don't keep those on your camera.
Who are you here as?
Their representative or my boyfriend?
If you're their representative,
today's my day off.
Taking landscape photos is my own hobby.
You have no right to interfere.
Go back first.
Stay with a coworker for a couple of days.
What are you going to do?
Miao Jing.
Everyone, check everything.
See if anything else is wrong.
Bring all the tools back.
Mr. Tao, the trucks are all set.
Everything's done.
We see this in office buildings all the time.
Young people like chasing thrills outdoors.
It's totally normal.
Let's go, Mr. Tao.
Pack up and get ready to board.
[Motor Vehicle Inspection Card Stub]
- Bai, here you go.
- Okay.
Let's head out.