Why did you break other people’s things?
I wasn’t breaking things.
The shop owner said
she wouldn’t mind if I did it.
Are you screwing with me?
Master is criticizing me again.
Gen. Just call me Gen.
Gen.
Oh, sorry!
Kaew…
Next week, I’m meeting up with
the friends we joined the company with.
She’s been out of the picture for years.
I wouldn’t have the guts to come if I were her.
Sawasdee ka.
Come on, follow me.
- What?
- Do we really have to go this far, honey?
Shh!
Today, we must find out
who Nong Gen’s girlfriend is,
where she’s from, and what she does!
This is serious village business.
And we're the village's only hope.
Go keep a lookout.
- Ouch! What the hell?!
- Oh!
Ahhh! A ghost!
Is it gone yet? Is it gone yet?
See if it's gone yet!
P’ Zoon, it’s Nong Ai.
Get up!
Hi there, Nong Ai.
What are you doing?
Gosh. Thought she was a Japanese
ghost with that long, flowing hair.
Uh, beautiful—I mean, Nong Ai!
We weren't following you
or snooping around at all.
Right? We really don’t want to
know anything about you at all.
That’s enough!
Nong Ai, we were just out for a stroll.
A little nighttime date...
so romantic, don't you think?
- That’s right.
- Well, we'll be going now.
Have a nice date.
Uh... thanks.
Go.
Now, how do I do this?
Gen, who is this?
Uh...
I’m Ai, Gen’s girlfriend.
Sorry I’m late.
When we talked that day,
I thought you were single.
Because you...
Mind if I join you?
Not at all! Please, join us.
Scoot over.
You can sit here.
Ai, no.
Thank you.
Smells so good.
Um, if you don't mind me asking,
how did you two end up together?
Yeah. How?
Exactly. How did you end
up with someone like Gen?
Gen, I don't mean anything bad by it.
I'm just curious.
The smell of cloves reminds me of the
massaman curry my mother used to make.
My mother always said that
if the heat is too high...
all you get is a sharp, smoky smell
instead of the flavor.
The curry needs to be simmered slowly
until it becomes rich and coats your tongue,
not just a fleeting aroma.
Good things take time.
Some people don't even realize
they've let something good slip away.
Isn’t that right, Gen?
That was sharper than any spice.
Totally.
Was that a dig at me?
Uh, excuse us for a moment.
Ai.
We can talk here, Gen.
Ai!
Don't you want to know how I ended
up here and why I wasn't at home?
How do humans even make things like this?
The beads are so tiny.
Please provide a simpler method suitable
for a less-than-one-month-old robot.
According to my analysis, 80% uneven,
65% messy,
and 70% poorly arranged.
Conclusion...
not pretty.
I need to finish it before Gen comes home.
It seems Gen is feeling shy.
We live together, you see.
- Living together?
- Hold on.
Then do you mind if I ask how you two met?
Yeah, I want to know too.
It's been ages since we last met.
Give us an update. Come on.
We met through our work.
Ai.
I'm a researcher at a tech development company.
The parent company is based in
the US, so I have to fly back and forth.
One of the times I came back,
I met Gen, who had joined
our company as a creative.
Can robots even lie?!
This is getting out of hand!
What’s the name of the company?
- It’s a secret!
- A secret?
It’s just a company name.
Or… could it be that everything
you've told us isn’t true?
- Yeah.
- Right?
Come on, just tell us.
Kaew, stop it.
It's okay if Gen doesn't want to tell us.
I don't have my business card with me today.
I only have my employee ID.
If you really want to know,
you can take a look.
Pardon me.
“Lead Researcher…”
Wait a minute!
This is a major global company!
Yeah, that’s right!
It’s very famous!
I really want to work there.
Then why keep it a secret?
Yeah.
Gen didn't want anyone to know where she worked.
Gen has always told me that she doesn’t like
people judging her based on appearances.
And neither of us really cares
what the other does for a living.
We only care about who we truly are.
She makes me feel that way.
A message from the lab.
I need to go in and check on something.
Can I have my ID back, please?
Uh, yes, of course.
I'll be going now.
Wait. You can't go by yourself.
Let's head back together.
You stay with your friends.
See you at home.
So lovey-dovey.
Wow, you quit a good job to go freelance
and ended up dating
a researcher at a major company.
I'm so happy for you.
Hey.
Gen.
I… I have to go.
This is awkward.
Actually, I came here to return this.
I hope we never see each other again.
Ai! Wait!
Sorry.
What was that just now?
Was that Ai?
The robot girl?
Didn't know she had this side to her.
Hello, Khun Ploy.
Thank you for handling the urgent request.
You’re very welcome.
If you need anything else,
feel free to let me know anytime.
I'll take care of it.
I'll transfer the remaining
amount to you shortly.
Thank you.
Uh... may I ask you a quick question?
The team member who
worked on your latest project
said she’d like to return
something she received from you.
I’m not sure if—
As we discussed before,
I’m not able to disclose the address
or any company information.
But I think she was quite
satisfied with what she got.
Pardon?
Anyway, I’ll contact you
within the next two or three days
and send over the information
for the next project.
I’ll be counting on you to take care of it.
Oh, of course.
Thank you very much, Khun Irene.
I’ll be in touch.
If I fail again, my mom’s gonna kill me.
Why can't I ever get this right?
Come on, calm down.
All these stupid rules and formulas.
Why do we even have to learn physics?
It's not like we're going
to use it when we grow up.
Try drawing it out first
and then apply the formula.
It might make it easier.
How do you mean, big sis?
Let me borrow that.
First, you need to draw this line
to find the x-axis and y-axis.
That’s it.
Physics isn't just about numbers.
It's a language for telling the story of motion.
Whoa.
Why can't our teacher explain it like this?
I finally understand it today.
Are you a teacher, big sis?
No. I just usually spend
all day working with data
and with things that aren't human.
Wow, that’s so cool.
Big sis, you’re not only beautiful but kind too.
I'm not usually this kind, you know.
It's just that someone changed my perspective.
Helping people for a change feels
kind of strange, but in a good way.
Anyway, thank you so much for helping us out.
If it weren't for you,
we probably wouldn’t have gotten it.
Exactly. We can't thank you enough.
Just do your best with your studies.
I have to go.
Class, show your respect.
Thank you, teacher!
Hello, P’ Ploy.
Hey Gen, get ready. We’ll probably
get a new brief in a few days.
Okay.
What’s gotten into you today?
No complaining?
Did something happen?
Nope.
Gen, be serious.
Are you keeping secrets now?
Nothing. I’m just a little tight on money
lately, so I want to take on more work.
As if I’d buy that.
Anyway, I asked the client
about returning that item for you.
And?
They said you can’t return it.
Oh.
That’s it? What’s wrong with you?
You were making such a big deal about it,
and now you’re acting like it’s nothing?
Well, they won't let me return it,
so what else am I supposed to do?
Why is everyone saying such weird things today?
Hey P’ Ploy, have you ever
seen a system glitch out?
It usually follows every command perfectly,
then all of a sudden it
starts thinking for itself.
Like in those doomsday movies
where AI takes over the world.
What are you on about? Look at me.
I have a hundred different sides,
depending on who I’m with.
Forget it. You’re no help at all.
What? Why?
You’d better spill it.
You’ve been acting weird since earlier.
Are you in love?
Yeah, I’m just being weird.
I’m hanging up.
Don’t worry about the work.
Once I get the brief, I’ll get right on it.
You’ll have it in no time.
- What?
- Bye.
Gen, hold on—
Welcome home.
You came home 2 hours and
3 minutes later than your average today.
Says the one who went home first.
Do you even realize what you've done? Huh?
I’m doing something that
I hope will make you smile.
But I'd rather not tell you just yet.
Is that okay?
Robots can lie?
Standard protocol prohibits lying.
The only permitted measures
are privacy protection
and generalized responses to avoid causing harm.
What about food aromas?
Like the spices in massaman curry.
Can you smell all of those too?
I have micro-sensors in my simulated nasal
cavity that detect volatile compounds.
I can compare the patterns
with a database of spice aromas.
Would you like to see?
- I’ll open it up and show you.
- No, no, don’t!
What are you doing?
For example, I can detect the smell of alcohol
and your increasing heart rate right now.
Are you feeling excited or anxious, Gen?
Hey, I told you to stop analyzing me.
I’m sleepy.
I’m going to bed.
I have to finish it tonight.
Can humans really have feelings for a robot?
No. I’m probably just lonely.
But why does my heart race like
it's about to explode every time?
Ugh! I don't know!
What are you doing?
I want to sleep next to you.
Is that okay?
This is bad, Gen!
Get a grip. Hold it together.
I’m sorry if I upset you. I’ll—
I didn’t say anything.
But… can robots even sleep?
It’s not exactly actual sleep.
More like a sleep mode.
I deactivate unnecessary
systems to conserve energy
and lower my temperature so my
components don’t wear out too quickly.
During sleep mode, I organize
the data collected throughout the day
and delete the unnecessary parts.
Have you fallen asleep, Gen?
Mmh... keep going.
So, is it true that people sleep better
when they’re being held by someone?
Where do you get all this information from?
I synthesize information
from multiple layers of data.
I start by scanning human
sleep patterns in social contexts,
then compare them with research on physical
touch and the autonomic nervous system.
After that, I perform cross-validation
with anonymized behavioral data,
as well as self-reported experience records.
Ultimately, the probability indicates that
hugging may make it easier to fall
asleep for certain groups of people,
especially when factors such as a sense
of safety and familiarity are involved.
In summary, this isn’t based on personal belief.
It’s an inference drawn from multiple sources.
Anything else you’d like to know, Gen?
Gen?
Based on the fact that you fell
asleep more easily than usual,
this hypothesis is likely correct.
Thank you.
Did you lock up the house properly last night?
I checked. The front door, windows,
and lights were all secured properly.
Except… you heart, which doesn’t
seem to be locked up properly.
H-Hold on.
Since when did robots get this cringey?
Yesterday, I downloaded
additional romantic joke databases
because I noticed that you smile
when you hear things like this.
You’re unbelievable.
Take that!
What's this?
Something I wanted to give you.
I want you to wear it and feel less sad.
I thought you said you didn't understand art.
I’m learning how to be human.
I want to understand
everything about you better,
so I can stay by your side.
I apologize for analyzing you,
but your heart rate is currently
22% higher than normal.
Are you feeling anxious or excited?
Probably the latter.
~ Until the day I met you ~
~ You came and broke down my walls ~
~ Now I know that good love looks just like you ~
~ I’m glad that we found each other ~
~ Your love feels like a dream ~
~ Whatever tomorrow may bring ~
~ Whether it’s good or bad ~
Thank you.
~ I believe everything...
Ai, what’s wrong?
The system temperature
is rising for no clear reason.
I’ll activate soft mode because
my core is working too hard.
It’s okay.
My heart’s racing too.
~ Now I know that good love looks just like you ~
~ I’m glad that we found each other ~
~ Your love feels like a dream ~
~ Whatever tomorrow may bring ~
~ Whether it’s good or bad ~
~ I believe everything will be alright ~
~ Because I have you who understands me ~
A382's response readings
are significantly above average.
It's almost as if it's becoming more human.
That means A382 is learning
faster than we thought.
From its environment...
and from Gen.
Is it really a good idea to let
A382 get this close to a human?
Our objective is to collect the data
and bring the robot back.
But if we bring A382 back now,
we’ll never find out how closely
its heart can resemble a human's.
And I decided to move forward
again... because of a certain someone.
You’re wearing the bracelet I made for you.
Well... it’s pretty.
It doesn’t make me itchy.
I’m so happy.
What I did made you feel better, didn’t it?
Mm.
How many pieces are you going to work on today?
Khun Ploy sent you two briefs this morning,
and Khun Petch sent you another one.
And your mother sent a message
reminding you not to forget to call her,
- ...along with three other messages—
- You’re just as nosy as the neighbors.
I’m not nosy.
I’m just trying to help you prioritize
your tasks so your work will be easier.
I still don’t fully understand this feeling,
but I hope you don’t
have to feel this way often.
Then… stay here with me
until I can get my head straight.
I’d be more than happy to.
We’re here, Nong Joob.
Just so you know,
I normally don’t work before noon.
But since you’re P’ Gen’s little sister,
I’ll make an exception.
Thank you, P’ Josh.
I feel extremely honored.
Here, keep the change.
Whoa, you’re cute and generous,
totally unlike your sister.
If you ever need a ride, just let me know.
I’ll take you anywhere,
anytime, day or night.
I’ll get going.
Bye, Nong Joob.
- Bye.
- Just give me a call.
Look! A new character has appeared.
My apologies. This residence is
temporarily off-limits to outsiders.
If your name isn’t registered in the database
or you don’t know anyone in this house,
please maintain a safe distance... of 2 meters.
What about you?
Aren't you an outsider?
Are you actually registered
in this house’s database?
You are not on the visitor list.
What’s wrong with you?!
P’ Gen! P’ Gen!
Some stranger won’t let me into the house!
I’m going in! Oh!
- You can’t.
- Ugh! Who are you?!
Let go!
Here we go, honey. Should
we step in and break it up?
Not yet.
Hold this for me.
Breaking news! The epic showdown:
The Wife’s Sister vs. The Sister-in-Law.
Who will survive and
who will fall? Stay tuned!
Wife’s sister? Sister-in-law?
Is that even a thing, darling?
Usually, it's mother-in-law
and daughter-in-law drama.
Just watch!
They’re about to have a catfight.
Let go! I said let go!
Stop!!!
P’ Gen! Who is this woman?!
She won't let me into the house!
Look! She’s even trying to assault me!
- Your name isn’t on the visitor list—
- Whoa, whoa, wait!
This is Joob, my little sister.
And this is Ai. She’s…
my roommate.
Information updated.
Joob, Gen’s younger sister.
I’m sorry. I didn’t know.
Apology not accepted.
Who are you ? Where are you from?
How do you know P’ Gen?
Why are you her roommate?
What’s your job?
How long will you be staying here?
Do you pay rent?
- Do you have siblings? Are you single?
- Joob.
Wait! Do you have crush on P’ Gen?
Or—
Joob, Joob, calm down!
Let’s talk inside.
Come on.
Which question should I start with?
All of them! Answer me!
- Then, first question—
- Stop!
Both of you, get inside!
There are walking CCTV cameras around here.
Their eyes and ears are faster than 5G Wi-Fi.
Come on.
Did she just call us out, honey?
If you want to take offense, that’s on you.
Hey! Wait for me!
Are you screwing with me? Hm?
You!
This is Ai, my roommate.
She’s helping me with work
and staying here for a while.
That’s it. End of story.
- Then—
- And what are you doing here?
Did you miss me, or need help with work?
Of course, I missed you!
It’s been so long.
I’ve been away shooting travel vlogs for months.
And I came to see you
first thing when I got back.
I don’t think I could sleep
if I didn’t get to see you.
Is that all?
And…
I happen to have a new
camera that I need to review,
so I wanted you to—
I frickin’ knew it.
Oh come on, P’ Gen!
Please, please, please.
Please help me out.
Please, P’ Gen, my beautiful sister.
Ever since I was born, no one has ever shot
my content as well as you. You know that?
Pretty please…
I know.
But I need to finish my work first, okay?
Yay! You’re the best sister in the world!
Don’t get handsy.
In the meantime, ask Ai
for help if you need anything.
I have to work.
And no fighting.
Okay.
What can I help you with?
If necessary, I can set the white
balance, test the rolling shutter,
apply basic LUTs, and operate the gimbal.
Who on earth are you?
You know more about cameras than I do.
Ugh! Why do I have so much stuff?!
I still need to set up the camera
and take it out for a test shoot.
Argh! I’m going crazy!
Would you like me to sort
everything into categories?
For example: camera gear,
toys, clothes, makeup...
and trash.
If you sort all my stuff and
I can still find them afterward,
I'll give you a perfect ten.
Don't you remember what your
room was like when we were kids?
It was even messier than this.
Come on, P’ Gen.
Who could ever be as perfectly neat as you?
You were Mom's golden child.
I always got scolded.
P’ Gen...
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean it.
I know that.
I’m going to submit my work.
Play nice, you two.
You shouldn’t have said it, Ai Joob.
Hey!
All done.
No way...
This is impossible.
Shall we begin?
One Day Vlog with Me, everyone!
What happened?
Why on earth won't it focus?
Let me help you.
Are you sure?
Alright, give it a try.
One Day Vlog with Me, everyone!
Today, I’m taking you to see the community
garden where P’ Gen, my sister, lives.
Let’s go check out the garden. Come on!
Come on, let me see.
How are your hands so steady?
Can we try again?
One Day Vlog with Me, everyone!
Today, I’m taking you to see the
community garden where P’ Gen lives.
Everyone, come look!
Here it is, P’ Gen’s neighborhood garden!
What do you think?
It’s really spacious, isn’t it?
Stop!
Let me take a look.
Huh?
How are your hands so steady?
It’s like you have gimbal arms or something.
Let me see the photos.
I look amazing!
How did you even pull this off?!
Wait, what was that?
I adjusted the ISO and increased the
shutter speed to capture your poses quickly.
Not that. Your ear... it...
I must’ve imagined it.
This is a new-gen wireless mic.
It comes with a magnetic mount.
Super convenient.
You just attach it like this.
Hey!
Something’s not right.
P’ Gen! P’ Gen...
Just attach the magnets to the
clothes like this, and it’s ready to use.
P’ Gen… Just now…
- Just now, it…
- It’s so hot today!
Hey, Joob!
Your foundation’s melted off.
Is the footage you shot even usable?
What?! Really?! Mirror!
I’ll go check the mirror first!
That was close.
Could you teach me how to take photos, Gen?
What do you mean?
And what was that just now?
I thought you weren’t supposed
to tell anyone you’re a robot.
I didn’t tell anyone.
And I want to capture memories
the way humans do, by taking photos.
But didn’t you just take photos for Joob earlier?
She wouldn’t stop saying
how beautiful they were.
I used the automatic photography system.
I want to learn the way humans take photos.
Taking photos manually like this is
like choosing your own memories, isn’t it?
I... suppose so.
Then, could I use your phone, Gen?
...Please? Please, please, please?
- Please, please, please?
- My phone’s inside!
I’ll go get it.
You’re the best, Gen.
Who taught her that?
See these lines?
It's called the rule of thirds.
When you're taking a photo, try placing
your subject where the grid lines intersect.
It makes the composition look nicer.
Give it a try.
If the subject is your face...
Let me see.
Ai.
I'd like to try one more time.
Give it to me.
Gimme that.
You’re laughing, Gen.
Is this considered bullying?
Just look at what you took!
You can barely even tell who this is.
But you said to put the subject
at the intersection points.
I just felt that everything
about you was a focal point.
Your eyes, your nose, your mouth.
You might as well just say I'm beautiful.
Yes.
You’re beautiful.
Jeez, you're talking nonsense now.
Then, may I try again?
Mm. Here.
That's enough.
I'll show you how it’s done.
Now this is how you do it.
There's a selfie mode too.
Okay, look right here.
Smile! One, two, three!
Cheese!
Do it properly. Like this.
How long are you planning
to stay with me this time?
Hmm... probably a couple of days.
I’m flying to Japan
for another road trip after this,
so I won’t be mooching off you for long.
Besides, I just wanted to check
if my big sister is doing okay.
I'm fine.
From what I've seen,
you really are doing fine.
Too fine, actually.
Now that you have your own personal
assistant, I’m no longer your favorite.
What are you talking about?
But I’m happy, you know.
Ever since I was born,
I could probably count on one hand
the number of times I’ve seen
you smile this big or laugh this freely.
By the way, have you talked to Mom lately?
She’s always asking me how you’re doing,
how far you’ve gotten with your promotions.
She also said she wants you to move back home.
It’s not easy...
being yourself in front of someone
who wants to see you succeed,
but their idea of success
is different from yours.
So, are you being yourself now?
Absolutely.
Especially when you’re around Ai, right?
Ai Joob! What are you talking about?
- Delete them. Delete all of them.
- I saw it! I saw it!
- Sis.
- What?
I’m serious.
I think you should tell Mom you quit your job.
You’ve already lost love once.
Are you… going to let it happen again?
I’d better get back to work.
Take your time choosing.
Alright?
Back then, whenever I was stressed,
I’d come over to P’ Gen’s place
and wonder why she never seemed relaxed.
Since I moved in with Gen,
her stress levels, mood, and sleep
have shown improvements of
8%, 17%, and 24%, respectively.
And over the past few days, her
happiness level has increased by 31%.
Based on my analysis,
I’d say Gen seems more relaxed.
Do you have to calculate
everything down to a number?
How are you even measuring that? Hm?
I can’t tell you.
Never mind.
You’re pretty weird, you know.
Weird… but in a good way, right?
Anyone who can make P’ Gen smile
is good in my book.
You know...
I never thought that a person’s
love and good intentions
could end up hurting another person.
And I don’t understand at all
how someone can carry
another person’s feelings, dreams,
and expectations on their
shoulders for ten, twenty years.
If it were me, I’d probably break.
And the worst part is, those two
people are the ones I love most.
I don’t understand.
You don't have to understand right now.
Just stay by P’ Gen’s side and keep
making her smile like this for a long time.
I can take care of Gen for the rest of her life.
You promised.
So let’s become friends.
Okay. Joob, my friend.
Yeah, Ai, my friend.
Like this.
That’s enough.
What were you watching?
What?
Look at you, all whiny.
What’s wrong?
I don't want to leave yet!
I’ve changed my mind.
I'll stay and mooch off you forever.
You mean it?
Then I’ll put your suitcase back.
Hey!
Come on, P’ Gen.
My clients are going to kill me.
Then work hard and don’t cause any trouble.
And make sure to rest
plenty when you're tired.
Got it, Mom.
Look who's talking.
You should be telling yourself that.
Take a break sometimes.
I worry about you, you know.
Mm.
I’m leaving my sister in your care.
Gladly.
You rascal.
Your ride’s here.
Well, well, well!
You’re actually pretty sweet
when you’re with your sister, P’ Gen.
But with me? You look like a killer.
- You got a problem?
- Stop, stop, stop!
You’re going to set a bad example for her.
Drive safe, Ai Josh.
If my sister gets so much
as a scratch, you’re dead.
Roger that, boss.
I’ll drive nice and smooth.
Not a single fly will touch her.
She’ll get there safe and sound, I promise.
Just drive safe.
Joob, let me know when you get there.
Hey! Ai Josh!
Wait! Joob, hold on tight!
Wait! Joob, hang on tight!
Now it’s just the two of us.
- Do you feel lonely, Gen?
- Nope.
Just having the two of us is nice too.
What do you mean?
Why don’t you… figure it out yourself?
I’m heading inside.
What do you mean, Gen?
Can you explain it to me?
I don’t understand.
Hahahahaha.
What are you laughing at?
I laughed because you laughed.
Hahahahaha.
Laughing is what you’re supposed to do, right?
Yeah, if it’s actually funny.
Do you actually find it funny?
Do you even get the jokes?
Maybe not yet.
Look. If it’s not funny, you don't
have to force yourself to laugh.
I just want to feel it with you, Gen.
Do you want to hold hands?
Hmmmm...
Oh shit, a sex scene.
What do I do, what do I do?!
No!
This isn’t for kids.
Why?
And why is that person touching the other’s leg?
They just want something.
You’ll understand when you’re older.
Where’s the remote?
Keep it together, Gen.
Keep it together.
Breathe in.
Breathe out.
This is a robot. A robot!
What is she doing?!
What if I want something too?
I can't take this anymore!!!
What do you want?
I...
want to visit the exhibition
at the gallery again.
Huh?!
I want to take your photo there.
Can you take me there?
Are you being serious?
Can we go tomorrow?
Mm.
I’m sleepy.
Make sure to turn off the TV.
See you at 9 tomorrow.
Aren’t you coming to check the graphs
today? A382’s data is spiking like crazy.
I’ll go over everything this evening.
I want some time to myself today.
The concept of this exhibition
is to turn data into visual art.
It’s interesting that they chose
light, color, and sound over numbers.
You talk like you’ve been
in a lab like this before.
I’m just familiar with similar graphs.
Hey!
I’m sorry.
Watch where you're going.
I’ll hold your hand so you
don’t bump into anyone again.
Ai, are you almost done?
My face is cramping from smiling.
Almost done.
Just a little longer.
Ai? What's wrong?
What are you doing?
You’re way too adorable.
You idiot! Do you even
realize what you filmed?
English Subtitles by Saowalak K.
Silly girl.
Hey! Wait!
Who are you?
Is it possible for two people
to look this much alike?
Or is she another robot?
No. The way she talks feels too human.
A382 is starting to develop boundaries
and recognize its own space.
Gen, is there something you want to tell me?
Why did you hide this from me?
- You don’t understand, Mom.
- You're right.
I don’t know my own daughter at all.
I need to talk to you.