[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[MARLA]
They say the universe has rules.
Invisible ones.
Unbreakable ones.
Like the
Pauli Exclusion Principle.
The Pauli Exclusion Principle
says,
"No two identical things
can exist in the same space
at the same time."
Ms. Briones, done already?
Yes, Ma'am.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
Ma'am, I need to tell you
something.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC SWELLS]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MARLA] So sometimes,
if you want something in...
something else has to get out.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
April Javier,
wait for me outside.
I'll take you to the
principal's office later.
[MARLA] Because sometimes,
for things to fall into place,
Miss Javier.
Out!
Something...
or someone...
has to go.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MUSIC STOPS]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
So, I guess we can agree
that we're all wasting time.
[ISOBEL] Marla,
I know I'm the only psycho
in here,
but are you out of your mind?
Wait.
Girl, no way,
this isn't girl's girls, no.
Wait a minute.
Let's listen to Marla first.
[CHAIR SCREECHING]
Why are you so shocked?
[MARLA] Isn’t this the whole
reason of our girl group?
To take revenge on the
people who've wronged us.
And obviously, April wronged us.
She leaked our nudes!
Through Cole's coercion.
[ISOBEL] Where do you think
she got those photos?
So what if it's true?
[DAPHNE] She had a choice
to not do it, right?
- Agree.
- But she still did it.
[NYX] But girl,
there's still this thing.
I'm wondering, why?
What does she get out of it?
What?
April wants to get back at me!
Because I reported her
for cheating before.
Of course, you're going to
make this about yourself.
[ISOBEL] Marla, our nude photos
were released.
Including that of April's.
Why are you just so lovesick,
that your genius brain
is just malfunctioning?
Excuse me,
what does my genius brain
have to do with this?
And you really have to leave out
the fact that you're lovesick,
and really stupid with boys.
Hey!
[NYX] Girls, calm down.
Take a deep breath.
Breathe in, breathe out.
[INHALES, EXHALES]
I understand the both of you.
Yeah, it's true.
Our lives were really ruined...
when those nudes were leaked.
But... but!
Just look now.
We're eligible for honors
again because
we won the Hackathon, right?
Remember?
You know, technically...
Technically, we already
got what we wanted.
So, can we just...
forget about the revenge part?
- Huh?
- [IN UNISON] No!
That's your common ground?
Girls.
May I just remind you.
We became eligible
for honors, again...
because of Cole.
I don't owe him anything.
Yes! Correct.
We don't owe him anything.
But if you think about it...
if he really wanted
to destroy us,
he wouldn't have helped us.
He wouldn't have agreed
to help us
if he really wanted to
bring us down, right?
I mean, make it make sense.
Come on.
The only thing
that's making sense right now
is April's motive.
We’re being sidetracked.
That's Cole's goal.
[ISOBEL] We have to remember
our original plan
in targeting Mr. Ramirez.
He's in our way.
He protected Migo
and in doing so,
he protected the boys.
I Agree-ana Grande with you.
[NYX] That's it.
But, still.
Poor April.
I feel bad for her.
She's unaware that
she's being groomed.
How crazy.
What's it again,
what's that word again?
- Lovesick.
- Lovesick!
Lovesick, oh my God.
The probability is also high
that if we succeed
in our revenge
against Mr. Ramirez,
we'll also succeed in
our revenge against the boys.
[DAPHNE] Migo will drop out,
and Cole loses another lackey.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Okay, fine.
[MARLA] As long as
we don’t involve April
in our future plans,
sure.
Okay.
Let's get to it then.
Our main target...
is Migo.
[MARLA] And through
Mister Oliver,
we can kill two birds
with one stone.
Our only problem is...
how do we get evidence?
Especially now without April?
Although, even if she were here,
it's not like she would feed
Mister Oliver to the alligators.
Um...
Girl?
My yellow ribbon asks,
are we the alligators?
[FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING]
There's only one way
to find evidence.
Shit.
Wait...
Uh...
I don't understand.
Why did you say shit?
[FOREBODING MUSIC CONTINUES]
There's only one person...
who can hack anything else...
aside from April.
Ah, shit!
- Ohh!
- Oh... shit.
Basically...
the target...
will become...
our ally.
[GASPS]
A sacrifice.
[NYX] Ally.
[FOREBODING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[CLEARS THROAT]
[SCOFFS]
Are you ready to do
what is necessary for...
- justice?
- [WHIMPERING]
Sis...
It's like my brain broke
into two.
I'm having second thoughts
right now.
Why must it be me?
I know I'm the eye candy of
our girl group, but...
- do you want to take over, sis?
- [DAPHNE SCOFFS]
Do you want me to
get murdered by Lester?
- Not me.
- What?
Are you and Lester
still together?
I didn't say that.
What I mean is,
he gets jealous quick
and I think,
he hasn't moved on
from my beauty.
But, there's no time for
second thoughts 'cause...
between the two of us,
you're Miss Congeniality, right?
So... You totally got this.
All we really need is for him
to help us hack Mr. Ramirez
without him knowing.
So you can do this.
[FAKE WHIMPERS]
April!
Why did you have to be
on hiatus?
Hiatus?! [EXHALES SHARPLY]
We wouldn't have to face
this problem tonight.
- Right?
- Enough, it's alright.
April won't help us anyway...
I suspect she even installed
cybersecurity in his phone.
But, what if...
- [GASPS]
- [THUDS]
What the--
Hey.
Hi, Migosky.
What're you doing, Nyx?
[LAUGHS WRYLY]
Hello, Migosky.
Are you feeling okay?
You look sick.
[GASPS SOFTLY]
- [WHINING]
- Ah! Ah!
- Wait, wait, wait...
- [BAWLS]
- What's the problem now?
Wait, wait, wait!
No, no, no!
Wait! Stop crying, stop crying!
Stop...
Ah...
[NYX BAWLING]
Are you okay?
[QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING]
[CHAIR SLIDES]
It's...
It's Mr. Ramirez...
- [NYX SIGHS]
- Huh?! Mr. Ramirez?!
Don't tell me you fell
for him too?
- You, too?
- No-- Not me!
I mean...
I mean, did he also
give you...
...low grades in robotics?
Oh my gosh...
You know,
I think it's so unfair.
Why?
Why? Because my works
are colorful?
Full of life?
Littered with hues?
I didn't deserve that.
Did I deserve that?
Of course not, Nyx.
Uh...
You know, for me...
You're the best in Robotics.
[QUIRKY MUSIC CONTINUES]
Exactly, right?
[STAMMERS]
I don't deserve that at all.
That's why... [CLEARS THROAT]
You need to help me to...
access...
...and hack the system.
[SNICKERS]
All his profiles and...
accounts he uses...
...connected with
professors of SOSH.
So, I can get what I deserve.
- Oh, wait a minute, Nyx.
- You can do it.
You know, I really believe
you can do it.
- Nyx.
- No offense,
isn't that what you did...
- Nyx.
- to get back in...
Section 1?
Nyx, I'm telling you...
I want something in return.
[QUIRKY MUSIC CONTINUES]
What do you want?
You know what I want?
For you to help
with my Calculus assignment.
Huh?
[MIGO] Yes.
Idiot.
You're so good at hacking
and manipulating test results.
Yet you still need help with...
Calculus?
You don't understand.
What...
you're asking of me,
it's not that easy.
Ever since your nudes
were leaked,
if you only knew,
it's so difficult to hack
the school system here.
It's no joke, Nyx.
What you're asking of me,
it's nearly impossible, Nyx.
I'm aware...
I know I'm so good.
I'm not just good--
Gosh, I'm handsome,
charming, everything.
I can do anything.
I'm really one of the
best hackers in the world, Nyx.
The hackers I faced off against,
all veteran hackers,
truly the hustler hackers
in the whole country.
Then the virus they've put,
is one of the
most poisonous virus ever.
Like gremlins which
if attacked,
it multiplies
over and over again.
Goodness. [SIGHS]
There's no one like Migo.
Right, Nyx?
- Hey, Nyx!
- Oh, poor you!
Really?
- Whatever you explained to me.
- I know right.
- I feel for you.
- Yes. [MOUTH CLICKS]
- Right?
- It was just too much, girl.
There.
I think...
you can help me anyway, yeah?
All we just need is
to access and...
...hack to manipulate my--
M-My grades in Robotics.
Right?
I think, you can do it.
Please?
Pretty please?
[CHUCKLES SLIGHTLY]
You have such beautiful eyes.
[QUIRKY MUSIC CONTINUES]
You flirt!
You're such a cutie!
Oh, you're really cute!
I get the charm.
- You're so charming, you know?
- [MIGO CHUCKLES]
Charming.
Alright, give it to me.
Perfect.
I'll help you with Calculus,
promise.
Here it is, I'm ready.
See how pretty my laptop is,
it even has flowers!
It's like you were so sure
I'd help you out, huh?
- Prepared?
- Of course!
Who could even...
resist my...
facecard?
With this bangs?
Oh my gosh!
It's irresistible, you know?
Do it!
Whatever you say.
[KEYBOARDS CLANKING]
[SYSTEM CHIMES]
[QUIRKY MUSIC CONTINUES]
This is wrong!
- [LAPTOP SLAMS]
- [GRUNTS]
- It's not me!
- Don't you slam
my pretty laptop!
You know, Migo,
you're my crush.
[GIGGLES]
I wanted to tell you I've had
a crush on you for a long time.
- Really?
- Uh-huh.
Since twenty...
...four hours ago?
[GIGGLES]
You're really the cutest.
Really?
I'm your crush?
Yes, I already told you.
Please just help me.
Come on.
[SIGHS] Okay, fine.
[QUIRKY MUSIC CONTINUES]
[DOOR OPENS]
Hey, Daphne.
What are you doing here?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[DAPHNE] Hey, April.
What's with the questions?
Are you Principal Mckenna?
Do you own this school
or something?
You look suspicious, Daphne.
You girls planned
something again?
Plan?
Stuttering.
We're not planning anything,
April!
What was that?
Look here.
Like my screen?
It's got a privacy
screen protector.
Cool, right?
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Are you targeting me?
Wow! You're full of yourself!
- Who's there?
- Stop it!
Step aside or else.
Or else what?
You know, Nyx,
I'm telling you,
if April didn't worm her way in,
I would've courted you.
[QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING]
[CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY]
So, you're threatening me?
I'm gonna rough you up.
You think you scare me, Daphne?
I'm used to getting beaten up.
- Hey!
- It's off-limits! Go away--
- Get out of my way!
- No! You can't!
- [DAPHNE] No! No! Stop!
- [APRIL] Move!
What's that?
Hm?
[MIGO GRUNTS]
[ROMANTIC MUSIC PLAYING]
Mm! Wow!
You're already done?
You did great, Migo!
- Wow!
- Wow...
You're really something!
- No way!
- Get out of my way!
- Stop it!
- I'll take your headband!
I'll take your headphones!
- You really won't stop, huh?
- Ouch!
[APRIL] Daphne!
Where are you going?
Please just stop.
Hey, Daphne!
You're the best.
Wow.
Nyx?
- Okay! Perfect!
- Nyx?
- Goodbye!
You know what,
I think... I think...
I'm think I'm not thinking.
- Nyx?
- Take care. Bye!
Nyx! Nyx, if you
ever need anything,
just kiss me!
I mean, text me!
[QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING]
[SIGHS HAPPILY]
I've already told you girls,
my plate is full.
I can't help you.
But, sir,
we really need your help
on our thesis.
We read your article
about AI becoming
maternal systems.
You said...
that in the future,
AI-assisted breastfeeding
support will proliferate
to help in monitoring latching,
feeding patterns.
That article of yours...
[IN UNISON]
"Your Mother's An AI."
[MARLA] Yes, sir.
[OLIVER SCOFFS]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
I can’t believe you girls
actually read that.
[CHUCKLES] Of course.
We look up to you.
[OLIVER CHUCKLES]
I mean,
thank you.
You know, not a lot
of students actually
take an interest
in what I write.
But clearly,
you two are not like
a lot of the students.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Why don't we...
talk about this over dinner?
My treat.
Hm.
You know, we shouldn't
be limited to the classroom.
And clearly,
we are more comfortable
when it's just us.
So...
You're both very mature
for your age.
It's like...
it's like you can actually
understand what I'm saying.
- [OLIVER] You know?
- I agree.
You?
Mm-hmm.
Sir...
I made this
especially for you.
Cookies.
Alright.
You made these, huh?
Mm-hmm.
And...
how did you know
that I like cookies?
Have you...
Have you two been spying on me?
[BOTH CHUCKLE NERVOUSLY]
Oh, you wouldn't know.
What?
[CHUCKLES] Okay.
Go on, sir.
Try it.
[ISOBEL] Take a bite.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[MARLA] Mm.
[SPITS]
[OLIVER] What the hell is this?
Oops.
What's wrong?
I'm sorry, sir.
I didn't know you had such
a low tolerance to spice.
[ISOBEL] Oh.
It's okay, I can save you.
Water?
[MARLA] That's...
chili and wasabi flavor.
Wasabi?
In a cookie?
[MARLA]
Just trying something new.
[ISOBEL] There you go.
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
[GRUNTS, INHALES SHARPLY]
[ISOBEL] All done.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Okay.
It's gone...
the spice.
[MARLA AND ISOBEL] Aww...
[MARLA] But, what do you feel?
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Dizziness...
[THUDS]
K.O.
Just like we planned.
[SHUDDERS]
I was acting like you
for a second.
How do you...
not close your eyes.
My eyes hurt.
I don't blink too much.
I'm human.
It's normal.
Good job. Good job.
Oh!
Good night!
[MARLA GIGGLES]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
[CLAPS SLOWLY]
[GRIM MUSIC PLAYING]
- [CHAIR RATTLES]
- [INHALES DEEPLY]
What the fuck is going on here?
Welcome to your
worst nightmare.
[CLAPS] Huh!
You need to resign now.
And leave the school.
[ISOBEL] Quietly.
[GARBLED] Or else...
something bad
will happen to you.
What?
Nyx, what?
Hey, girl.
Come on, move on already.
It's just a kiss.
You don't understand.
He's got very bad breath.
Felt it down my throat.
You girls are
fucking unbelievable.
What is this, a joke?
What is this, a prank?!
What? Am I viral now?
Oh, you will be.
If you don't leave SOSH.
[EXHALES] Shit.
I think you know exactly
why you're here.
These are the girls you played.
The ones you promised
you'll marry.
You're a predator!
Predator...
[INHALES SHARPLY]
I got a word for you:
"consensual."
[OLIVER]
You know what that word means?
You should know, you're Top 1!
"Consensual" means,
I never forced
any of these girls
to be in a relationship
with me.
[SCOFFS]
And for fuck's sake, guys,
come on,
why would you believe anything
that these crazy people say?
Hannah?
Scarlet?
You both know,
the love I had for you
was real.
It just didn't work out.
[ISOBEL]
What are you, a teenager?
You’re in a position of power.
You’re our professor,
for crying out loud.
Maybe it's you who's crazy.
Consensual?
Consensual, your face!
[OBJECTS CLATTER]
This is consensual.
[CLIPS CLACK]
[SWATS]
[SNAPS]
[CLIP CLACKS]
[STAPLER CLICKS]
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
I thought...
I was special.
But, I was just one of many.
I've been waiting so long...
to take you down!
Scarlet...
Wait a second,
just so I won't forget anything.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
You told me,
you cared about me.
You told me I was different.
You told me I was mature enough,
making me think,
that makes it okay.
[HUFFS]
But, you're the adult.
You knew exactly
what you were doing,
and I didn't.
If you want more emotional,
- more angry,
- Girl!
or more colder.
Girl, you forgot to edit.
[MARLA] Is that a screenshot?
It's ChatGPT.
You could have cited
your sources instead.
That's okay.
- [MARLA] It's okay, it's okay.
- It's okay.
It's okay. It really is.
It's fine, just...
- just get another clip.
- Grab a clip.
- It's fine.
- Get two.
- Now, get three.
- Another one.
- Yes!
- Perfect!
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
Is that it?
You're happy now?
You got your revenge.
Was it...
supposed to make a difference?
You girls are acting like
I was the only one
who had fun
during our times together.
If I remember correctly,
I was even the one
who broke up with you.
[INHALES, EXHALES DEEPLY]
Marla.
Nyx.
Isobel.
- Daphne
- What?!
Untie me now.
Or I'll make sure that...
you'll never graduate.
You're threatening us.
He's right.
This isn't enough.
We have to end his bloodline.
[MARLA] Mm-hmm...
[APRIL] Mr. Oliver?
Girls, what the fuck?
Untie him now.
- April, girl.
- Girl.
It's not your cue yet.
What cue?
Ah...
But you're here anyway.
I'm sure you heard
the testimonials...
testimonials?!
...of the girls.
This is for your own good.
No!
This is all staged
just to break us up.
You don't know the feeling...
You don't know how finally,
I have someone
who makes me feel safe.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
My whole family
doesn't even care about me.
They don't even believe in me!
But Oliver...
Oliver makes me feel that I...
I matter.
He protects me and he guides me.
And that's none
of your business.
That's why I'll
never abandon you
We love each other, right?
Oliver?
April...
I wish...
I've never been
involved with you.
If it wasn't for you...
I wouldn't be here.
You are my biggest mistake.
[WHISPERS] Wow.
[SOFTLY] How shameless...
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[RING THUDS, CLATTERS]
You disgust me!
[BREATH QUIVERS]
[FOOTSTEPS RECEDING]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[THUDS]
April.
If you change your mind...
[THUDS]
[DAPHNE] Let's go.
[FOOTSTEPS RECEDING]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[CRYING, SOBBING]
[SOBBING]
[APRIL SNIFFLES]
- [TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [APRIL SOBBING QUIETLY]
[SNIFFLES]
[MUSIC FADES]
[DEFIANT MUSIC PLAYING]
[DEFIANT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[DEFIANT MUSIC TURNS TRIUMPHANT]
[DEFIANT MUSIC PLAYING]
[DEFIANT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MUSIC FADES]
[DEFIANT MUSIC SWELLS]
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[DEFIANT MUSIC PLAYING]
[DEFIANT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MUSIC STOPS]
[SOFT CHIME]
- Cheers!
- Cheers.
[MARLA] Oliver out.
Migo will eventually fall.
Drink up, everyone.
[CLEARS THROAT]
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[INHALES SHARPLY]
What did you do?
We just want to know the truth.
Bitch! What is this?
Betrayal?
Is this a coup?
Is this the Senate?
Hey, girls.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Are you back together
with your exes?
- No!
- No.
Let me
rephrase the question.
Did you ever break up...
with your exes?
Cole broke up with me, remember?
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
- No.
- Got you, girl!
I knew it.
Do you plan on breaking up
with Cole, Marla?
I'm trying to fix things.
Not try?
You jealous?
[ISOBEL] You wish.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
You stupid, stupid girl.
Why am I stupid...
when you're the one who
can't see the evidence
right in front of you?
[MARLA] April is the one
who can't be trusted!
Why?
Is April the only one who
should be held accountable?
Wait a second!
Why are you talking like that?
Sure.
Let’s say they didn't
leak our private photos.
[ISOBEL] You saw
their group chat.
You saw all of their messages,
how they checked
and rated your bodies.
And you know.
You remember.
It's disgusting!
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
What if..
it's just AI?
[DAPHNE] April could've
faked it, right?
You both look pathetic!
[ISOBEL] I pity you.
Both in denial.
They're lost cases, Nyx.
It's really difficult going
against people who
choose to play blind when
faced with the truth.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
To tell you the truth, girls.
You're unfair.
You forced me to break up
with Ant,
then you have the audacity
to relapse?!
My God, so unfair!
[NYX] And on top of that...
you forced me
to make out with Migo!
- You're driving me crazy!
- Hold on, Nyx.
Wait a minute.
Let's check the facts.
You chose to kiss Migo.
Besides, even if we didn't
meddle with you and Ant,
you'd never last anyway
because he's into boys!
I love him!
Stop!
Why are we fighting?
We're not supposed
to be fighting!
We share one goal.
We share one enemy.
April is not the enemy!
Enough!
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Isobel?
You say you pity me?
No!
I pity you.
So incapable of love.
That is your defect!
- [TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [MARLA BREATHING HEAVILY]
Guys.
I'm so sick.
I'm so sick of
all this fighting,
all this goddamn fighting.
Every day, we're fighting.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
I just want my high school life
to go back to normal.
Is that so hard to ask?
That's why Cole and I...
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
We're trying to fix things.
[MARLA INHALES SHARPLY]
What?
You're judging me?
It's so easy for you to call me
dumb and stupid.
It's so easy for you to say that
this is not worth anything,
but...
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
It is for me.
Why would you condemn me
for staying?
I believe,
there's still hope for us.
I'm the only one who knows.
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Nyx.
You would know, right?
Out of all the people here,
you should understand me.
You know, girl...
It's all right to hope.
[NYX] To wish...
that maybe they'll change.
It's possible, so go.
I'll give you that.
But you know what's wrong?
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
It's that you two still hope
and believe
that you'll be the ones who
will change Cole and Lester.
That will never happen!
Cole and Lester will never
change just for you two!
That's what
you don't understand!
You're driving me crazy.
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
The truth is...
they're the ones changing
the both of you.
[NYX] You can't see it yet.
But I can see it clearly.
We can all see it.
Something bad...
is going to happen.
And we...
won't be there
to catch you anymore.
Are you threatening us?
[FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING]
Yes.
So, stay out of our way.
[FOREBODING MUSIC CONTINUES]
So...
this is war?
Are we disbanding?
It seems so.
[FOREBODING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Nyx?
You're siding with the enemy.
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
Which enemy are
we talking about?
[FOREBODING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Don't worry.
Marla?
Daphne?
We'll go easy on you.
[APRIL] Besides,
it's Cole and Lester who
we're really after.
We're just sorry...
if you two become
collateral damage.
[FOREBODING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MUSIC TURNS PLAYFUL]
[LINE RINGING]
Hello, Mommy?
Guess what?
Top 10!
[GIGGLING] Yes!
Thank you!
[LESTER] Wait.
Wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Top 9?!
What...
What the fuck?
No!
How did I end up at Top 9?
[EARL] Yes!
I knew it!
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
No...
I was just lucky.
Charming?
You and I need to talk.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
It's okay.
I know you did your best.
Wow.
[CHUCKLES]
Congratulations, babe.
You did it again.
Top 1!
Look!
Goodness!
[GIGGLES]
Proud of you, babe.
You're not mad at me?
Babe, you know...
after everything
we've been through,
what I realized was...
these rankings
don't really matter to me.
Top 1, Top 2, Top 5.
You're all that matters to me.
I don't want to compete anymore.
What's the point, right?
Even if Dad beats me up,
even if he hurts me,
I'd take it all.
Because all that matters is you.
What we have right now.
Congratulations, babe.
I've got a smart,
beautiful girlfriend.
[BOTH GIGGLE]
Thank you.
I think...
we deserve to celebrate?
- Ooh. Okay.
- Right?
[BOTH GIGGLE]
Hold on. I need to get
something from the locker room.
Okay.
Oh, babe, wait!
I forgot something.
[SMOOCHES]
- Love you, babe.
- I love you too.
See you later.
[GIGGLES]
[DARK MUSIC PLAYING]
[DARK MUSIC CONTINUES]
Mama...
Daddy!
[WHINING]
[HUFFS]
Damn.
That... Riely or whatever,
tried to outsmart me.
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
Anyway.
Do you want to
go out for dinner, or...
would you rather be...
my dinner?
My treat.
And besides, I...
- [THUDS]
- need to let off some steam.
I missed you so much.
[DAPHNE BREATHING HEAVILY]
Lester.
Really? Here at school?
[SCOFFS] What's wrong?
There are CCTVs here.
Babe, we're not going
to get caught anyway.
Do you know who my mom is?
And besides, we're not
the only ones kissing here.
there's other people
kissing here, too.
Yeah?
- [SLAMS]
- Huh?
Hmm?
- Lester.
- Hmm?
- No!
- What is your problem?
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
Daph?
[SCOFFS]
Is this about your rankings?
Huh?
Baby. Babe.
Look at me.
You did great.
Better than me.
Huh?
[SCOFFS]
You know,
you shouldn't stress
about your rankings,
in the future, babe.
You have me.
And dedicate yourself.
Once I inherit
my dad's business,
you'll have nothing
to worry about.
- I said stop!
- Ahh!
It's just you and me,
loving husband and wife.
[CHUCKLES]
Hey, Daph?
You know,
when we're together,
you can just stay home...
You know, do some yoga...
read a book.
Hey!
Learn how to cook for me,
for your future husband.
Yeah?
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
That's exactly
what my mother told me.
Because she is true.
Like I said,
you can just stay home...
do yoga, read a book, relax.
While I get that bread, yeah?
Hey!
I mean it.
I love you, Daph.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SMOOCHES]
Lester...
Lester, I don't want to.
I said stop!
I said stop it!
[GRUNTS]
I don't want to!
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
- [THUD]
- [GRUNTS]
[GRUNTING]
[THUD]
[DAPHNE WHIMPERS]
Does it hurt?
Does that hurt?!
[THUD]
[SMOOCHES]
Lester!
- Lester!
- Come on, hit me!
Come on, I'll lighten it up.
Hit me.
Hit me!
Fucking slap me!
Don't you want to?
- Okay.
- [GRUNTS]
Okay. Okay.
- [UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [BREATHING HEAVILY]
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Wait, wait... w--
Daph?
[DOCTOR] Continue compressions.
One milligram epinephrine
administered.
Check rhythm.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
[MUSIC BECOMES SUSPENSEFUL]
Miss, which room number does...
Dessalyn Baldemor stay?
There on the right, Ma'am.
[MACHINE BEEPING]
[DOCTOR] Continue compressions!
Check rhythm!
[NURSE] There's no pulse, doc.
[DOCTOR] Asystole.
[MACHINE BEEPING RAPIDLY]
Check rhythm.
Stop compressions.
No pulse...
no spontaneous breathing.
Time of death, 8:47 PM.
Kindly notify her family.
I'll talk to them personally.
- [MACHINE BEEPS]
- [SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
Daphne!
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]