- When Dad tried to win your heart,
what did he do?
- Your dad often patted me on my butt.
- Huh?
- Why are you patting on my butt?
- It’s covered with sand.
- Don’t pat on my butt.
- Can you tell what I’m thinking right now?
- You’re getting too close.
- Are you crossing the line?
- You crossed it first last night.
August, what volume are you up to
in the manga?
Volume 30.
What about you?
Volume 39.
Guys, I’m here.
How are the photos, Achi?
Let me see.
Achi, your face looks so funny in this picture.
You look dumbfounded.
(The photo album is a sign that…)
(the carefree days of childhood are slowly turning into the journey of adulthood.)
(We want to cherish this happiness
while it lasts.)
(The charm of a film camera is that…)
(the most outtake photo is taken
when we had the biggest laugh.)
(Each photo can be taken only once.)
(It’s the first time we wore colorful clothes
that we’d never wear again.)
(It’s the first time we stole our dad’s wax
to copy our favorite celebrity’s hairstyle.)
(It’s the first time we wore our favorite shoes
and walked out with confidence.)
(It’s the first time
we did many crazy things together.)
(It’s also the first time…)
(that we experienced love.)
Augar, look.
You look so funny in this photo.
Stop it, Achi.
Guys.
I have something to show you today.
What is it?
Now, I have my own phone.
I also have one.
Me too.
My phone is a newer model.
I also got a new phone.
My mom gave my old phone
to our house helper.
Now, this is brag-worthy.
Why do your phones look so good?
Your phone is an older model.
This is not cool.
But it’s okay.
At least it’s more convenient
to contact you guys now.
Good. I won’t feel lonely now.
When I was the only one who had a phone,
I had no one to call.
Are you trying to flex on us?
Hey.
Let’s exchange our numbers.
Ko Neung and Ko Song,
you don’t have to do that.
You are living next door to each other.
You guys hang out every day.
You’re so damn annoying.
Of course,
we need to have each other’s numbers.
In case of an emergency.
Did any of you get the postcard that we sent?
What do you mean?
How are we going to get it?
Didn’t we send it to someone else?
I mean…
What Ko Song means is that
if we wrote it to our future selves.
Right?
I wrote to myself.
Me too.
See? We all wrote to ourselves.
Are you sure?
What did you write to yourself?
It’s none of your business.
I can write whatever I want.
Don’t be so nosy.
Are you having a secret with me?
You guys are having a secret with me, right?
August, if you are saying this,
doesn’t it mean you didn’t write to yourself?
Tell us who you wrote it to.
Who did you write it to?
I wrote to my parents.
I wrote to wish them good health.
Ptooey!
Did you write a birthday card?
I don’t believe you.
It’s obvious that you are lying, August.
This is odd.
Are you flirting with a girl without telling me?
August.
You guys are ganging up on me.
You guys are in a relationship.
August, what the hell are you saying?
Ouch.
Hey!
Little boy, get in.
Augar, do you know how to drive?
Sure.
What is this?
Ko Neung, get in.
Augar.
Do you know how to drive?
Sure.
Ko Song, get in.
Augar, do you know how to drive?
Sure.
So now we can take a trip, right?
We can take a trip without any worries.
That’s right, Achi.
Do you want to go to Bangkok?
I can show you around the city.
The kid from Bangkok is showing off.
I mean it.
I want to go to Chiang Mai.
My dad has a house there.
Do you want to go?
This is a real example of showing off.
Why didn’t August come with you?
He wasn’t home.
Augar, where do you want to go?
Yes, where do you intend to go?
No.
Where are you taking us?
I just want to go for a drive.
Why?
Don’t you have a destination in mind?
Augar, you are going quite slow?
Your speed is only 60 km per hour.
We are not in a rush, right?
What’s wrong, Augar?
The weather is not hot.
Are you sick?
Why are you unusually quiet?
I want you guys to be my witness.
For what?
This is my first time driving.
How is it?
You don’t mind it, right?
Thanks for trusting me.
Stop talking and
just pay attention to the road.
I get it.
But I have my driving license.
Augar!
Here.
Thanks.
Can I eat it?
Or do I have to do something first?
You can eat it.
Okay.
Right, I received it.
I got it this morning.
Why did you bring it with you?
Someone might see it.
Even if they see it,
they won’t know who wrote it anyway.
We finally get to go out together.
Yeah.
We were in Grade 10
when you sent me the first note, right?
Do you still have it?
I’m not sure.
It’s probably in my book box.
Please don’t let him find it. Amen.
It’s embarrassing.
It’s been so long. Two years.
If someone sees us together,
won’t they be confused?
I don’t think we will run into anyone.
Augar, damn it. Pull over.
What the hell is going on?
August, help me.
I almost died.
What are you doing here?
What are you two doing here?
So this is where you’ve been all this time.
August, why are you with Tle?
Oh, that’s the postcard that you wrote.
Yes, I remember it.
No, it’s not.
Are the two of them…
Nonsense.
Let me see it.
No.
Tle, take it.
Tle, let me see it.
Give it to me.
Good job, Ko.
I was about to read it.
Run.
Tle.
Hey.
When will they stop acting childishly?
What did you bring?
Wow! It looks tasty.
This is the first time
that we hang out in your yard.
It has a full view of the orange tree.
It’s so refreshing.
You must really like it.
Seriously.
It’s so delicious.
I don’t want someone here to feel left out.
It’s unbelievable
that August and Tle are dating.
One of them is a bookworm
while the other is a manga fanatic.
How do you know that they are dating?
They might still be flirting.
Tle has flirted with him for a long time.
He has sent notes to him since Grade 10.
It’s so cool.
What about us?
Are we dating?
What is this?
Why are you suddenly asking me this?
Probably yes.
Can you answer it seriously?
Yes, we are dating.
I’ll be right back.
What should we call each other?
Baby, babe, sweetie, darling?
So cheesy.
What is this?
Did you make it?
Do you like it?
Very much.
This one is mine, and that one is yours.
You can use it to store whatever you want.
Do you mean our things?
It’s up to you.
The box is not big. What can I put in it?
Who says it’s not big?
Look.
I can put the moon in it.
You are getting good.
Where did you learn the pickup line?
Then I’ll use this box to store the sun.
I’ll feed my boyfriend.
Your boyfriend wants to feed you too.
It’s so refreshing.
Why is your hair this color?
Hello, Mr. Kong.
You.
Why is your hair so long?
You dyed your hair.
You keep your hair too long.
Fix it before next week.
Doesn’t it feel like watching yourself?
Let’s go to the classroom.
Hello, I’m Buntham Pongsuwan.
I’m 16.
Nice to meet you.
Your seat is in the back.
Hey.
Doesn’t it feel like watching yourself?
Mine is longer than yours.
I’ll catch up with you soon.
Don’t get too cocky.
You can’t compete with me, boy.
Hey.
Look, the game is over.
Sorry.
Don’t say you’re sorry.
You are not sorry.
I’ve read up to volume 33.
What?
Damn, you are so fast.
It’s quite fun.
True.
August, when is the contest?
Next two weeks.
Are you nervous?
You will be the ultimate fan of Dragon Ball.
It will not be easy.
Many people apply to join the contest.
Augar.
Did you drive to school today?
Are you trying to get on my nerves?
Are you going to try out
for the national youth team?
Of course.
If I get on the team,
you have to come and watch my game.
Fine, I’ll pray to the deity
to help you make the team.
Shall we promise the deity that
we will repay him with 9,999 boiled eggs?
So you can make the team in one try.
Stop it, Achi.
Chickens cannot lay that many eggs.
Stop it, both of you.
You don’t need to pray to the deity.
Believe in me.
I’ve got skills.
False skills.
I still remember your driving skills.
Your driving was freaking scary.
Then don’t ride in my car again.
Where have you been?
I went to talk to scholarship students.
They said that college seniors will come
to introduce their faculties.
There will be seniors from a med school.
Also, seniors from Communication Arts, Engineering, and Sport Science faculties.
What faculty are you interested in?
Ko Song is interested in med school.
What about you, Achi?
What do you want to study?
My mom wants me to attend a med school.
But I’m interested in sport science.
Are you interested in sport science
or an athlete?
Are you planning
to take care of a basketball athlete?
Assh*le, shut your mouth with it.
Damn it, Augar.
Ko.
Can I borrow your phone?
Just take it out.
You can’t let teachers see it.
You are smiling.
You like it, don’t you?
Who permits you to change it?
What?
My number is saved as Orange.
Your number is saved as Orange’s owner.
Why?
Are you feeling shy, Orange’s owner?
Hello, everyone.
Please join the group of the faculty
that you are interested in.
Let’s go.
I believe that you are here
because you are interested in med school.
I have questions for you.
How many years does a medical degree take?
-Seven years.
-Six years.
That’s right.
How many bones are in the human body?
206 bones.
Correct.
How many bones are in the human spine?
26 bones.
You must have studied it.
We will draft a plan for a two-storey house.
You’ve got a good build.
What sport do you play?
Basketball.
What do you want to be?
A national athlete.
Then you came to the right place.
In the next activity, I need a volunteer.
Can you be the volunteer?
You will be working on a set of a film,
a drama, or a commercial ad.
Many activities are waiting for you
if you study communication arts.
Hold it like this.
Does any of you want to study in the field?
Please join us
at the Faculty of Communication Arts.
I have basketball practice.
I’ll be back.
Alright.
What’s wrong, Boss Ko?
I’m bored. This is not fun.
None of these faculties is interesting.
None of these faculties is interesting?
Or you aren’t interested
in any of these faculties?
No.
Does it upset you when you see it?
You feel uneasy when you see it, right?
You want to walk to him and grab his collar.
You are imagining things.
I can tell from the look on your face.
I think I’m right on this.
What about you and Tle?
Will Tle choose to attend med school
like Ko Song?
Yeah, I think so.
Why?
Aren’t you worried
about being apart from him?
I’ve never thought about that.
Why are you thinking about it?
Excuse me.
What are you two doing?
Damn. It looks good on you.
It’s good that you’re here.
Let’s go grab something to eat.
The senior said they will buy me shaved ice.
Ouch. My stomach hurts.
I need to go to the bathroom.
It looks good on you.
What’s wrong?
Don’t you have to hurry back
to talk to the senior?
What are you doing?
Listen to your heartbeat.
No, stop it.
I heard it.
You are jealous, aren’t you?
Jealous?!
That’s nonsense.
Are you jealous?
No.
You are definitely jealous.
What if I am?
Why are you smiling?
This is cute.
I don’t want to feel this way.
But I can’t help it.
So I don’t know how to tell you.
This is your dream.
I don’t want to bother you.
I…
When I was in the group,
I felt like I didn’t belong there.
I’m acting like a jerk.
You’re not a jerk, Orange.
I get it.
I really do.
I’m sorry.
This is the first time
that Boss Ko said he’s sorry.
So what?
It doesn’t mean you can do anything.
I will keep an eye on you 24/7.
Okay?
If you’re going to do that,
why don’t you move in with me?
That’s a bit much.
Excuse me. My name is A.
I think you have a unique face.
Are you interested in
being a photoshoot model?
Who are you talking to?
You.
What’s your name?
Ko Neung.
I’m Ko.
Your name is mod.
My name is Ko, not Mod.
You are also funny.
But…
Who are you?
In a simple word, I’m a talent scout.
I go to schools and scout good-looking teens
to work as models or celebrities.
I see.
Can we trust him?
Do you want my business card?
Here.
I’m looking for a model to shoot
a cover of a teen fashion magazine.
I’ll give you 3,000 baht as your fee.
Damn, 3,000 baht.
You don’t need to agree right now.
You can go back
and talk to your parents first.
You can call me later.
I really like your face.
I’ve got to go back to Bangkok now.
I’ll be looking forward to your call.
Bye.
Goodbye.
What should I do?
He doesn’t seem like a bad guy.
He will give me 3,000 baht.
Do you want to do it because of the money
or because you want to be a model?
Both.
Ko.
Come here.
I’ve got to go.
Ko.
I’m keeping an eye on you, Dr. Glasses.
It’s been three days.
Have you called him?
No.
But my parents said I should give it a try.
Do it.
If it’s what you like, I’ll support you.
Is my boyfriend going to become a celebrity?
You’ve been teasing me a lot lately.
You should go back to study.
If you don’t get in med school,
I’ll laugh at you.
You are mean.
Are you sick?
I feel a bit feverish.
You should take medicine.
I will before going to bed.
Are you sure
you can go to school tomorrow?
No problem.
If you can’t, just tell me.
I’ll take leave to be with you.
No. Stop it.
What should I do with A Supajee?
It’s your home.
Can’t we go for another lap?
I don’t want to go home yet.
Stop being clingy.
You are all grown-up, aren’t you?
So you didn’t call to tell me
when you would be home.
My phone battery is dead.
Hello, Mom.
Hello.
Are you Augar?
I remember you.
Yes, I’m on my way home.
So I gave him a ride.
Thank you.
Since you gave him a ride,
why don’t you join us for dinner?
If you say no,
I won’t let you give him a ride again.
Yes.
What do we have for dinner?
I prepared your favorite dishes.
Really?
Yes.
Enjoy the meal.
How do you know me?
When I go to pick Achi up at school,
I always see you with him.
I just didn’t get out of the car to meet you.
Is that so?
I didn’t know that.
One more thing,
Achi tells me everything about you.
Everything?
Yes.
Recently, you went on a trip together.
He also told me everything about the trip.
Right.
Are you…
I’m not mad at you.
I get it.
It’s not strange.
The faucet can be broken anytime.
But I have something to ask you.
You need to be honest with me.
Yes.
Do you know who sent this postcard?
I found it when I was cleaning his room.
Mom, what are you doing?
Why did you go into my room?
Let me mess up your hair, little boy.
Mom.
Is my son seeing someone?
Let me mess up your hair, little boy.
Mom, stop it. Give it to me.
Who calls my son ‘little boy’?
Little boy.
Stop it.
See you.
Good night, Augar.
See you, little boy.
My mom might see it.
Ko.
Ko Song.
Hello, Dad.
Hello.
I just talked to him on the phone.
He said I could come in.
Come in.
He’s upstairs.
Yes, Dad.
Dad.
Have you checked on Ko Song?
I just got back from work.
Why?
He was sick.
But he said he feels better now.
Can you come here? I want to talk to you.
Yes.
During the past two years,
I have had a problem at work.
Ko’s mom and I have talked.
She has to move back
to take care of her mother.
His grandmother is not doing well.
Thank you for keeping him company.
Yes, Dad.
Don’t worry.
My friends and I will take good care of him.
I don’t even know that my son was sick.
I don’t have time for him.
I hope you will visit him often.
Yes, Dad.
You can go now.
Dad.
Maybe he just wants a quick chat with you.
How are you?
Are you tired from studying?
Have you eaten anything?
It doesn’t take long
to ask him these questions.
I’ll go upstairs now.
You go back to studying
right after you feel better.
You are very diligent, Doctor.
I saw the light in your room
has been turned off for a while.
Why did you take so long to come here?
My mom was telling me about a soap opera.
Are you bored?c
No.
Can we talk?
Sure.
Ko Song.
Yes.
After we graduate from high school,
will you leave me?
Will you go to a college far away from here?
Will we still get to see each other?
Orange.
Just thinking that
we won’t get to talk often like this,
it already makes me feel sad.
It’s okay.
I promise that we will get to see each other.
If we attend different schools,
it will be hard for us to see each other.
If that’s the case,
I’ll try to make time to see you.
Ko Song.
I promise I won’t miss our meeting.
You don’t need to promise me that.
No, I want to.
Because I want to see you too.
If we don’t have many chances
to talk like this,
it also makes me sad.
Ko Song.
What are you doing?
What is this? Let me go.
You’re so stubborn.
Stop thinking about us being apart.
Ko Song, let me go.
Even though we like different things,
it doesn’t mean we will go separate ways.
Don’t argue with me.
If you do, I’ll kiss you.
But I want to argue back.
What did you say?
No. I’m just kidding.
(I heard from an adult
that the first time will help us grow up.)
(I think these words are not only for kids.)
(But it can apply to every phase of our life.)
[THE 10-FINALIST QUALIFYING ROUND
OF DRAGON BALL ULTIMATE FAN]
(We all have our first time.)
[THE 10-FINALIST QUALIFYING ROUND
OF DRAGON BALL ULTIMATE FAN]
(August didn’t pass the qualifying round
and didn’t get to appear on the show.)
It’s okay.
I’ll buy you an ice cream.
Come on.
Damn. Thawan Obkit.
Achi, I got on the team.
(Augar passed the tryout
for the national youth team.)
(He made the team.)
So the person who sent you this postcard
is Augar, right?
(Achi opens up with his mom and
tells her that the postcard is from Augar.)
Achi, you can date anyone that you want.
I just want you to be honest with me.
(Ko Song’s Dad has breakfast
with Ko Song on Monday.)
Ko.
Let’s have breakfast together.
(I, the Orangeman,
get to do something new.)
His look can go well with many styles.
Augar, August, Achi.
Ko Neung.
Boss Ko.
I have something to show you.
What is it?
Here.
Damn. You look so good.
You look so good, Ko.
What do you think?
Open it.
Let me see.
Damn.
Look.
(Thank you for every first time in our life.)
(It helps us grow up.)
- Why do we have to grow up?
- Damn.
- August, you made it.
- This is how life is.
- We each need to follow our own path to grow.
- In your future, will I be a part of it?
- No matter where you and I go, we will never be apart.
- Can you do that, Ko Song?