[Episode 13]
[I cut my hand. Come back and do the dishes.]
[It's late. Why...]
Why have you been coming back so late lately?
I need to catch up on sleep.
Don't call me for lunch.
Mister.
This one? Okay.
Ten yuan.
Thank you. Here you go.
Yi, take a look.
This month's income is half of last month's.
Aren't those high schoolers on summer break?
They all come here to shoot pool.
And every one of them is running up a tab.
Table time, sunflower seeds, peanuts...
They're charging everything to their tabs.
We're almost out of electric bill money.
Can't you scare them a little?
I'll ask Yong
to scare them a little next time...
Has the girl
Yang mentioned last time been here recently?
What girl?
Never mind.
Okay.
Good. Bend down a little.
That's it. Relax your hand.
Yi. The girl.
The girl's here. Look.
- Spread my fingers?
- Yeah, spread your fingers.
Good. Bend down a little.
Relax your hand. That's it.
Nice shot.
Can I have your boss coach me?
You mean Yi?
He just runs the place. He doesn't coach.
Besides, he's been through real storms.
He wouldn't care about this small stuff.
What kind of storms?
I don't know the details.
Last time some idiot barged in here,
Yi almost put him in the hospital.
I think he's definitely got some history.
Really?
Yes. Pull your hand back a little.
Nice shot.
Keep going.
Hit this one?
This one first.
All right.
I'll coach her.
What's going on?
Come outside with me.
Is this how you do business, Mr. Chen?
I paid for an hour. I just started.
Fine.
I'll coach you. Finish this game.
Can we go now?
Of course.
This isn't a place you should be.
Stay away from them.
Why should I listen to you?
Are you trying to make me miserable on purpose?
Me?
You're the one who's had a problem
with me this whole time.
Yes.
As long as you stay here,
I'm always worried, and everything feels wrong.
Is that clear enough, Miao Jing?
Worried?
Why are you worrying about me?
Right.
It's not my place to worry.
Your hour's up. You're off work, Mr. Chen.
Going home?
Give me a ride.
I'm not going back. Not tonight.
Yi. Sleeping here again?
Have some breakfast.
Come on. I picked these out for you. Hurry.
Soy milk and buns. They will get cold. Hurry.
Come on.
Is the person in charge here?
Routine inspection.
Do you have a business license
and a fire safety permit?
Yes, officer.
They're right here. This way, please.
The fire inspection was last week, right?
Yes.
- The surveillance is all working fine.
- Everything's normal.
Yes. The whole shop is covered,
and outside we have infrared cameras too.
Fruit knives don't count
as controlled knives, do they?
They don't, but we've had reports
of groups gathering here and causing trouble.
Is that true?
A business talk fell through,
and there was a small argument.
I wouldn't call it a gathering.
I didn't think this would trouble the police.
Since you took over and opened for business,
stay away from anything illegal.
Thank you for the reminder, officer. We will.
Captain Zhou, all paperwork is in order.
No problems.
Let's go.
Take care.
Why did he come in person?
Tell everyone we're closed today.
Yi.
Come eat at my place tonight.
I'll make you salt and pepper ribs.
When Li Qiao and I move into our new place,
we'll throw a housewarming party.
I'll have her make you another real feast.
By the way, Bo,
send me your real estate agent.
Why do you need an agent?
I want to rent out the apartment.
Rent it out?
Has Miao Jing driven you insane?
Hello, sir. Here to view a property?
Yes. I made an appointment with Manager Xu.
I have an apartment I want to rent out.
Mr. Chen, right? I'm Xu. Please, have a seat.
Liu, get him some water.
Mr. Chen, please sit.
Here's the contract.
We've gone over your property details online.
This apartment is in an older compound,
so the facilities may be a bit dated.
If you rent it out, the rent may not be ideal.
That's fine. Lower rent is fine.
The key is speed.
Speed?
Honestly, if you're willing to list it,
that might be a better deal.
- If you put it up for sale--
- I'm only renting, not selling.
Not selling?
Short-term or long-term is fine.
I can negotiate on rent, utilities, anything.
The key is speed.
You're making a lot of concessions, Mr. Chen.
Do you have any requirements for the tenant?
I just need you to do me a favor.
Who is it?
Hello.
I'm a manager at Comfort Home Real Estate.
My last name is Xu.
I'm not buying a property. Thanks.
Please don't misunderstand.
Mr. Chen booked a viewing for me.
Mr. Chen?
Didn't he message you?
[I'm renting the place out. Don't bother me.]
Chen Yi sent you here, right?
- Yes, that's right.
- Please, come in.
- All right.
- Take a look around.
Okay. The living room is pretty big.
It is.
Sorry. The bathroom faucet is old.
I just fixed it, but it's fine. It works.
Look at the balcony. It gets great light.
The morning sun feels really nice in here.
The main bedroom is very large too.
And all the furniture is here.
The bed and cabinets can all stay.
Okay.
Look at this hallway.
The ceiling height is comfortable, right?
- Yes, it is.
- This is the second bedroom.
It's a little smaller,
but look at this window. It's very nice.
The whole place feels airy.
Come look at the kitchen.
The kitchen has a separate layout,
so the grease and smoke won't get out.
A family eating here would feel so warm.
And look over here.
It's a little messy,
but it's all storage space.
This would sell for a good price, wouldn't it?
Come look inside the kitchen.
I've already talked to the agent about it.
It'll be dealt with in the next few days.
Hai City has everything.
Go back and live your life.
Let's stop tangling up each other's lives.
What about you?
You don't need to worry about me.
I'm not telling you to leave right now.
I'll rent you another place outside.
Miss Miao. Why don't you wash up too?
There was a lot of dust just now.
- Wipe yourself down.
- Alright.
Mr. Chen, you're here too.
This room probably hasn't been dusted.
There was too much dust. It got in my eyes.
Since you've thought it through so carefully,
and you're the owner,
I'll definitely get you a good price.
Consider it repayment for taking me in.
Miss Miao.
Here. Take these.
- Come in, come in.
- Okay, come.
Hello. We spoke on the phone.
Go ahead and look around.
This is the living room.
That's the balcony. It gets great light.
It's spacious too. Want to take a look?
Sure.
Come on. Take a look.
It's really nice. It really is big.
The furniture can stay.
The balcony light is great. It's good.
The furniture is old,
but you can move right in.
- Let's see the rooms.
- Okay.
Come on.
As you can see, there are two bedrooms.
This is the main bedroom,
and this is the second bedroom.
The hallway ceiling height is very comfortable.
It really is.
What's going on?
Miss Miao heard you wanted to sell the place,
so she immediately contacted two big agencies.
Highest offer wins.
This is going to be hard to clean up.
Anyway, these walls definitely need repainting.
But if you're in a hurry,
wall panels would work too.
That's right.
Walls in older compounds are all like this.
They're more or less the same.
Buyers in this area care about the location.
They'll have to renovate it anyway.
So see if you can give us a good price.
- What?
- No problem. Of course.
Mr. Chen, if you're serious about selling,
I'll arrange buyers now. List it with me.
What do you think, Mr. Chen?
Whatever. She's the one with all the ideas.
Careful. Slow down.
One of the agents who came today
has a client urgently looking to buy.
They've already come to see the place.
That fast?
Yes. I've negotiated the price too.
Four thousand eight hundred per square meter.
Fifty percent down payment first.
That's a very good price for the old town.
But they want to renovate,
so they don't want the old furniture.
So I called movers to take it all away.
You didn't ask me before selling the apartment?
Aren't I asking you now?
Where's the property deed?
This is a notice, not a question.
Keep your own things.
Then I'll throw them away.
- Mister, take this up to the truck first.
- Sure.
Put this one last.
This is glass, so be careful.
Put it on top later.
You can't just throw photos away.
It's bad luck.
Leave it with me. I'll handle it.
It's just a photo. Let the movers take it.
Miao Jing, what exactly are you trying to do?
Sell the apartment.
I'm unemployed now. I have no income.
If I help sell the apartment,
you can at least give me a cut.
You're unemployed?
Yes.
I don't have a job now. I have nowhere to go.
So I had to come back. Satisfied?
Mister, hold on. Stop moving things for now.
Just stay here. Stay as long as you want.
We're not selling the apartment.
Move it back down.
- Bring them back down.
- Alright, alright.
How did you lose your job?
Over there, I worked from 8 AM
to 10 PM every day.
And I had to deal with all kinds
of workplace politics.
I was exhausted.
Did you ever think
about changing companies in Hai City?
I had no one there, and the rent was expensive.
But don't worry.
Once I find a new job, I'll move out.
I won't bother you.
Stay here.
It's not like you're renting this from me.
Problem solved?
Didn't you decide to rent it out?
Why change agents and stop renting it out too?
Miao Jing has nowhere to go.
I'm keeping it for now.
I knew it.
Why are you dressed so formally today?
I'm meeting an old friend.
This is awful.
Keep silent later. We're discussing business.
Where's the sugar?
- Mr. Xu, long time no see.
- Manager Chen. Long time no see.
You've changed a lot.
Just a little weathered.
Bo. You haven't changed much.
Sit.
Coffee?
After the Kuangxia project ended,
we lost touch.
I thought it was a real shame.
In that crooked operation,
meeting a decent client like you was rare.
Thanks to you,
we avoided a lot of trouble back then.
But today, I'm the one who needs a favor.
Here's her resume. Please take a look, Mr. Xu.
Mr. Xu? Why so formal?
Why are work experience
and project experience blank?
I put the resume together.
She can fill in the work experience herself
during the interview.
These past few years,
I haven't really known what she's been doing.
Miao Jing?
Is this the girl from back then,
the one you had me check scores for?
Yes.
All right. I'll help.
But let me say this up front.
I can refer her internally,
but whether this works out,
and whether she gets an offer depend
on her overall qualifications.
Given my position in the company, I
can't really set that kind of precedent.
Giving her a chance is enough, Mr. Xu.
You're still calling me Mr. Xu? Why so polite?
I need to get her out of here.
I can't let her keep staying here.
Be honest with yourself.
I saw through you a long time ago.
You talk tougher than anyone,
but when have you really let go?
You even stayed up making her resume
and found connections behind my back.
You rushed to buy people coffee
at over 100 yuan a cup.
You even planned her fallback in Teng City
after she quit.
She came back because she lost her job.
I see.
It must've been hard for her alone in Hai City.
I don't mind supporting her.
It's just she needs a way to stand
on her own feet.
That way, even if she leaves later,
it'll be easier for her.
When are you going to think about yourself?
See if you like this color.
- We can change it if you want.
- Okay.
This all comes as a set.
If you take the whole set,
you won't have to match things yourself.
- We'd like to look at some other shops first.
- Let's keep looking.
- All right.
- Let's go.
Let's look across the way.
- Hello.
- Would you like to know more about our sofas?
We're just looking.
This one is leather.
This sofa is excellent.
It's Nordic style, perfect for young people.
And this model folds out.
You can use it as a sofa,
then lay it flat as a sofa bed.
The size is pretty good.
You can choose the color too.
Look. There are so many colors to choose from.
This color is nice.
Got it.
Does this coffee table come with it?
Yes. The coffee table is in the same style.
What about that cabinet?
Same style too.
Then let's take all three.
Great. Anything else you'd like to see?
You can keep looking over here.
There are cabinets inside,
and dining tables too.
You're back?
You did this?
I've got good taste, right?
You spent so much. Do you have enough money?
No need to empty your savings just to spite me.
Thank you, Mr. Chen.
I restocked the refrigerator.
Wait. Hold this up for me.
My neck hurts from looking down.
I can't see.
Clean yourself up tomorrow.
Come meet a friend with me.
Who?
A friend from a construction company.
Their company happens to be hiring.
Sure. I'll meet them.
[Resume]
Tell us a little about yourself.
My name is Miao Jing.
I graduated from Jiaohai University. I'm 25.
It's an honor to interview with your company.
Listing my awards would probably bore everyone,
so let's just talk directly.
Then we'll be direct about our conditions too.
Our hours are 8:30 AM to 7 PM.
There's a ninety-minute break in between.
Our projects are highly flexible.
Sometimes you'll need to stay
at the company to coordinate.
Can you accept that?
So overtime culture is strong at your company.
The more you work, the more you earn.
Some salespeople practically live here.
Because they know
that commissions are where the money is.
I respect labor law.
Overtime is fine.
As long as you pay me at 150% the weekday rate
and triple pay on statutory holidays.
You've got quite an attitude.
Tell us about your work experience
and projects.
I used to work at an audit firm.
I went from internal audit to external audit.
I've handled cases big and small.
All right. We understand your situation.
Go home and wait for our notice.
[Changlan Construction, Xu Lin Feng]
About Miao Jing's interview...
Does she not really want to join our company?
Human Resources thinks she's not a great fit.
Sorry I couldn't help this time.
It's fine. I caused you trouble.
I know her temper.
If a friend's company has an opening later,
I'll introduce her.
Don't worry yet.
You're Miao Jing, right?
I've heard a lot about you.
Back when your brother and I ate dust
on construction sites,
he talked about you all the time.
Back then, he ran around
for your school applications.
Now he's running around for your job.
Your brother really looks out for you.
I have a meeting, so I'll head upstairs.
You two talk.
Let's have dinner with Miao Jing sometime.
If you can't find a job, just stay home.
You have the education.
You'll have plenty of chances.
Don't put too much pressure on yourself.
Money isn't that important.
Let's go.
Big!
Flip!
Yi. This month's bill.
Bo.
After running a billiards hall for years,
do you want to do something else?
I think things are fine now.
Save for a down payment,
get a mortgage, then have a daughter with Qiao.
Isn't that a perfect life?
Everyone.
Thank you all for your support.
We'll soon close for renovations and upgrades.
On our last day, all table time is free.
Play as much as you want.
Come on. Keep playing.
After this,
we're becoming a snooker training center.
Closing time will also move up to nine.
All billiards lovers are welcome to join.
But things like cigarettes
and alcohol will no longer be offered.
What snooker training center, Mr. Chen?
If you want to drive us all out, just say so.
- Right, everyone?
- Exactly. What does that mean?
Mr. Chen, have you really decided to switch
to teaching kids how to play?
Those willing to do me this favor today,
play as much as you like.
Those who aren't are welcome to leave.
Let's go.
- Let's play a bit longer.
- What's this all about?
Let's go.
- Let's find another place. Let's go.
- Next place, next place.
Let's go.
This announcement came suddenly.
Take this week to decide to stay or leave.
Anyone who leaves gets paid for the full month.
Anyone who stays, from now on,
taking tips privately is strictly forbidden.
The work won't be as easy as it is now either.
We're going to run a legitimate business.
Yi, why? The billiards hall was doing fine.
With this change, coaches, training partners,
and customers will all be gone.
Coaches and training partners are easy to find.
What we need now is someone for the accounts.
[Closed for renovations.]
[Diagonal Elite Pool Training Camp]
The snooker center is open.
Professional snooker training.
Please take a look.
Our snooker center is open.
Opening? It's nearby, right?
Snooker, right here.
- Yes, we've changed to snooker.
- Professional billiards training.
Snooker training.
- Take a look.
- No thanks, no thanks.
It's right here. You can go straight in.
- Snooker lessons. Come and take a look.
- Yes, go on in.
Snooker training.
Ma'am, snooker.
This way. Snooker training is this way.
Come learn more about it.
Take care, ma'am.
- To the right.
- Snooker lessons.
Come by anytime.
To the right. Okay.
Yi, we've been at this all morning
and barely handed any out.
Most people just booked open tables.
We have fewer customers now.
We just opened. What's the rush?
The equipment hasn't even arrived yet.
Come on. Billiards training.
Learn about our snooker training.
Come on. It's right this way.
We're opening next month.
Here they come.
There's more inside.
These are fragile. Be careful.
Slow down with these.
Bai, are you okay?
- Are you all right? Let me help you.
- I'm fine, I'm fine.
- No need.
- I'll do it, I'll do it.
I'm fine. Go on.
- Sit down for a bit.
- Take a break.
Rest for a while.
Are you okay?
- Bai, have some water.
- Thank you.
- I'm leaving.
- Don't mention it.
Delivery services are really advanced now.
When I was a kid, we only had the post office.
That's true. We never had any of this before.
When it first took off in the early 2000s,
it was mostly big companies using it.
Now it's everywhere.
[Haoyun Logistics]
Why is she taking pictures?
No pictures.
My friend is coming to pick me up.
I'm afraid he won't find the place.
If it's not allowed, I'll delete it.
It's fine. Thank you so much earlier.
I've held you up here for so long.
I'll get going. I'll leave you to it.
Okay.
[Investigation Category]
[Cen, the working group is
not fully in place yet.]