[Episode 14]
- Let's come back another day.
- Sure.
- They can't pay the electric bill again?
- Why is the power out?
Xin.
- Xin.
- Stop shouting!
- What's the shouting about?
- The power's out.
They'll think you have no customers
and can't pay the electric bill.
You two have too much free time?
Why stay open if you can't pay the bill?
Seriously.
- What is going on?
- And they have the nerve to talk about us.
Li, they're going too far.
Who?
The property management people.
What do we do, Li?
Our contract expires next month.
Why push us out and not the other shops?
Why panic?
With Yi and me here, they won't push me around.
The number dialed is temporarily unavailable.
Please try again later.
Li, I'll go with you.
There is strength in numbers.
Are you kidding?
For something this minor,
I need a crowd to look tough?
Pick up those rhinestones.
One missing piece costs me 20 yuan.
Don't leave a single one behind.
Be careful, Li.
It's only the few of you here?
Where is your manager? I want to see Liu.
Director Liu isn't here today.
Tell me what you want. I'll pass it on.
Can you solve it if I tell you?
Who made that tenant optimization list?
That list follows all our rules and procedures.
Every item was checked and screened one by one.
Also, we've had four complaints
about trouble in your shop.
What if I insist on staying?
Are you going to throw me out?
This is a proper mall.
We follow proper procedures.
You should move out on schedule.
If that won't work,
pay a deposit and I'll give you more time.
Do you know who my boyfriend is?
You're new here, right?
Haven't you heard of Chen Yi?
- Chen Yi?
- The one from the old district?
- Yes.
Asleep?
No.
Thank you for doing this.
I'll try to get there early.
You don't have to change your plan. I wasn't--
You weren't going back because of me. I know.
I'm not that full of myself.
I'm more familiar with the area.
I'll go ahead and check things out first.
That way, when Xiao Yu and the others arrive,
they'll have a clearer idea.
You're simply a workaholic.
Get some rest when you get home.
Miao Jing.
What?
I don't want to keep staring at the car roof.
How about now?
That one. That shop right there.
This area is lively.
The location is pretty nice.
Yeah, it's much brighter than the old place.
Look, that shop stands out the most.
[Store for Sale]
It really does. You can spot it right away.
Then we won't have to move anything ourselves.
They'll move everything over exactly as it is.
They won't dare lose a single rhinestone.
Li, I told you. They don't dare push us around.
With Yi here, what can't be solved?
Li, was Yi like a movie hero back then,
saving the damsel in distress?
All it took was one phone call.
He didn't even have to come in person.
Li, Yi is so reliable.
[All Contacts, Select, Return: Yi]
You're so lucky.
Li, has Yi not been coming around much lately?
Men have careers to handle outside.
What man spends all day circling a woman?
What are you trying to say?
You know I'm seeing someone lately.
He runs a fruit shop
by the power bureau compound.
And then...
And then what?
Anyway, he told me...
that Yi brought some new girl home recently.
I don't know if it's true.
Of course it's not true.
Don't you know Yi protects his own woman?
Probably another clueless girl chasing him.
You haven't told anyone else this, right?
No. Don't worry, Li.
So you're the one. You don't look that old.
How old are you?
Asking my age right away? That's private.
Quite the act. You even bought fruit.
Already learned to care that fast?
I see several girls like you every year.
But I'm the only one who stays by Yi's side.
Think this through.
Don't waste your youth
on something going nowhere.
Is that so?
Girl, I'm saying this for your own good.
I don't want to make things ugly for you.
What are you doing? Yi protects his own.
Let's talk inside.
Tough one.
Change your shoes.
How could I let a guest wash the fruit?
Go sit down. I'll do it.
Didn't Yi tell you?
He doesn't like anyone touching his kitchen.
I think he did.
You're awfully calm.
So you already knew he had a girlfriend.
I did.
Girls these days really are impressive.
But your sweet homemaker angle is new.
You're not like the ones I usually see.
What are they usually like?
Hot, beautiful, and charming.
Someone clean and plain like you,
with no particular flavor, really is new.
Then his taste is pretty consistent.
What do you mean?
Isn't that you? Hot.
Don't try to get close to me.
I'm not easy to deal with.
After all these years with Yi,
what tricks haven't I seen?
All these years?
Has it been three or four years?
More than that. Four or five years, maybe.
Anyway, we've been together for a long time.
Stop chasing what's not yours.
Four or five years. That long?
How did you two meet?
It's been so long. Who still remembers?
Why am I even talking to you about this?
I'm only curious.
I heard he wasn't in Teng City before.
I wanted to know where you two fell in love.
You even know that?
What, still not giving up?
I thought you'd want to tell me more
about your story with him.
I remembered wrong. It was three years ago.
Yi had just returned to Teng City.
It was on the back street
behind the billiards hall.
A few thugs were harassing me.
I was ready to fight them to the end.
Then Yi showed up.
He brought a few men
and dropped those thugs fast.
That's how we met.
After that, we spent time together and clicked.
Then we got together.
So he came back to Teng City three years ago.
Why do you keep clinging to these tiny details?
Yi bought it. Get it?
Good news is coming soon.
If you insist on clinging to Yi, I don't care.
When the time comes, you'll get nothing.
You'll only make things awkward for both sides.
That's all I have to say.
Your things are all here.
There are toiletries in the bathroom cabinet.
When I moved in, I didn't know whose they were,
so I packed them away.
I'm Miao Jing, Chen Yi's sister.
I've been living here for over half a month.
He wasn't home when I came,
so I cleaned up myself.
You're his sister?
He never told you before?
Not at all.
You two talk. I won't bother you.
Why are you here?
The property office
pulled another stunt today.
They want us to move out.
They think I'm easy to push around.
Why didn't you call me before coming here?
I heard there was a girl at your place.
Yi, I didn't know she was your sister.
You never told me.
You didn't say anything to her, did you?
She asked a bunch of random questions,
and I bluffed my way through.
Don't forget what we agreed on before.
- I'm sorry.
- Keep your distance from her from now on.
I didn't handle today well.
Did Tu Li give you a hard time?
That's her room.
She had every right to be angry.
I'm the one who should apologize.
That's not her room.
She only stays there once in a while.
Are you busy tomorrow?
Giving me work again?
I mean, if you're free,
do you want to come by the billiards hall?
I have plans tomorrow.
What about the day after?
There's something I'm curious about.
If your girlfriend stayed over,
why sleep in separate rooms?
She and I aren't what you think.
Darn it, Yi.
Is this still our shabby little billiards hall?
Why does it smell like disinfectant?
Does it? Buy some incense.
Put incense here?
I'll go buy it.
Hello.
- Hello. Just one person?
- Yes.
Would you like a practice partner?
No, thanks.
- Table four.
- Okay.
Nice shot.
One more.
Any fresh news here?
We're here to play.
Talking business ruins the mood.
Yeah.
Then how about this, Mr. Huang?
We go up there later and take them down.
- I'm on your team.
- Can you handle it?
Back in the day, I was on the school team.
With one move, I could hook him and drop him.
Miao Jing?
Top three, at least.
Miao Jing.
- Yi Lan!
- It really is you.
Why are you back?
You're playing here too?
Yeah.
- It's been five or six years, right?
- Yeah.
You're so beautiful now.
No, you were pretty before too.
You just have more of that big-city feel now.
You're exaggerating.
Are you here by yourself?
I had plans,
but something came up and he couldn't make it.
So I decided to get some exercise by myself.
No point wasting the court fee.
Then let's play a couple of rounds.
Sure. We can catch up too.
I ran into a friend.
You guys play by yourselves for a bit.
What?
So?
So what?
Yi's newly renovated billiards hall.
How do I put it?
Isn't it a little too proper?
I'm not quite used to it.
That's not what I meant.
Then what? Just say it. Stop hesitating.
It's my newly learned supermarket trick.
Yi's billiards hall has been upgraded, right?
I didn't know how else to help.
Kids should like this.
Darn it.
It's good.
But look at this.
Will the customers get used to it?
I think it's great.
Have you finished the accounts?
Bring them over later. I'll take a look.
I should've kept my mouth shut.
Once Miao Jing gets here,
you can stop nagging me.
I'll go do the accounts.
We need to buy a few more advanced cues.
Did you buy the spare balls?
Yes. They're all in the storeroom.
Come on. Let's go take a look.
All right. Yong, watch the place.
- We're going to take a look.
- Okay.
How is this average?
Yi, looks like I don't have the key.
I'll make a call.
- Hello?
- Babe.
Do you have my storeroom key?
Why are you always so forgetful?
My bad, my bad.
I'll come get it from you later.
Wait. I think I saw Miao Jing.
She's playing badminton at our place.
All right. Got it. I'll come find you later.
Bye.
Li Qiao said Jing is playing badminton there.
I'm going.
- I'll go instead.
- Why?
Are you going to find Miao Jing?
If we wait for you to get the key
and come back, it'll be night.
- I always knew you were a good student,
- Thank you.
I didn't expect you to have such stamina too.
So in your mind, I'm just a bookworm?
I didn't say that.
Are you still working in Hai City?
Are you back on vacation this time?
I'm back to handle something.
I'll probably stay for a while.
That's good.
I heard you now work
at the Development and Reform Commission.
You're a government official now?
What official? I'm just a regular clerk.
I envy you, honestly.
People say once you make it out,
everything gets better.
But once you really leave,
you realize how small you are.
Nothing wrong with coming back to Teng City.
The policies are favorable now.
A lot of emerging industries
get their start in small places like ours.
Hao Yun Logistics is headquartered here, right?
You know Hao Yun?
You know Hao Yun too?
Hao Yun is the pride of Teng City now.
I dealt with them when I first started working.
They've grown better and better over the years.
Yi. Sorry to trouble you.
Yi. Aren't you going to say hello?
I won't interrupt her catching up.
Have they paid? I'll cover it.
She didn't have plans with a friend today,
she also said she came alone.
They probably just ran into each other.
Yeah, companies these days only have a future
if they develop in line with policy.
Back in school, who could've imagined
a logistics company could take the market?
Times change.
But your job must be pretty hard too, right?
It's all right.
I heard their boss is hard to deal with.
You mean Mr. Zhang?
I don't get to deal with Mr. Zhang.
I usually coordinate with their managers.
But I heard Mr. Zhang really values talent.
He doesn't care where you come from.
Really?
It's been so long. Let's take a photo.
Sure.
You really changed after the big city.
I thought you wouldn't agree.
You know, you used to be really quiet.
When we graduated,
you wouldn't even let us sign your uniform.
We were kids.
I'll get my phone.
Okay.
- Come on.
One. Two. Three.
Looks great.
I thought you weren't coming.
He's the one who stood me up.
So you came back to visit family.
Perfect. We're about done, so I'll head out.
- You guys have fun.
- Let's catch up next time.
Remember to send me the photo.
Sure. I'll send it through the chat app.
Keep in touch.
I came to get the key.
Bo's girlfriend works the front desk here.
She said you were playing here.
What a coincidence.
Since I'm here, let's play a game.
Why use me as an excuse?
Focus on the game.
Do you need something from her?
Do you want her to help you find a job?
Or is it because of Tu Li?
Do you want to move out?
Does it hurt?
No.
I'll take you home.
No need. It's not on your way.
Do you want to come to my billiards hall?
I have medicine there. Let's treat it first.
Later, we'll go home together.
4,800.
4,800? What costs 4,800?
4,000. 40,000.
Lighting installation. Next--
You're back.
Then you two talk...
We'll do the accounts in the storeroom.
We're leaving. You two talk.
Let's go.
Sit down. I'll get you some water.
You look pretty fancy now.
It hurts.
Well. About Tu Li,
don't take it to heart.
She and I aren't actually...
Why ask me to come
to the billiards hall yesterday?
Want to help manage the accounts here first?
You can look for a job slowly then.
I'll pay you.
Do I get weekends off? Do I get overtime pay?
I can't handle too much pressure right now.
I can't take hardship at all.
Fine. Just don't go too far.
This is a small business.
Don't get the wound wet
for the next couple of days.
Go into the room first.
I'll come over in a bit.
Yi.
I'm just an employee.
Don't make this hard for me.
You're putting me in a tough spot too.
So let's not make things hard
for each other, okay?
If Mr. Zhang weren't asking you sincerely
for this small favor,
he wouldn't have let me be this bold
and park the car right in front of the shop.
What can I possibly do to help Mr. Zhang?
[Closed for renovations.]
You'll know once you go in person.
Please.
Don't spring this kind of surprise on me again.
- Pull the car over.
- Okay.
[Paroxetine: A medicine to treat depression.]
[Not recommended for mood swings
between manic highs and depressive lows.]
Rest here for a bit.
I'll have Bo take you home.
Why aren't you taking me?
I have something small to handle.
Are you really running a small business?
Hello, Yi Lan. It's me.
I need to ask you a favor.
It's about what we discussed this afternoon.
Miao Jing.
Let's go.
Where is she?
Hello.
Hello, ma'am. Do you have an appointment?
I don't.
Please show your invitation.
Please take a look at this first.
I just graduated from university.
I interned at Hao Yun before.
This is my internship certificate.
I was supposed to start full-time,
but the day I was due to report,
I fell and missed it.
Sorry, this isn't a Haoting invitation.
I can't let you in.
A senior at the company told me that
Mr. Zhang is very kind
and really values talent.
I want to ask him in person for a chance.
You can't go in.
Mr. Zhang has important guests today.
- He doesn't have time to see you.
- I won't disturb him.
I'll just wait at the entrance.
I'll see him during a break.
Sorry. Please leave.
Please, just be kind and let me in to see him.
Bye.
This way, Mr. Yao. This way, please.
- I can do it myself. Thank you.
- Mr. Yao, take care.
I hope we have a pleasant cooperation.
My friend, when it comes to money,
we share the risk.
Now that Yi is back,
our road ahead will only get broader.
Good.
Then let's drink to that.
From now on, we're in the same boat.
Come on.
- Cheers.
Yi.
I just remembered.
Back when you were at Kuangxia,
you worked under Zhang Bin too.
Why does it seem like you're not as close now?
I left Zhang Bin years ago.
Chen Yi, you really have been lying to me.
Hello? What's wrong?
I'm hurt. Come pick me up.
At the old factory where we scavenged as kids.
You're hurt? Where?
Why are you there this late?
Wait there for me.
Sorry, Mr. Zhang.
Something came up at home. I have to leave.
It's fine. He has always been like this.
He does things his own way.
As long as our cooperation goes smoothly,
everything's fine.
- Good.
- Come on.
Miao Jing.
Where are you hurt?
I'm not hurt.
I lost something.
What did you have to look for right now?
The earrings you gave me are gone.
Is it that serious? I'll buy you a new pair.
If you don't want to help, I'll look myself.
Take this.
Why wouldn't it be serious?
Chen Yi, tell me. Why wouldn't it be serious?
It was right here back then.
You told me to keep walking and not look back.
What about you?
Have you let go of the past and moved on?
Chen Yi.
Do you even know what you're doing?
I found them.
Miao Jing.
Do you hate me that much?
Yes.