I do like her.
I really do.
But she's carrying a child.
Sis, I'll be honest with you.
Please don't get mad.
I truly do like Xiaofang.
But about the baby...
Actually,
we don't have to raise it ourselves.
You mean Granduncle, right?
At our last meal,
I could already tell.
He's very interested
in Xiaofang's baby.
Go on then.
What's your plan exactly?
Sis.
You're a woman of great wisdom.
Let me lay it all out for you.
Here's the thing.
Uncle Yang
has always had one regret.
He wants a great-grandson.
He treats me like his own son.
I'm a simple man.
I repay kindness with kindness.
So I've always
kept this in mind for Granduncle.
Actually, this child,
Xiaofang and I can raise.
We'd just give Uncle Yang
the title of great-grandfather.
Hoping the old man can
have support and care in his old age,
and live out his years in peace.
Xiaocang.
Since you've laid it all out,
I'll be straight with you too.
I think
you're someone who is
truly
a cut above the rest.
Your situation may be modest now,
but I'm very bullish
on your potential.
You've served by Granduncle's side
for so many years,
and he thinks so highly of you.
Your future is bound to be
absolutely boundless.
Sis.
Aunt.
I swear to the heavens,
once Xiaofang is with me,
I'll treat her well.
From now on, your family...
From now on, our family
will have gained a real son.
But...
But what?
What's wrong?
Do you have any other concerns?
This morning,
I was at a five-star hotel
enjoying my brunch.
But Xiaowei, he...
He...
He's not even human.
Dressed like a gentleman...
I recorded everything.
Who the hell are you?
You.
Stay away from Yang Xiaofang.
Or I'll expose
every dirty secret of yours.
Are you Xiaofang's...
That's right.
I'm the biological father of Yang Xiaofang's child.
I'm warning you.
Stay away from her.
What the hell are you acting tough for?
You're just an ex.
Hey, bird's nest, what did you say?
Stand right there!
Why should I stop just because you say so?
Why would I listen to you?
Stop right there!
Xiaofang already said she's done with you.
I'm courting her openly and honorably.
Openly and honorably, my foot.
You've got nothing but rotten intentions.
You can't give Xiaofang happiness or freedom.
And you can?
That dowry-haggling stunt your family pulled
is the town's biggest joke right now.
Then I'll expose how you
faked being an elite to trick her.
I'll blow it wide open.
Xiaofang hates being lied to more than anything.
Listen, senior,
in this one life we get,
isn't it all about keeping up appearances?
In front of the woman I love,
I put my best foot forward.
What's so wrong with that?
I trust
that we're both gentlemen.
Do you dare
compete fair and square,
to win Xiaofang's heart?
Your only talent is lying.
How shallow. How is that lying?
Can we
compete openly, just this once,
without any dirty tricks?
A contest?
No way I can compete.
My mom's little e-scooter is way too old.
Who's talking about that?
I meant competing for Xiaofang.
That Xiaowei guy,
he's all bark and no bite.
He's such a petty little man.
Yesterday he cornered me on purpose.
He threatened me.
He won't let me
be together with Xiaofang.
I'm just worried about the baby.
I'm just worried
about me and Xiaofang.
You don't need to fear him.
He's just a good-for-nothing.
A useless fool.
If his dad tells him to go east,
he'd never dare go west.
So that means
we've got to deal with his dad first.
Qi Deyao,
that guy's a money-grubber.
Wherever there's money to be made,
he sniffs it out and heads right over.
Back in the day, he was a poacher.
And he still hasn't changed his ways.
He still sneaks into the woods
and sets traps.
Setting traps?
That's poaching!
That's really not okay.
Whether he catches anything or not,
it's illegal all the same.
That family is really something else.
This needs a serious investigation.
Where are you going?
I'm heading up the mountain.
I'm making you what Cantonese folks
love to slow-cook the most:
pork rib and corn soup.
Isn't that too light?
Right now, what you need
is to eat light and get your strength back.
What's going on here?
Look, this is the real deal, right?
Look at this elegance.
Come on, and check this out too.
Isn't that Shu Qingcang?
Yeah, it's Shu.
Look, so handsome.
A fine-looking man.
Captain.
Why is he doing law enforcement stuff?
We're still live-streaming.
Right, right, come on.
And this one here.
Yes, yes.
Look at this fur color.
This kind of shade,
how luxurious, just look.
Look at the shoulders, everyone.
Yeah, show us more support.
Still streaming?
Place your order!
Three, two, one, cart's open!
Alright, alright, stop streaming, stop.
Come over here, come here.
Sorry, folks.
We've got guests at home.
We need to entertain them.
Stopping the stream, stopping now.
Cooperate with official business, come on.
Shu.
Officers.
So, you've come to our home.
What official business brings you here?
Forest Police, on official duty.
Police ID.
Qi Deyao.
Yes, that's me.
I'm a law-abiding citizen.
Someone reported you.
You've been in the forest,
setting animal traps illegally,
hunting wild animals.
Captain, look.
It's all physical evidence.
All physical evidence.
All evidence.
Let me hear you out.
Hear what?
Just listen.
I'm telling you, no, no.
It's a misunderstanding.
These are all wholesale goods from Yiwu.
Yiwu.
Honey, honey.
Bring the Yiwu purchase order
over here.
Purchased from Yiwu.
All through legitimate channels.
See?
Comrade.
Yeah, look.
They all have tags.
Right.
The tags are right here, see?
Tags.
Every one has a trademark.
Check any of them, all tagged.
Every single one.
Alright, alright, that's enough.
I get it.
Tags.
Got it, got it.
Here, check out this big one.
How's it over there?
Find anything?
Captain Lu.
What's this?
An animal trap.
An animal trap, a trap.
Livestreaming, setting traps in the forest.
Deliberately disrupting the ecosystem.
Young man.
You look pretty handsome,
but you love slapping on labels, huh?
Don't get worked up.
These are props.
They're plastic.
Daughter-in-law, come here.
Demonstrate for the officers.
Officers, watch closely.
Bare foot, bare foot.
Right.
Go on.
See?
It's fake, doesn't hurt.
Fake, can't hurt anyone.
Try it yourself, see?
And every time I finish streaming,
I clean up the whole set
spotlessly.
No harm done to the forest at all.
Hey.
Stop gawking at the show here.
If the Qi family suspects
we're the ones who set them up,
that'd be trouble.
But this is pretty fun.
Let me watch a bit more.
Unbelievable.
Do you know how many people...
how many you've led astray?
Don't you go too far now.
Oh, now you're the righteous one?
These traps of yours,
whether real or fake,
you're placing them out there.
You people have caused
a very bad influence on the public.
Do you understand?
Young man,
you're a good-looking fellow.
Why do you speak so harshly?
You're selling fake goods here, and you still...
They all have trademarks, don't they?
Your wording's off.
You shouldn't have brought
these fake goods in the first place.
They're not fake.
Alright, alright, enough.
Enough.
I understand.
I've got a handle on the situation.
You can sell these things,
but if you're using livestreams
to sell to consumers,
you must respect one thing.
Fake is fake.
You can't sell it as real.
I'll report this to my superiors.
Whatever the penalty is,
wait for notice.
Alright.
I really get it this time.
You two ladies,
from now on, you're not allowed to, you know,
claim it's real anymore.
Didn't you stock this?
You stocked it, Old Qi.
I...
Enough, enough.
Just remember.
Be careful.
Okay.
Shu Qingcang,
next time, verify the facts
before calling us.
We get so many reports every day.
They can't all be this sloppy.
Captain.
Move out.
Moving out.
So...
Remember, now.
Yes, yes, yes.
Yes, don't worry.
I'll fix it however you say.
Officers,
have some water.
No need.
Take care, sir.
Look at that.
Thanks for your hard work.
Thank you, thank you.
Captain.
So it's you.
What's up?
You set me up.
Pulling a dirty trick on me, huh?
What dirty trick?
Captain.
Does Xiaowei know him?
Xiaowei called them.
This big guy is bad news.
Take care, Captain.
Be careful next time.
Okay.
Take care, Captain.
Why is everyone leaving?
Alright, alright, alright.
Nothing to see here.
This Qi Deyao,
what shady thing did he do now?
Said he was poaching animals.
Fined thousands.
Almost got locked up.
Don't talk nonsense.
Don't spread rumors.
It was a mix-up, a false report.
Folks,
break it up, break it up.
Go on, go on.
Head home.
What are you trying to do?
You and your scooter!
Why are you revving it like that?
You wanna hit me?
You're gonna run me over?
Go ahead, hit me if you dare!
Just try it!
Bro, bro!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
I was settling a personal score.
Sorry, sorry!
Xiaofang!
Uh, I was just scaring him.
Xiaofang, you're my witness!
He just tried to murder me, Xiaofang!
Xiaofang!
Xiaofang, where are you going?
Get off, now!
I won't.
Get off!
No way I'm getting off.
What are you doing? Get off!
I won't.
Wherever you go, I go.
Get off, now!
I won't.
Get off!
I'm not getting off!
Get off, now!
I won't. Let's see how you chase her.
Bro, I'm sorry, bro!
I can't win against you.
Your key!
Give me your key!
Xiaofang, Xiaofang!
He said he wanted to ride the scooter,
so I let him ride it.
Qi Xiaowei!
You're playing dirty!
Xiaofang!
Xiaofang, is it heavy? Let me carry it.
Xiaofang, look at this guy.
He's playing dirty, Xiaofang!
And it's uphill too!
You're inhuman!
Xiaofang, slow down!
Be careful, Xiaofang!
Slow down, slow down, slow down.
Just worry about yourselves!
Be careful, Xiaofang, Xiaofang!
Xiaofang, slow down!
What are you doing? You're pulling me!
What?
I'm pulling you? I gotta reach Xiaofang!
Get out of the way!
You!
Where's Xiaofang?
Xiaofang!
Two idiots.
We're done for.
What do you mean, done for?
I've never been here before.
What do you mean you've never been here?
Isn't this the hill behind your house?
I'm telling you, without Xiaofang,
neither of us is getting out.
Don't say that!
Hurry, find her!
Xiaofang, Xiaofang!
Xiaofang!
Big idiot!
Nothing.
Xiaowei!
Qi Xiaowei!
You think this can stump me?
Don't you know what I do?
"Seek the dragon, split the gold, watch the mountain coils."
"Each coil is another gate."
I follow it, going right.
So much stuff still left.
What am I gonna do?
I'm telling you,
I told you not to livestream in the woods.
But you just had to cause trouble.
What are you nagging about?
It's for the livestream effect.
The real environment, you know?
I earn money streaming. You spend it just as fast.
As stingy as you are,
like I could ever spend your money.
I earned all of that myself.
Stop messing with my stuff.
What am I gonna do with all this stock?
That rotten jerk.
He actually reported me.
Bastard, how dare he mess with me.
Who are you talking about?
The guy from earlier today.
Brought people over to throw his weight around.
That guy,
dressed like a gentleman,
driving that little car,
the one chasing after Xiaofang.
No wonder this suddenly happened.
I guessed right.
She really hooked a big fish.
What big fish?
He's just a bully riding on someone else's power.
He himself is nothing.
Now it all makes sense.
He sees you as a rival in love.
Making our family the sacrificial lamb.
Qi Xiaowei.
I'm te- telling you,
you'd better calm down from now on.
If you push him too far,
and he keeps causing trouble every day,
our family can't take it.
Weren't you the one who told me
to win Xiaofang back?
Now he shows up at our place once,
and you wimp out.
I'm telling you, I'm not backing down.
I'll fight him to the end.
This kid's suddenly grown a spine.
Kind of like me when I was young.
Full of yourself.
Uncle.
The details of the situation,
Director Miao and I
have already looked into thoroughly.
All these years,
you've been silently
protecting our forest resources.
You are our
unsung hero.
Comrade Yang Fanhu,
here, put it on.
Fang'er,
you've got to properly thank Xiaocang.
If it weren't for Xiaocang,
could your dad have become a Forest Ranger?
Could your dad
have gotten this armband?
Even without this armband,
my dad still goes up the mountain every day.
He's been a Forest Ranger all along.
How is that the same?
Before, he was on reserve.
Today he became official.
Come on, applause.
Xiaofang,
see how happy your dad is today?
Look how well I handled this.
I'm about on par
with Xiaofang, right?
I think she knows deep down.
After pining for so many years,
today it's official and proper.
It's official.
Huzi
Congrats, congrats, congrats!
Congratulations!
Now it's officially certified, huh?
The title "Forest Ranger" is truly sacred.
You wearing it, you truly deserve it.
Well deserved indeed!
Spit it out. Cut to the chase.
Fine, I'll be blunt then.
Riding your daughter's coattails, huh?
I never thought Xiaofang
had it in her.
I know Xiaofang right now
wants to marry up.
Huzi, but think about it carefully.
Right now, they
don't mind, just chasing the novelty.
Attracted to Xiaofang's cute little face.
But two years down the road?
Once the novelty wears off,
he'll use the kid as an excuse.
What'll happen to Xiaofang then?
Every time I think about it,
my heart
just aches.
After all, the child
belongs to us Qis.
Huzi
We've both been through it, right?
We know better than these youngsters.
As the old saying goes,
nothing beats the original match.
So the best place for Xiaofang
is still with our Xiaowei.
Am I right?
Are you done spouting nonsense?
Xiaofang already told me.
She doesn't want to be with your son anymore.
Huzi.
I sincerely
want what's best for both kids.
We're both fathers, right?
Right?
We can't just let
the kids run wild on their whims.
Here's the thing.
Let's you and me first
hash this whole thing out.
In the end, the kids' marriage
is up to us two dads, isn't it?
Am I right?
How did your son end up
with a father like you?
He's really out of luck.
Cursed for eight generations.
Xiaofang's affairs
are hers to decide.
You're the useless one,
and yet you act righteous?
No wonder your wife ran off with someone.
Back then you couldn't control your wife,
now you can't control your daughter.
Yang Fanhu!
Who are you calling a dog?
Just you wait, you'll get yours.
I could just bite you to death!
I'm so mad!
Huzi.
I steamed these.
Fresh out of the pot.
These are for you.
Two little tigers, two little tigers,
running so...
Okay, okay, here.
Do you still remember?
Back then you loved eating
the buns I steamed.
You could down a whole tray in one go.
Time really flies.
So many years, just like that.
This Forest Ranger job of yours,
you've finally made something of it.
With or without this armband,
the job's the same.
What else could I do?
How have you been lately?
I've been going on blind dates.
I was thinking
of finding someone in our village.
Find someone
I grew up with,
someone I know inside out,
and make do living together.
No, you can't just settle.
Life is yours to live.
Besides, if you really want to find someone,
you gotta find one with, with...
a foundation of love.
Love?
My daughter taught me that.
But I think
what she said makes sense.
Keep it.
Wipe your sweat.
Now go on.
Okay, okay.
Okay.
Love
Xiaofang
Aunt wants to ask you something
What do you think of Xiaocang
as a person?
Shu Qingcang?
He's alright, I guess
Alright?
That's great!
Then you should
give it a real shot with him
Why would I date him?
Tell me
are you really that clueless
or just playing dumb?
Look
these past few days
Xiaocang has done so much for our family
First he dealt with the Qi family
and let out our Yang family's frustration.
Was that not just a misunderstanding?
And your dad's job
the job your dad has been dreaming of
for all these years
it finally came through, didn't it?
Xiaocang has a real, steady job
and he goes up the mountain with you every day
to dig herbs
He's clearly taken a liking to you
This Xiaocang, you know
He handles everything, inside and out
He puts in real effort
and he's sincere
Xiaofang
A plump duck like this
right at your lips
don't let it fly away!
But I don't like him
And besides
there are no real feelings between us
How could that ever lead to happiness?
Look at all those novels and dramas
Since ancient times
plenty of couples got married first
and fell in love later
And another thing
if he really marries you
for the sake of his own future
he'll have to treat you well
What does any of that matter?
Let me be straight with you
Your Granduncle
wants a great-grandson
He wants the one in your belly
Yang Bite
Xiaofang
You'll always be Yang Bite's mom.
That's a fact nothing can change.
But have you thought about it?
You have to work and earn money.
Where would you find the time
to take care of this child?
Besides,
you make so little money.
What kind of living conditions
could you give the child?
If you give Yang Bite
in Lineage adoption to Granduncle,
it'd be totally different.
The resources Granduncle can offer,
the living conditions,
and the level of education,
compared to you raising him yourself,
it's a world of difference!
You have to put yourself
in the child's shoes
and think about what's best for him.
And think about your own future
too.
Assess the situation.
The wise adapt to the times.
Got it?
Aunt,
giving my child away will make me happy?
Is this the future you're talking about?
Just listen to Aunt this once.
My choice
is the right one.
I see it.
Right here, right here.
Here, Xiaofang, have some juice.
Thanks, you're so attentive.
Xiaofang,
you're truly Granduncle's lucky star.
Granduncle, you're too kind.
You came to our family and did so much,
put in so much effort.
I'm very grateful.
So
I don't want you to lose out either.
Of course.
This is all what Granduncle should do.
Granduncle,
you want a great-grandson, right?
Goes without saying.
But are you sure
what I'm carrying is a boy?
Well, this...
The ultrasound clearly shows a boy.
The little guy,
this is a little boy, right?
Yes, yes, yes.
This is our
Yang family's bloodline!
But Granduncle, look,
what's this?
The little boy turned into a finger!
Granduncle
Let's play a Mystery box game.
Mystery box?
That's right.
My belly is a Mystery box.
Let's make a bet.
Is it a boy inside,
or a girl?
But opening a Mystery box costs money.
Not much.
With a belly this big,
let's just say one million.
And once it's born,
whether boy or girl,
no returns or exchanges.
Uncle Yang, Uncle Yang!
Xiaofang, how can you talk
to Granduncle like that?
What did I do?
Granduncle's been so good to me.
Would I let him get shortchanged?
Granduncle,
we're doing business here.
I've got to get the money I'm owed
upfront.
Wait, you, this...
Oh right, Shu Qingcang.
I'll agree to be Mrs. Shu.
Don't you like me?
Let's go get married right now.
What if I give birth to a girl
and Granduncle doesn't want it?
Then you'd back out too,
and I'd miss out on
such a great husband.
Aw, you're shy.
I'll grab my ID and wait for you.
Granduncle,
I'll come see you next time.
Wait, Xiaofang, you...
Xiao Shu!
Get my heart pills!
I've got them, I've got them.
Here, here, take these.
Easy, easy, easy.
Okay, easy, easy, easy.
Easy now.
Unbelievable.
Still in the womb and already this fierce.
Once it's born,
it'll be just like its mother,
turning the world upside down!
A girl's fine, a girl's great!
What's so great about it?
You're just raising her for someone else.
Your brain's really pickled in soy sauce.
Look at nowadays,
how much you get for marrying off a daughter.
Sons are the money-losers now.
Favoring boys over girls?
That's ancient history.
Girls are great.
You can collect a fortune down the line.
You're obsessed with money.
Two heads!
When my granddaughter marries,
that's another fortune.
Such a great deal!
What are you muttering about?
I, I was just saying...
You gave me two sons,
and I finally get a granddaughter.
I'm happy!
Where's your son?
Lying upstairs.
Useless piece of work.
What's this?
A finger.
And what's this?
A great-grandson.
Definitely a great-grandson.
That Yang Xiaofang is just fooling me.
Yes, yes, yes.
She just doesn't want me to have a great-grandson.
Right.
Didn't you say
Yang Xiaofang agreed to marry you?
You even guaranteed it to me.
You want a future? I'll get it for you.
But where's my great-grandson?
Great-grandson?
You'll definitely have a great-grandson.
Guaranteed.
Guaranteed, guaranteed.
Just give me a little more time.
I'll definitely get Yang Xiaofang to marry me.
And by then,
you'll be the great-grandson in her belly—
the... the child in her belly
will be your great-grandson.
It's out! It's out!
Uncle Yang, this is a good omen!
A great-grandson.
You're definitely getting a great-grandson.
Grandma.
I'll hang this mosquito-repelling
herb pouch on you.
Then you won't get bitten.
Smells nice, right?
Yes, it does.
Did you really do that
right in front of them?
Of course.
Right in their faces,
just... like this.
Who's gonna spoil them?
You're full of sneaky tricks.
Actually, boy or girl, it's all good.
It's a blessing from the heavens.
We should welcome it either way.
Grandma, let me ask you quietly.
We won't let Bite know.
Do you prefer a great-grandson or granddaughter?
I love them both, boy or girl.
The stars up in the sky
and the fireflies down on earth,
which one isn't precious?
Bite.
Even inside the belly,
someone already loves you this much.
You're so lucky.
And I'm so happy too.
Xiaowei.
Xiaowei, wake up.
You've been like this since you were a kid.
What are you doing?
Xiaowei...
Dad let you down.
It's my fault for being stingy.
Back then...
If I had just gladly
handed over the wedding money,
you and Xiaofang would be so happy now.
You've been drinking this early?
Dad admits his mistakes and fixes them.
From now on,
I support you in pursuing love.
Don't be afraid of that Shu guy.
In the face of my son's love,
what is money?
Son, come here.
Let's spruce up today.
Be good.
Let's look sharp today.
Get all dressed up nicely.
Come on, come on.
What are you doing, Dad?
Wear this one.
And this hairstyle...
Let Dad fix it up for you.
Dad knows.
I'm very fashionable.
Look.
Absolutely stylish.
See?
Those gifts...
Bring them along in a bit.
We'll go to the Yang family's place.
Today counts as our first
formal visit.
You must be on your best behavior.
Remember that.
Back then,
how did you win Yang Xiaofang over?
Today,
you're gonna win her back for me.
People need a bit of love in their lives.
Dad understands.
Love.
I love you.
So this is the pig you got
using that pig card?
That's right.
This pig looks so sturdy.
It must taste delicious.
You'd better stay away from it.
This pig charges without holding back.
The pig is here,
but this pig...
who's gonna slaughter it, Sis?
What do you mean?
I'm this pretty.
Me, slaughter a pig?
Only my brother can do this.
Right.
As for my dad,
he went up the mountain this morning.
He said the Forest Rangers have training today.
Then who's gonna do it?
Don't look at me.
With my little frame,
this pig could kill me.
It's gotta be big sis then.
Take the lead now.
Why are you looking at me?
Aren't you ashamed?
You're the only
guy here.
You can call me little sister.
Little sister.
I'm going to the bathroom.
I'm off to do yoga.
You, you, go easy!
It stinks so bad.
No way, no way.
Little sisters, they all ran off.
What the heck?
Why is it you?
Why can't it be me?
It's you, of all people,
out here taking out the trash?
Let me broaden your horizons.
Why are you running?
Move, move, move!
Get out of the way!
A good dog doesn't block the road.
Well, I am the dog.
You little punk, step aside!
Aunt! Aunt!
Xiaofang!
Aunt!
Coming!
Aunt! Aunt!
Aunt!
Xiaocang.
Fresh plums, just washed for you.
Thank you, Aunt.
Come.
Come, come, come.
Xiaocang's here.
He's a guest I invited.
Lately,
he's helped our family a lot.
Qingcang, Qingcang.
Aunt, if there's any work to do,
I can help.
Aunt, I came to work too.
I can do any kind of work.
No need, no need.
You work at a desk, just take a rest.
What work could you possibly do?
Don't make me laugh.
After I get tired at the office,
I do manual work to relieve stress.
You're a guest.
Just rest well.
You're an artist.
Your hands can't get dirty.
No, wait.
How can a guest do work?
Stop fighting over it.
Today everyone's got work to do.
What is it?
Slaughtering a pig.
Okay.
What's wrong?
This pig is so pitiful.
So young and already getting slaughtered.
Can't help it.
It was born a pig.
Hope its next life is better.
Then let's go easy on it.
How's it going?
Can you handle it?
Come on!
When the tide goes out,
that's when you see who's sincere.
Since Xiaofang stopped going on blind dates,
no one comes around anymore.
Only those two
still come by often.
Look at those two.
Clearly neither of them knows how to slaughter a pig.
But for Xiaofang's sake,
they're going all out to impress.
Those in the know say Xiaofang's picking.
Those who don't know,
they're saying out there
that Xiaofang's stringing along two men,
comparing their offers.
How about we vote?
Make the choice for Xiaofang.
Big sister, you go first.
Isn't it obvious?
Shu Qingcang.
Who invited him over?
He's educated.
Jingjing, you're here.
Come to my room for a minute.
I need to talk to you.
Jingjing.
Come, come, come.
Here.
Take a look.
Let me show you someone.
What do you think of him?
Have some water.
Careful.
What do you mean?
Young Shu, Shu Qingcang.
What do you think of him as a person?
What are you getting at?
Isn't he chasing after Xiaofang?
If Xiaofang doesn't fancy him,
those two won't work out anyway.
So I was thinking,
if you took a liking to him,
I could introduce
the two of you.
Unbelievable.
What's wrong with you?
You've gone too far, Yang Fanyan.
I rushed back here
thinking you'd finally agreed
to lend me the money.
But no.
You won't help me raise the money,
and you've still got time
to set me up with a man?
I don't have a mother like you.
This is beyond ridiculous.
Fighting with Aunt again?
Jingjing.
Still angry?
Don't be mad.
Look at you.
Got something good and didn't include me?
Trying to keep it all to yourself again?
What good thing?
Play dumb.
Keep playing dumb.
Come on now.
Don't just think about your own daughter.
Look,
if Xiaofang doesn't want Xiaocang,
and Jingjing doesn't either,
you've still got me, right?
I'm willing.
Have you no shame?
How old are you already?
Have you lost your mind?
Where's your head at?
What are you even thinking?
Last time at dinner,
Granduncle really adored Dandan, didn't he?
Granduncle wants a boy.
Isn't Dandan one?
I could give Dandan up
for Lineage adoption to Granduncle.
And you call yourself his mother!
Even if you're willing,
would Dandan be?
That kid doesn't know a damn thing.
I'm his mother.
I'm doing this for his own good.
As for Granduncle,
he just wants the title.
If Dandan goes through Lineage adoption,
it's just a formality.
Just change what he calls him.
He'd still stay with me, of course.
With Granduncle's means,
Dandan's schooling, his exams,
and getting into college,
we wouldn't have to worry about any of it.
Like his residency,
housing,
finding a wife later,
she'd definitely be a city girl.
You're really dreaming with your eyes open.
You're almost as bad as Qi Deyao across the way.
You're such a schemer!
This kind of thing,
it's not up to me.
Isn't Xiaocang here for exactly this?
Just ask him for me, sis.
Xiaocang, come here a sec.
Someone wants to ask you something.
Something very important.
Very important.
It's nothing, nothing.
What does Lineage adoption mean?
Lineage adoption is when you give your own son
to a brother who has no son
or to a relative as their son.
Pig bro, have a bite.
Pig bro.
What VIP treatment.
Right?
Only gets this before slaughter.
Exactly.
Let's do it.
Sorry, buddy. Three, two, one.
Come on. Three, two, one.
Do you think, while it's asleep,
a stab would still hurt a lot?
Of course it'd hurt.
Nice, listening to music.
Xiaofang.
Is there any
other option?
Wh-what?
I think
it's too skinny.
How about we raise it a bit longer?
You noticed too, right?
We should keep it till New Year at least.
As a New Year pig. How's that?
Alright then.
Let's make a choice.
Decide its fate.
What do you choose?
I choose to set it free.
I choose to let it
go into the forest.
Just think, in the big forest,
there's so much good food.
What big forest?
Send it to the creek.
What's at the creek?
The creek.
It'll suffer a bit now,
but it'll thank me later.
Thank you for what?
I'm a pig-slaughtering maniac. As if I don't know
where a piglet ends up eventually?
It'll definitely thank me in the future.
It's a pig. What does it know?
How about we vote?
Help Xiaofang make a choice.
Choose for it, for its own good.
Does a pig need your fake mercy?
It's a domestic pig.
Setting it free means death anyway.
Quit being dramatic.
Damn, that's fierce!
Grandma
About that choice everyone's talking about,
which would you pick?
I choose
to feast on meat.
So good!
Weren't they saying Dandan went missing?
How did Xiaofang and Jingjing
end up running away too?
Why did you take so long?
What's going on here?
I heard Xiaofang ran away.
We can't find her anywhere.
I want to report it.
Please send officers right away!
What if she's been trafficked?
Don't let him touch my leg!
Help!
If you want to make money,
don't treat yourself like a human,
and don't treat others like humans either.
Get up, get up, something happened!
Look at the time! Stop sleeping, get up!
He couldn't have
actually run off with Xiaofang, could he?