Miao Minzhi
This Yang Xiaofang...
going on blind dates with a huge belly every day.
As the village director,
shouldn't you do something about it?
She's a grown young woman,
and she's not married.
Why should I interfere with her dating?
The amusement park project,
did you tell other people about it?
Those men so eager to date her,
they must know about this.
They're just after
Xiaofang's compensation money.
Right?
Qi Deyao,
even if she has a pretty face,
but...
she's carrying Xiaowei's child!
Otherwise, even if she were a fairy,
no one would want her.
Qi Deyao,
when you have a hammer,
everyone looks like a nail.
What are they after?
They're just after Xiaofang herself.
No matter what they're after,
you have to do something!
Why should I?
It's not like we're becoming in-laws.
Go talk to Fanhu yourself.
Me, go to Yang Fanhu?
Bow my head to Yang Fanhu?
In his dreams!
After her?
Aren't they still after her compensation money?
I absolutely won't let them
get what they want.
Where are you rushing off to?
Xiaowei's sitting idle at home.
None of your business whether he's idle!
Why so worked up? Can't I even mention it?
Yang Fanhu,
can you please
rein in your daughter?
We've had our quarrels, sure,
but look, I agreed to the bride price.
Young couples fight,
they sulk a couple days, then it's over.
Xiaofang's gone too far!
Going on blind dates everywhere,
making this joke spread to the county.
How am I supposed to show
my face?
You have a face left?
Whether my daughter dates or not,
what's it got to do with you?
How is it none of my business?
No matter what, Xiaofang
has to marry into our family.
Says who?
Why?
"Says who?" "Why?"
Because of the child in her belly!
That's our Xiaowei's child.
Which law says so?
Show it to me!
Yang Fanhu,
you're talking law with me?
Let me tell you,
the law can't handle this.
This is ethics,
this is morality!
Use some common sense,
okay?
Sure, sure.
What are you doing?
If you won't talk law with me,
I'll talk fists with you!
Yang Fanhu,
your daughter's reckless,
and you're just as reckless as she is!
Your own wife
is out there chasing after other men,
and you still have the nerve
to sit here reading?
Didn't you say nobody wants Xiaofang?
So what's the rush?
You...
You're so calm sitting here.
Have you come up with some plan?
Xiaofang likes herbs.
She said she'd gather herbs for the baby.
I get it now.
You're doing this to win her over,
catering to her interests, right?
But how long are you gonna read?
Fine, I'll stop reading.
Okay? I'll stop.
Okay, read, read, read.
Okay, read on. I won't bother you.
Okay.
Hurry up and finish.
So noisy, chattering away.
Mushrooms.
Xiaofang!
How can you walk backwards over here?
That's impressive!
What are you doing?
Making your tears flow back in?
It doesn't hurt, doesn't hurt.
Xiaofang.
I...
You went on that blind date,
and I was so upset
I couldn't eat properly,
couldn't sleep properly.
Did you eat these poisonous mushrooms?
Xiaofang!
Lean against the tree.
What is this?
Poison.
Xiaofang, you did the right thing.
I really do deserve to die.
You once laid your sincere love
right there in front of me.
Qi Xiaowei.
You brought this pain on yourself.
This won't make me get back with you.
Get back together?
Xiaofang wants to get back with me!
Xiaofang!
You're getting back with me!
This Master Jia
is quite a well-known figure
throughout the surrounding villages.
He specializes in resolving inner turmoil
and clearing the mind.
Master Jia, I've heard so much about you.
Uncle Yang, have some tea.
By all accounts,
my body normally
doesn't have any real issues.
So why do I feel so weak,
so uneasy inside?
What have I got to be uneasy about?
I've already retired.
You have no grandchildren.
That's the source of your unease.
You've got something weighing on your heart.
Master, you're absolutely right.
What I lack is a grandson.
But may I ask, Master,
how can I stop feeling this way?
In your family,
do you have any close relatives
who are already pregnant
and about to give birth?
I don't think so.
No.
Actually, there is one.
Take a look.
"Single mom bravely seeking marriage."
What in the world is this?
Going on blind dates with a kid?
Isn't that a disgrace?
Old boss,
this is Yang Xiaofang.
Who? Xiaofang?
Yang Shu's granddaughter.
Right.
She's a proper close relative of yours,
and Xiaofang is pregnant.
That's it, then.
The child in her belly
is your source of strength.
Once you have him,
your heart won't feel empty anymore.
Xiao Shu,
hurry up.
Go to the Yang family and find Xiaofang.
Yes.
Mr. Yang,
your credit card is long overdue.
We're hoping you can
pay it off as soon as possible.
I mean, look at you,
calling yesterday, today, every single day.
Aren't you sick of it?
Not at all, Mr. Yang.
This is my job.
I have to remind you
that the consequences of
an unpaid, overdue credit card
are very serious.
I don't have the money.
That's all I've got to say.
"No money, no money."
Look,
if there's really no other way,
just ask your family for help.
Fine, fine, fine, I got it.
Stop calling.
Don't be so stubborn about it.
Who am I supposed to ask? Who?
Hello.
Who are you looking for?
I'm here for the Yang family.
The Yang family?
Yes.
Which department are you a leader of?
Not quite yet.
Thanks for the kind words.
He'll be a big shot in the future.
Oh, no, no.
Zhu'er.
Yang Fanzhu.
Shu Qingcang.
You...
What are you doing here?
Looking for you.
For me?
You...
I hardly recognized you.
How long has it been?
Over ten years, I think.
About ten years.
I remember when you...
first left to make your way.
I only came up to your chest.
Yeah, time flies.
Now you come up to mine.
Look at you.
In that suit,
you look sharp!
It's just work attire.
That car...
Is that yours?
Just for getting around.
Man, you're doing well.
You... you...
Where are you working now?
Nothing fancy, really.
What's that noise?
Uncle.
How is he?
Nothing serious.
The antidote Xiaofang gave him,
it's fine, works well.
It's been days, and he's still like this.
And you call that fine?
Come on, Uncle,
do you actually know what you're doing?
Anyone who eats poison mushrooms
gets loopy for a few days.
If he likes singing, just let him sing.
Let him sing.
Our family's pig,
after eating poison mushrooms,
for a whole month, thought it was human.
Stood up and talked back to me every day.
Give him this medicine, this one.
This is for dogs.
Here, this is for humans.
This one, okay.
Okay, okay.
Uncle.
Thanks for your trouble.
I won't see you downstairs.
No need, no need.
Quick, hold him down!
Hurry!
Look at you,
saving money at your son's expense.
Getting a vet?
What does he know?
You think your son's a pig?
You got that right.
Running off to eat poison mushrooms.
If he's not a pig, what is he?
Fine, sing, sing, sing.
Come on.
Yell louder.
Yell over this way.
Shut it, let them hear!
Sing!
Sing that way.
Let the neighbors hear.
Sing!
You pighead!
You little brat, who are you calling a pig?
You beast, ordering me around?
What are you doing?
No!
Xiaowei!
You little brat!
You've gone mad, mad!
Xiaowei, Xiaowei, Xiaowei!
Don't hurt yourself, Xiaowei!
He's gone mad, mad!
Mad!
Mad, mad!
Your boss is my uncle?
Yes.
I've been driving
for Uncle Yang for years now.
Didn't he
retire years ago?
He did.
But the company's busy,
and Uncle Yang keeps saying
he's not up to it anymore.
Then why are you still driving for him?
Well,
I'm interning at the company now,
so Uncle Yang still has to lead the way on a lot of things.
My uncle arranged this for you?
Yes.
That's why Uncle Yang's my benefactor.
He may have retired,
but we can't just give him the cold shoulder, right?
Exactly.
So I want to serve him well,
enrich
and make the most of
his retirement years.
That's the right attitude.
As a person,
you should repay kindness.
These are plums from our farm.
Try some.
Have plenty.
They're really delicious.
Thank you.
We haven't been in touch for over a decade.
Coming by out of the blue,
is there something going on?
What could there be?
Uncle Yang's getting on in years,
feeling nostalgic.
Mid-Autumn Festival's coming up,
so let the family reunite
and have a lively time.
Xiaofang,
do you remember Grand-uncle?
Vaguely.
Grand-uncle was pretty fierce.
Grandma,
do you remember that year
when he tried to hit me for something?
You even argued with him.
Mom, one New Year,
what was it Xiaofang did
that got Uncle so angry?
Xiaofang
broke your uncle's teapot,
and he wanted to hit her.
Right.
Grand-uncle raised his hand to slap me,
right in the face.
My dad rushed up and grabbed him like this.
What's wrong?
Did you pull something? What is it?
What is it? You didn't pull anything, did you?
To the hospital!
Hospital, hospital!
Quick, start the car!
Let's go!
Take mine,
my four-wheel-drive sedan.
I...
Don't panic, it's okay.
Auntie,
why do I feel like since I came back,
my belly's grown a lot bigger?
Of course.
The family's been feeding you well.
The baby's growing by leaps and bounds.
But the days ahead
are going to be tough.
The fetus is developing healthily.
First child, right?
Yes.
Here, look.
This is the baby's head.
This is the baby's leg.
So fun.
So amazing!
Doctor
Is this...
Does it look like a boy?
If you think so, then it is.
If you don't, then it isn't.
I don't mean anything by it.
I just wanted to ask.
Should we prepare some...
little dresses,
or little pants, you know?
Auntie, stop asking.
Boy or girl, we'll love it.
Get both dresses and pants ready.
That's a lot to prepare!
Doctor, can't you give us a hint?
All right, the exam is done.
Right, right, right.
Your hospital has rules.
Come on.
Let me wipe it off for you.
Get up slowly.
Come on.
Put your shoes on.
Here.
As long as everything's fine.
Yan'er.
Brother, brother, Dad.
Don't worry.
The doctor said
mother and baby are both healthy.
Take a look.
Look,
isn't he...
crossing his legs?
Lying flat at such a young age.
That's way too comfy!
Will he even want to come out?
No, no, no.
He wants to come out and meet me too.
Here, this is...
It's a boy!
A boy, great, a boy!
Xiao Shu,
why are you so excited?
You like kids too?
I do. A boy's great, a boy's great!
A girl's great too.
Right, both are great.
A boy's great.
Look at that cloud.
It looks like Cupid.
I saw it in Xiaowei's studio.
Who is this?
Cupid.
He symbolizes love.
He's a little angel.
A little angel.
I've decided.
I'll name him Cupid.
Call him what?
Yang Bite.
That's quite a foreign-sounding name.
Great name.
Cupid, I know him.
He's that...
little boy who shoots arrows,
right?
Yes, the one who loves shooting arrows.
Right, right, right.
A boy, a boy.
A boy's great, a boy's great.
A girl's great too.
Jingjing.
Jingjing!
I've been calling you forever.
Didn't you hear me?
You... you're here too?
Didn't you say you were in Guangzhou
and not coming home for the holiday?
I felt like coming, so I came.
Well, if you're coming back,
you should've told me in advance, right?
Right?
What are you doing at the hospital?
What else would I be here for?
I'm sick.
You're sick?
What kind of illness?
A serious one.
Give me some money for treatment.
Jingjing.
Don't be scared.
No matter what illness, don't worry.
I bought medical insurance.
Whatever illness you have,
they have to pay for it.
Okay, okay, okay.
I'm not sick.
Not sick? You just said you were!
Are you sick or not?
Not sick.
You...
Then why are you at the hospital?
Don't tell me you got a boyfriend
and got in trouble?
What are you thinking?
It's Grandma who's sick.
But you said you were sick.
How about this? Come here.
I'll...
give you
some money.
Buy Grandma some supplements.
A hundred thousand.
How much?
All to save Grandma's life.
Where are you?
Mom!
Son!
I missed you so much!
Where's your dad?
Dad didn't come.
He had me come by myself.
You came by yourself?
He made you travel all that way alone?
Debt collectors come knocking every day.
Boss Qian said he has to lay low.
He couldn't take me with him.
So basically he stayed in Shenzhen
and I came to find you.
So you're not going to school?
Dad got me a month's sick leave.
Mom.
What is it?
You didn't want me to come?
About your dad's situation,
I don't want the family to know.
Keep your mouth shut.
Whoever asks me,
I'll just say Dad's busy with work.
Busy counting money.
Remember what I told you.
Uncle Hu's quiet, remember to greet him.
Your other uncle talks a lot, just tune him out.
Watch out for Auntie Fanyan.
She's obsessed with saving face.
Loves to compete with me.
Don't let her find out
that our family's struggling.
Or she'll laugh at us.
Who told you that?
Qian Dandan
You've gotten chubbier again!
Sis
Pregnant women all gain weight.
How come you didn't?
Back in my day,
when I was pregnant with your sister Jingjing,
I stayed slim too.
Well, when I was pregnant with you,
I didn't gain weight either.
Let me do it. Go eat.
Pour some broth on it.
Because you're all such well-behaved kids.
What's up?
Get up for a sec.
Sis,
is it gonna be a nephew?
It might be a niece, you know.
Whatever you have is fine.
I'm happy for you either way.
Boys and girls are equal anyway.
Same thing.
The hell are you happy about?
Eat.
Come on, Mom, sit down and eat.
Fanyan, put it here.
Right in front of him.
Dandan,
have some meat.
Grandma's the best!
Here.
Grandma missed you, Dandan.
This meat's made just for you.
Come on, take a bite.
It's all yours.
Thanks, Grandma!
Is it good?
So delicious!
I haven't had such tasty braised pork in ages.
Grandma!
Eat up, eat up.
That's 'cause your mom's a cheapskate.
Starving Dandan, no meat for him.
All she knows is spending money.
Buying herself new clothes, jewelry.
Your mom's so rich, all she's got is money.
What else can I do but pinch pennies?
What if Dandan grows up
and turns out like his sister Jingjing?
Just two phone calls a year.
When I'm old, no one to care for me.
Then don't I have to
save up for retirement myself?
What's wrong with providing for yourself?
That's called not burdening your kids.
You think raising kids means they'll take care of you?
The end result is always
getting shipped off to a nursing home by your daughter-in-law.
Dandan,
how could your dad bear
to let you come back all alone?
What's he so busy with?
His dad's busy collecting project payments.
Quit fishing for gossip.
Have some sense of boundaries,
you hear me, Yang Fanyan?
I'm just chatting with the kid.
What nerve did I hit with you?
Boundaries, my foot.
Do you even have any?
Every time you come back,
you're all high and mighty,
strutting in those sky-high heels,
like you wanna trample everyone
under your feet.
What happened this time?
Only brought one pair of heels?
Don't tell me
your old man Qian went bankrupt?
Mom, you...
I didn't say it.
Auntie guessed it herself.
Qian Dan,
let's go.
Mom!
I really didn't say it.
Old Qian really did go bankrupt?
It can't be true, can it?
Auntie clearly guessed it herself.
Why are you hitting me?
Stop hitting me!
Don't bother trying to stop her.
What's wrong?
Got too much energy to burn?
Here.
Eat these noodles.
Laughing at my expense, are you happy now?
I knew something was up with you.
Every time you came back before,
you'd swagger around showing off,
running here and there,
afraid nobody knew you married a rich guy.
But this time,
you won't set a foot outside.
No matter what,
you shouldn't hide things from family.
Still putting on a brave face.
Aren't you exhausted?
Yang Fanyan.
Don't stand there
shedding crocodile tears.
Ever since we were kids,
you've always been fake and phony.
Mom says you're sensible,
outsiders say you're respectable,
only I know how phony you really are.
That damn Old Qian,
he's dragged me and my kid down like this,
forced to hide out in the village,
becoming a laughingstock.
That bastard!
Once I'm back, I'm divorcing him!
You've never held a job in your life.
Divorced with a kid to raise.
How are you gonna make money?
How are you gonna support the kid?
Besides,
a woman your age,
what kind of man could you even marry?
No matter what,
Old Qian is Dandan's real father.
Right?
And he's got a sharp mind.
He'll find a way to make money.
He still has connections.
Just bear with it.
Get through this rough patch with him.
Can't you do that?
How am I supposed to get through it?
The debt he owes isn't small.
If it weren't for Dandan,
I'd have divorced him long ago.
If you divorce,
who gets Dandan?
I'm not as clear-headed as you.
Even if we had to live on scraps,
I'd never abandon Dandan.
I'm capable of raising him well.
Right.
Don't be like me.
Ended up so pathetic that
even my own daughter
refuses to acknowledge me.
A hundred thousand.
It's all for Grandma's life-saving treatment.
Consider it a loan from me.
I'll definitely pay you back later.
But...
I don't have that much in my account.
And right around the holidays too.
Where am I supposed to scrape it together?
Fine, I get it.
If you don't wanna give it, just say so.
What kind of attitude is that?
Am I still your mother or not?
What gives you the right to talk to me like that?
Every time I see you,
you've got a sour face.
Silent as a stone, not a single word.
And when you finally do speak up,
first thing out of your mouth is a hundred thousand.
Let's be fair here.
Your grandma getting sick
has nothing to do with me.
Your dad and I divorced long ago.
Whoever's supposed to pay,
it shouldn't fall on me, right?
Why shouldn't it?
Have you cared for me all these years?
It was Grandma who worked her fingers to the bone
to raise me.
Now she's sick and needs money.
I think you're the one who should pay.
I've never cared for you?
Every month,
right on time,
I sent your living expenses
straight to your dad's card.
I work my butt off out there every day.
Who am I doing it for?
Isn't it all for you?
I never cared for you?
Have a conscience when you speak.
Fine.
I have no conscience.
Right.
You do.
You have a conscience.
Help me pay Grandma's medical bills.
Okay?
I'm begging you.
Did Jingjing upset you again?
Don't mention her.
It's all my own doing.
How old is this girl now?
Why is she still so immature?
I'm gonna call and ask her
what she really wants.
No, no, no, don't.
Let me call her.
No, no, no.
Don't provoke her.
Listen to me, just ignore her.
You're just too soft.
Always feeling you owe her.
And she's got you wrapped around her finger.
How about this?
In a couple days, I'll call her
and tell her to come back.
Then you can deal with her.
Take my advice.
Even if Old Qian's not doing great,
you've still got money
invested with me, right?
What's there to worry about?
Alright, alright, alright.
Hurry up and eat your noodles.
How much money I've got left,
don't I know it myself?
Anyway, with my investments,
only profits, no losses.
You should be secretly thrilled.
That looks like Shu Qingcang.
Shu Qingcang?
Where?
Over there.
Why is he here?
Who knows.
Why is that car back here again?
Stop staring, stop thinking about it.
You're the one who rejected the daughter-in-law.
What's the point of watching her now?
Isn't that Xiaofang?
Has she landed some rich guy?
Coming from the city,
maybe he's got some inside info?
What inside info?
This Yang Xiaofang
is quite the operator.
On one hand, she's got your son
completely devoted to her.
On the other hand,
she's already in a luxury car.
Morals are going down the drain.
Ethics have collapsed.
The one who ate the poisonous mushrooms is feeling better.
Quick, come take a look!
Come on, right now,
something juicier than poisoned mushrooms.
So rude.
Here, take it.
Thank you, Grand-uncle.
May you, Grand-uncle,
have lucky days as swift as the wind,
bountiful years soaring like a kite,
more blessings, more wealth, longer life,
long as mountains, deep as seas, everlasting.
This kid's tongue,
so slick!
Really impressive.
I told you already,
watch fewer short videos.
Well, this kid's smart.
He's got a bright future ahead.
Manxia,
you're truly blessed.
Sons and daughters both,
grandchildren all around,
a flourishing family.
Thanks to your blessing.
Xiaofang,
you need to eat more these days.
Get more nutrition.
It's really important.
Xiao Shu,
take care of her.
No problem.
Have a shrimp.
Just peeled it.
This one.
Whole grains, they're good for you.
Here.
Thanks, I can do it myself.
It's fine, I know it's hard for you.
Here comes the main dish!
Braised pork!
Let me say a few words.
Seeing this dish,
I...
have so many feelings.
It reminds me of the old days.
I remember my youngest son,
on his birthday,
he said to me, "Dad,
I want a meal of braised pork."
But back then, I was poor.
Couldn't afford it.
I looked at
my son's pitiful little eyes,
and swore to myself,
if I ever made something of myself,
on the Yang family's table,
there'd be meat at every meal.
After hearing Uncle Yang's teachings,
I feel enlightened, like a spring breeze.
It made me realize
the importance of following the right person.
My family used to be poor, too.
My father
gave me life,
but Uncle Yang
gave me a life worth living.
Ever since I followed Uncle Yang,
my family
can finally afford to eat meat.
This reminds me of that old saying:
Follow the right person,
and even wrong things become right.
Follow the wrong person,
and even right things become wrong.
Uncle Yang,
you are the right person
in my life.
I hope
I can closely follow Uncle Yang's footsteps,
so that I—
No,
so that all our lives
can get better.
Come, come, come.
Tea in place of wine,
let me toast you first.
What kind of nonsense is that?
Learn a thing or two from him.
Words from the heart!
So talented!
It's all thanks to Uncle Yang's guidance.
Xiangyong, Xiangdong,
you both have kids, right?
Yes.
We do, yes,
but not a single one with a handle.
Mom,
what does "one with a handle" mean?
You're one with a handle.
As the old saying goes,
no matter how tall a tree grows,
its leaves return to the roots.
I have only one wish now.
The Yang family bloodline
cannot end
with me.
Fangfang,
eat more,
get more nutrition.
You're our great hero!
In the future,
when our Yang Bite studies in the county,
you can come to me for help.
Grand-uncle, you mean Yang Bite—
What I mean is,
what I'm saying is,
Fangfang,
you young people
must take care of each other.
From now on,
if you have any troubles
in life or with money,
just come to Grand-uncle.
We're not strangers, you know.
Thank you, Uncle Yang.
Have some food.
Come on.
Everything I needed to say,
I've said.
I believe they got the message.
You mean
asking for the baby?
I feel like they
didn't quite get it.
Is it really that hard to understand?
It's not your fault.
They're just not sharp enough,
slow on the uptake.
So you need to hammer it in,
make sure they understand.
Got it, got it.
So,
about my internship becoming permanent next year...
Although with the company bosses,
I do have some pull,
but
success depends on effort.
When it counts, you'll have to rely on yourself.
I'll keep your teachings in mind.
You're like a second father to me.
Without you,
I wouldn't be where I am today.
I'm like your own son.
So about the baby thing,
you absolutely have to make it happen.
Understood.
Take care on your way.
Waiter, pack this up.
Is that him?
That's him.
What are you worried about?
I already looked into everything for you.
That guy at his workplace
is just an intern.
His pay, compared to regular staff,
is only half as much.
Nothing to brag about.
But doesn't he have
a car too?
What does Xiaowei have?
Why are you boosting his ego?
Relax.
I checked out that car too.
It's not even his.
A conman.
A marriage scammer!
This Shu guy is definitely shady.
He's got ulterior motives.
I won't let my Fang'er
climb out of one mess
just to fall into another.
Did he just
insult himself too?
Where is he?
Just up ahead.
Today we've got to teach
this Shu guy a lesson.
Right here.
Is this really gonna work?
The most sophisticated wars
are often won with the simplest methods.
Let's do this.
Run, run, run, run!
Hey, buddy.
I really don't think you need to do this.
Don't be shy.
Driving the boss around every day,
your neck and shoulders must be sore.
Keep pressing.
I'm saying, you really don't have to.
Don't let the plain look fool you.
I've asked around.
This master's quite famous around here.
He only opens two hours a day.
Booking a spot is really tough.
Boss!
One bowl of beef sour-soup handmade rice noodles.
Over there, please.
What the heck?
Master, show us your skills!
Okay, okay, stop, stop!
Really, no need for that.
Look here.
Buddy, if you've got something to say,
just tell me straight up.
Just get to the point.
A dragon in shallow water gets mocked by shrimp.
A tiger on flat ground gets bullied by dogs.
Brother, I'm just going through
a bit of a rough patch.
See?
I knew you had something going on.
Life has its ups and downs.
It's totally normal.
When it counts, you rely on friends.
Here's what you do.
Whatever it is, just say it.
And I'll
handle it all in one go.
One-stop service.
But let me be upfront.
What I can help with, I'll help.
What I can't help with,
I'll break my rules to help you.
With those words from you,
I'm about to start borrowing money.
Money's no problem.
How much?
Fi—
Five hundred?
Five hundred, I'll transfer it now.
Fifty thousand.
How much?
Fifty thousand. Recently
I just joined a financial project,
and I'm short 50,000 yuan
in cash flow.
I'll only need it two days, then pay you back.
Just two days.
Cang, Cang, Cang, Cang, Cang!
You— help me out this once,
and I'll help you next time you need it.
You must handle the child's issue for sure.
Yes, yes, understood.
Did I say I was leaving?
I'm just a little jealous of you.
So young,
and already into finance projects.
How does that saying go again?
Gone half a lifetime, still a youth on return.
Master.
I admire your courage.
And not just you.
Even your niece, Xiaofang,
she really dares to think and act.
With that Xiaowei guy,
she cut him off just like that.
It's over.
Us Yangs,
we lack a lot of things,
but we've never lacked backbone.
现在啊
Translation>
Now,
even if Xiaowei begged on his knees,
Xiaofang wouldn't give him the time of day.
Really?
Impressive.
That said,
Xiaofang's so young.
She'll definitely find someone else later.
But bringing a kid along is such a hassle.
Ever thought of giving the child away?
No way.
Absolutely not.
With the Yang family backbone,
we don't do such shameless things.
No way.
That makes things tough.
What's so tough about it?
People lining up to meet Xiaofang
are in a long queue.
Can't even meet them all in a day.
Not tough at all.
When she meets the right one,
won't the kid have a dad?
Fate.
Yes.
And fate,
isn't that ruled by the God of Wealth too?
Lao Cang
I knew you could help me
Thank you, Lao Cang
Zhu'er
You know, a guy like me
might seem a bit worldly
but deep down inside
I'm just like you
just like Xiaofang
I long for true love too
Lao Cang, this...
this isn't appropriate
What's inappropriate about it?
It's just not right
I really think that
your Xiaofang is a wonderful girl
What?
I treat you like a brother
and you want to be my niece's husband?
What?
He's got his eye on Xiaofang
It sounds absurd
but it's the absolute truth
See, what did I tell you
When Uncle wanted to play matchmaker that day
none of you believed it
Now you get it, right?
But I think
this Xiao Cang isn't much of a catch
If he got a permanent position, maybe then
Fanzhu, I think
Make a call
Set up a meeting with Xiao Cang for me
I'm the biological father of Yang Xiaofang's child
I'm warning you
Stay away from her
A second marriage is worse than a dog's life
Xiaofang's best bet
is still with our Xiaowei
My belly is just like a blind box
Let's just take a gamble
See if it's a boy inside
or a girl
A good dog doesn't block the road
Well, I'm the dog then
Auntie, is there any work to do?
I can help out
Auntie, I came to help work too
Stop fighting over it
There's work for everyone today
What is it?
Slaughtering a pig