Is this the house?
Yeah, this is it.
When did you get here?
I came yesterday.
Been here a while.
Came right after breakfast.
Have you eaten yet?
Is this her brother, or...
Mom! Mom!
Mom!
Xiaofang blew Cupid's quota, Mom!
Alarm! Mom, Mom, Mom!
Code red alert!
Outside! Outside!
What's the panic?
The wolves are here!
What's going on?
Making such a fuss.
Bro! Bro!
From medium-rare to well-done.
All shapes and colors.
A whole crowd of guys, look!
They've blocked our front door!
Wait, what's going on here?
What's the deal?
Blind dates!
Here to meet Xiaofang.
What? Who's here for me?
Just look!
Blind date!
This is ridiculous, isn't it?
Now I get it.
My two hundred bucks.
What two hundred bucks?
That matchmaking video of mine.
I paid for promotion.
Big data's really that powerful?
Isn't this just insane?
Chase them off!
Chase them off, chase them off!
Bro, chase them off for me!
Bro! Bro!
Kick them out, get rid of them!
Bro, bro, bro!
Actually, I think...
Why don't we think bigger?
They're already here.
Let's check them out. Stay calm.
You're absolutely right.
Fanhu, Fanzhu!
Open the door and welcome them.
I want to see for myself.
If those two hundred bucks were worth it.
Hold on, Mom.
The thing is, my daughter's not worth...
Just...
just two hundred bucks? Come on!
Bro.
Go online more in your spare time.
Get online more.
Thanks for coming, everyone.
This is the first round.
Once you pass this round,
you enter the courtyard,
which is the VIP waiting area.
Whether you get in
is entirely up to you.
Let me introduce someone.
This gentleman
is my older brother.
The eldest of the Yang family,
in other words, Xiaofang's father.
But
there's no need to be nervous.
My brother looks serious,
but he'll guarantee this is
fair, just, and transparent.
Alright, alright.
Brother.
Gentlemen,
How you play reveals
your character.
Let's begin.
Checkmate.
I win.
Low emotional intelligence.
Eliminated.
I lost.
Letting me win, phony.
Eliminated.
Indecisive.
Isn't that too strict?
Grandma,
what's your standard for a partner?
The most important thing
is good looks.
My name is Wang Defa.
I'm thirty this year.
I'm a farmer.
I raise chickens that lay eggs.
I'm honest and straightforward.
I hope Xiaofang gives me a chance.
This is a little something
I brought for Xiaofang.
Alright, you pass.
Thank you, thank you.
Wait a moment.
The eggs.
If Xiaofang agrees,
I'll set up
an exclusive livestream room for her.
I'll just
meet her halfway.
Hey folks!
Done reporting?
My name is Hu Xiang.
My strong point
is that I'm very accepting.
Xiaofang,
and the baby in her belly,
I'll treat them both well.
This young man seems decent.
I work as a programmer.
My monthly income is 30,000.
I own a place in the city too.
Pass.
Wrong way.
Over here.
You're in quite a hurry, huh.
Where did you dig these guys up?
This is utterly embarrassing.
I just came to see
how pretty Yang Xiaofang is.
You and that guy from before
came in the same car.
Get lost, get lost!
Nothing better to do.
Scandalous.
That's what you get for showing off.
You ruined a perfectly good thing.
I mean, come on,
there were plenty of good options.
Would Xiaofang really settle
for our Xiaowei?
It's over.
No turning back now.
You.
Tomorrow, go grab a number too.
Get in line.
You go line up if you want.
I can't afford the humiliation.
After you, CEO.
Time for us to step in.
Vice President, shall we?
First off, congratulations, everyone
for making it to our final round.
We have four judges in total.
Only with a unanimous vote
can you stay
and officially
enter the matchmaking interview with Xiaofang.
Please welcome our first candidate,
Mr. Wang.
Yes, yes, yes.
You've been divorced, right?
Yes, yes, that's right.
So what do you think
is the most important thing in a marriage?
Tolerance.
Not minding that I'm poor,
not pushing me to be ambitious,
and not complaining about my bad sleeping habits.
No way.
Me, I'm planning
to buy a house in the county first,
then one in the district,
and finally in the city.
One, two, three properties.
But the deeds,
her name won't be on them.
So you're looking for
a free baby-making maid,
Am I right?
Didn't I tell you to leave?
I haven't even met her yet, I can't go.
I think your looks are
just so-so.
The negging type.
But he's pretty honest.
I'll definitely treat Xiaofang well.
Xiaofang already agreed by default.
I love you.
I wish to ride the wind and return home,
yet I fear those jade palaces above.
You wanna bet
I'll kick you straight into the pond?
Get out.
Show's over.
Mr. Right?
That only exists in soap operas.
Don't lose heart.
We should press on while we're ahead
and really
ramp up the promotion.
We'll definitely find someone.
More of them?
Next batch.
Time to end this farce.
How do we end it?
Bring out our backup stock.
This guy is really thoughtful.
He's not here yet,
but the gifts already are.
He knows how to do things right.
If he wants to meet, tell him to come here.
The county town is so far away.
I don't want to go.
He runs a hobby class.
He's got tons of things to handle.
Well, I'm a pregnant woman.
I'm busy giving birth here.
Cut the smart talk.
Would I ever hurt you?
Just look at him.
Such an artistic vibe.
A textbook
eligible bachelor.
An eligible bachelor?
What would he want with me?
Thinks I'm decent-looking?
Or that I can bear children?
He's a boss, and educated.
Those weirdos you mentioned,
how can they compare to him?
Let me be straight with you.
Two years ago,
his wife got sick
and passed away.
He has a daughter.
A grown man like him,
raising a daughter alone,
finding a suitable match isn't easy.
You're about to give birth,
so he can't be picky, right?
Standing in front of him,
you're not beneath him.
If you two really work out,
then a girl named He
marries a guy named Zheng.
A perfect match!
You can't shut me up.
This is one I acquired
as a new piece last year.
It's a seven-character regulated poem.
Written in oracle bone script.
Look over here.
These are some of the awards
I've received over the years.
Boss Hao, what an impressive resume.
Oh, not at all.
Let me tell you,
don't underestimate
the kids around here.
Hidden talents everywhere.
Take him for example.
His father
is the Agriculture Bureau Director.
Do you still remember
what I taught you last time?
This final vertical stroke,
it must be
clean
and crisp.
Let me introduce you to someone.
This girl.
Her dad owns a listed company.
Sweetie.
This "fa" character, this stroke here,
draw it out a bit longer.
You really tailor teaching to each student.
It's only right.
Personalized teaching is all the rage now.
Then how come I never see you
give this kind of attention
to the other kids?
Come here.
Come, come.
Xiaofang,
the fact that you'd ask that
shows you're still young.
A person's energy is limited,
so you must spend it
on those most worth it.
In the future, really,
the people who need to write
are the ones with
social status.
Take, for instance,
those two kids from just now.
You've got to read the room in life.
The ones worth grooming, teach them harder.
The rest, just getting by is enough.
Your kid's the same, actually.
What kind of person
he becomes in the future,
it all depends on
what kind of father
you find for him.
That's the key part.
I've truly been blinded by a single leaf,
missing the whole mountain.
All I have left now is admiration for you.
Xiaofang,
hearing you say that
really warms my heart.
It shows you understand what I'm saying.
I just realized
what you really resemble.
Come.
You're just like this sheet of rice paper.
Full of spirit,
but still completely blank.
Once you're with me,
I'll shape you
in every possible way.
Like that blue outfit you're wearing today,
I suggest you never wear it again.
It doesn't suit you.
I want you to wear more white,
so you look
pure.
Boss Hao,
I'd really love to learn from you,
but I already have a teacher.
And which master are you studying under?
Ever since I can remember,
I've been studying under
the famous Master Yang Fanzhu,
learning about the world.
Master Yang is renowned.
Surely you know him?
Of course, of course.
Of course.
Master Yang Fanzhu, of course.
We know each other well.
Right.
Master Yang's calligraphy is very famous.
Of course.
Then let me write something
and you give me some pointers.
Sure, sure, sure.
Lay out the paper.
Here.
Which brush do you use?
I learned grand freehand style from Master Yang.
Use that big one.
So bold.
Come, students.
Come on, everyone over here.
Let's study the grand freehand style.
Why did she write "daddy"?
Xiaofang was being sarcastic.
That boss was so full of "daddy energy."
What's "daddy energy"?
You don't even know "daddy energy"?
You, you...
Why do you fold planes like this now?
Can that even fly far?
Grandpa will fold one for you.
The kind of plane we played with back in the day.
That's how the teacher taught us.
Just listen to Grandpa.
This "daddy energy"...
means not respecting others.
Always thinking you're the best,
the greatest.
Wishing everyone in the world
would have to listen to him.
Keep it down.
So Xiaofang wasn't into him then.
Of course she wasn't.
Xiaofang has high standards.
At the very least,
he'd have to be like me, your son.
You're really something.
I'm a master.
Great teachers raise great students, right?
If you don't agree, just don't agree.
No need to mess with the guy, right?
Auntie,
you have no idea.
The way he kept bragging himself up,
so full of himself.
If he hadn't been putting on airs,
would I have treated him like that?
Enough is enough.
I know a lot of people
are lining up to date you,
but you have to be careful
about your own reputation.
Don't go treating yourself
like some big superstar.
I didn't.
Why wouldn't she be a superstar?
In this county now,
guys looking
for a good wife are everywhere.
Even with money, it's hard to find a wife.
Our Xiaofang
is basically
a superstar on the dating scene.
Son, you need to watch out.
The more suitors she has,
the higher her standards get.
You've got to do something,
sweet-talk her back.
You hear me?
I got it, I got it, enough already.
Brother Hu.
No, wait, Uncle Hu.
Let me get that for you.
You take a break.
Yeah yeah, Uncle Hu.
Want some water?
I just brewed some tea.
Uncle Hu, have you eaten?
Let's grab a bite together later.
They're all calling me uncle?
Uncle Hu, come on.
Come on, Uncle Hu.
Uncle.
What do you think of me?
What do you mean?
I'm not bad-looking, right?
Could you go for me?
What if Uncle Hu did go for you?
Marry you or something?
Exactly.
What are you all fooling around for?
Get back to work.
Go, go, go.
Little Lu,
these buddies of yours,
why are they all calling me uncle?
What's going on?
Uncle Hu,
you've worked hard.
Why are you calling me uncle too?
Actually, I should be calling you uncle.
I'm not even thirty yet.
About the same age as Xiaofang.
This is for you.
Thank you.
You're really skilled.
My family are woodcarvers by tradition.
Originally, we used to
build palaces for the emperor.
Don't worry.
If we really end up together,
I'll treat this child well.
Raise them as my own, for sure.
Doesn't matter if it's a boy or girl.
When they grow up,
I'll pass this craft down to them too.
Passing it down is a good thing.
But it also depends on the child's wishes.
Yeah, right.
We'll have more kids later anyway.
If they don't like it,
I'll pass it to our own kids.
Lu, you're really thinking far ahead.
Xiaofang,
there's one thing I really like about you,
and it's especially important.
You're pregnant, but
you still hike and work the fields just fine.
Means you're healthy and can bear kids well.
If we get married,
we've gotta hurry and have our own.
I really love kids.
Let's have five or six.
Five or six? Can you support them?
Of course I can.
All the money I earn from now on,
I'll hand it all over to you.
Lu, you love kids.
I love kids too.
You want five or six kids.
I want five or six kids too.
So here's the deal.
Why don't we just
have a whole basketball team?
How about it?
We don't need that many.
Not that many. Look,
a basketball team with subs
is only twelve.
I won't do anything else.
I'll just have kids all day long.
You'll hire me nannies and maids.
Let me think.
Once the kids grow up,
each one needs a house in town.
Prices in our town these days
aren't that high.
Just prepare ten million and we're good.
I'm healthy enough.
I just don't know if
your wallet's up to it, Lu.
Just as I thought.
Wait, where'd she go?
Aren't you playing basketball?
What are you dancing for?
Stop dancing.
She left.
That basketball guy just now,
he was here with Xiaofang.
She's gone.
I was keeping an eye out for you.
Don't worry, bro.
Xiaofang didn't agree.
Well, of course.
Bro, what are you
so smug about?
At her pace,
finding the next guy
is just a matter of days.
Stop dancing.
Why just sit here sighing?
What else can I do?
Just beat him up.
Then no one in the village
will dare mess with Xiaofang.
So every guy she meets,
I beat up?
How could I even live in this village?
No, bro, at this point,
you can't afford to care about that.
Exactly.
Your happiness for the rest of your life
is about to slip away.
Seems the ones my brother set up
aren't reliable either.
This isn't looking for a wife.
This is looking for a baby machine.
Better let me handle it.
Second Auntie has picked out
a perfect one for you.
Good-looking,
educated,
low-maintenance, not bossy,
obedient and loyal.
And most importantly,
rich.
Am I getting this right?
You're my blind date?
Sorry about that.
My son is a bit shy,
so I came to chat on his behalf.
No wonder you're a superstar mom.
Full of ideas and boldness.
Daring to think, act, and own it.
I really love a personality like yours.
Just like me.
Xiaofang,
I'm very pleased with you.
As long as you're willing to marry in,
a 200,000 yuan dowry,
transferred directly,
paid on the spot.
Auntie,
this is only our first meeting.
There's more.
The car and house are fully paid off.
You can move right in.
And one of my shops,
I can give you one too.
I promise,
your future good life
will make everyone envious.
Hold on,
even if you offer, I can't believe it.
We can sign a prenup
and put all of this
in writing.
Sorry, but
is your son unable to take care of himself?
No.
Infertile?
Absolutely not.
Way too old?
That's not it.
You look pretty young yourself.
Then what is it?
Stop guessing.
Shijie is a great guy.
He's very talented,
clean, and has good taste.
Keeps the house spotless,
and dresses very sharply.
He's really likable, very popular.
I'm just worried
he'll get led astray by the wrong crowd.
People say I'm too strict with him,
that I've smothered him silly.
Calling him a mama's boy and all.
I don't think that's true.
What right do they have to say that?
I just want to find him
a girl I think is right for him.
Ma'am
I don't think
this is right for me
Well, think about it
If the man isn't home
and he just pays up
what's the big deal?
Plenty of women
would kill for this, okay?
Sis, only you
could live like that
Everything you get for free
comes with a price tag attached
If Xiaofang marries into that
who knows what she'll go through
Uncle really thinks ahead
Let Uncle set you up instead
Someone reliable
A top-tier corporate guy
From our hometown
He happens to be on
vacation and coming home
I'll set up a meeting
I've got a good feeling
Meet him
As we all know
The countryside of the past
had limited functions
Idle resources
Talent draining away
But in today's society
demand for rural areas is exploding
City folks crave green mountains and clear waters
Young people
have a burning passion for startups
You must be wondering
why I'm meeting you like this today
What?
This is the age of efficiency
My schedule's fully booked today
During breaks in the lecture
we can chat simultaneously
You're probably confused
that I'd even agree to date you
Yeah
When my uncle told me
I almost cried tears of joy
Don't sell yourself too short
I have my reasons for meeting you
And you have your own value
Me? I have value?
I thought I was just
an ordinary person
Exactly
Your value
lies in being ordinary
After you marry me
you'll come with me to the big city
I can make money
but I don't have time
I need a woman
to manage the household for me
and take care of the kids
Someone as outstanding as you
must have plenty of women
willing to run your home and raise kids
lined up for you
But
none of them are cost-effective.
Some won't have kids
Some want me to sacrifice my career
to boost their own
And some actually
make demands of me
Isn't that ridiculous?
Ridiculous
But I think you're different
Good-looking
Presentable
Not vain
And willing to have kids
At the end of the day
I'm still a traditional good man
Dependable
Responsible
With a stable job
And plenty of earning power
Of course, I'm not pressuring you
You can occasionally
have afternoon tea
get your nails done
just like any housewife
Take photos, post on social media
So everyone around you, friends
and family
will know how happy your life is
This guy...
what does he actually look like?
I don't remember.
He's such a great catch,
and you don't even remember
what he looks like?
It's not my fault.
His face was like a blank mask.
No features at all.
Xiaofang,
what on earth is going through your head?
He's a big-city elite,
has a car, has a house,
and you're still being picky?
Well, why don't you go then?
You don't like this one,
you don't fancy that one.
What kind of guy are you even looking for?
I don't really know.
I think there should be mutual respect,
mutual trust,
comfort and ease.
Most importantly, we have to love ourselves first
before we can love someone else.
I can't quite explain it.
It's about the feeling, Auntie.
What the heck is "feeling"?
Can it give you money to spend?
Or raise your kids for you?
Actually, I get exactly
what our Fang'er just said.
Look at these guys.
Yao Jiahao,
Carpenter Lu,
Boss Hao,
Shijie, Han Jun.
They all show up wearing masks.
You can't see their faces,
and you can't see their hearts.
Speak plainly, would you?
You're the only one who doesn't get plain talk.
One's the guy you, Fanmei, like.
One's the one Fanyan likes.
One's the one you, Fanzhu, like.
And another one
is the one Fanhu likes.
Is this even Xiaofang's matchmaking anymore?
Aren't these all the ones you lot picked?
Our Xiaofang
has to find someone she likes,
right?
If there's no feelings,
then that's not called a match,
"matching"...
that's mating pigs!
Excuse me, coming through.
Coming through.
Take it slow.
Slow down, slow down.
Slow down.
Oh my goodness.
Careful, it's slippery.
Huzi.
Huanhuan.
I haven't seen you in years.
What brings you here?
Came back to see your mom.
My husband...
passed away last year.
Now it's just me.
I figured, out there is just out there.
Home is still best.
This is where my roots are, right?
Right, right, right.
Coming home feels grounded.
Grounded.
How come I heard...
your Xiaofang's out on blind dates everywhere?
Young folks these days...
they're really bold.
Way better than back in our day.
What about you?
Still on your own?
Okay.
They're here, they're here!
It's the rule.
No money, no getting out.
No, no, no.
No.
We've got the red envelopes ready.
Besides...
What's this?
You can't just raise the price now.
Whose family, right before getting out...
seems to be about the exit gift.
In-laws.
Our family's spent plenty too.
Bought a house, bought a car.
Just to get these two kids married.
We've emptied out our savings.
You think raising a daughter costs nothing?
Still won't pay?
Then forget the wedding.
Wait, you...
Xiao Zhu.
Get out.
Are we having this wedding or not?
Zhang Quan.
My mom had a tough time raising me too.
Just give it to her, okay?
Come on.
Didn't we already agree on this?
I'm begging you, alright?
All these relatives are watching.
Fine.
Son.
We're calling off this wedding.
We're not buying a daughter-in-law.
Let's go.
What the heck, you!
What are you even saying?
Zhang Quan, are you a man or not?
I am a man.
What kind of attitude is this?
Making me pay extra just to get out.
I don't have money.
Didn't I buy the house? The car?
Shameless.
I'm begging you.
Please cut our family some slack.
This is just a one-time thing for me.
It's a once-in-a-lifetime thing!
Then I'll go borrow it, okay?
Once I borrow it, I'll give it to you.
I want it now.
Let's talk this out nicely.
What kind of attitude is that?
I was following Xiaochao at the time
And we ran over to that
front entrance of the hotel
I wanted to go see them
And then, you know
I saw two groups start fighting
Xiaozhu with her mom and dad
were on this side
And on the other side was
Zhang Quan with his mom and dad
And this side was yelling
Get out of the car! Get out!
I won't! My daughter!
So what happened next?
In the end, they paid up
They paid up
Xiaozhu got out only after getting the money
I watched them up on the stage
"I love you"
"I do"
It was so weird
That's just what you think
Don't believe me? Ask Xiaozhu in a few days
Those two will keep living just fine
Sure, on the surface life goes on
But won't it bother them deep down?
It's like a nail hammered into a wall
Pull out the nail
and that hole in the wall
will always be there
Yes, that's exactly what I mean
Grandma
you totally speak my mind
People were poor in the past
Feelings were pure
Now people are rich
And everything has a price tag
Money's become the basis of marriage
And love has transformed
into a luxury item
Why are you learning from Yang Fanzhu too?
Never talking like a normal person all day
Auntie, you're amazing
Those are Master Fanzhu's exact quotes
Listen, Xiaofang
Can you stop running your mouth?
You've been willful enough already
After so many blind dates
You haven't liked a single one
At least pick one for us, would you?
Right?
My dad secretly told me yesterday
There's no rush
He'll support me
He's the one who spoiled her
What's most important in marriage?
Fanmei
You tell her
Money
She shouldn't have asked you in the first place
You're really obsessed with money
Even the husband you want is surnamed "Money"
If you ask me
All men in this world are the same
All crows under heaven are equally black
Grandma
Auntie says Grandpa is a crow
Says he's as black as a crow
That's a lie!
That's not right
Your grandpa
has genuinely cool, pale skin
The lantern paper for our ancestors
It can't fall into the river
Good thing I fished it out for you
The ink's all smudged now
I threw it in on purpose
You were gonna throw it away anyway
Why toss it into the river?
"Madam Zhou of the Qu family"
My grandma didn't even deserve a name
Might as well toss it in the river
Same with my mom
Her tombstone reads,
"Madam Wang of the Yang family"
But I remember her name
Before she passed, she told me
she secretly carved her name on a big tree
And told me not to forget her
But I feel that as long as
I think of her, remember her
she'll always be here
So then
What was her name?
Xiuhe
And your grandma?
My grandma's name is
Zhou Yunfang
Do you have a pen?
Yeah
Let's write their names
on the lantern paper
Okay
So you gather herbs
Yeah
Dad, Mom.
You... you stubborn girl!
The lantern slips the whole family was waiting for,
and you just grabbed them?
This child of mine...
Why are you so stubborn?
You won't even follow the ancestors' rules.
The coarse cloth Grandma wove
is still buried at the bottom of the chest.
Why can't she have a name on it?
Besides,
we float these river lanterns
so that those who've passed on
are remembered and missed, right?
If you don't write it, and I don't write it,
who's going to remember them later?
Well,
the child does have a point.
Fine, fine.
Hurry, hurry, hurry.
Come on, come on.
Dad, Mom,
don't forget:
my grandma's name is Zhou Yunfang.
We remember.
Thank you.
This...
is prickly pear wine I brewed myself.
I'm the one who should thank you.
That day...
your grandpa really...
crashed straight into my heart.
Love at first sight?
Your grandpa and I,
it really was love at first sight.
Xiaofang,
when your grandma was young,
she especially loved flowers.
Every time grandpa came down the mountain,
he'd pick lots of wildflowers for grandma.
Right?
No wonder!
That's why my dad always
brings home a bouquet of flowers.
Your dad takes after grandpa.
Deep down,
they're both romantics.
That's right.
For a while, I kept waking up from nightmares.
Dad would hold me,
and in his arms,
smelling his scent,
I felt so safe.
Sometimes when I think back now,
I feel like I can still smell
that faint scent on him.
Grandma,
did grandpa ever say
he loved you?
He did say he loved me.
Mom,
in your generation,
who ever talked about love?
Besides,
I've never heard my dad say it.
Your dad,
he did tell me he loved me.
When I married him,
he told me
he'd love me forever.
Then when I had you,
he told me again,
"I'll love you and our child forever."
Then when we had you too,
he said again,
"I'll love you and the kids forever."
Your dad,
in front of you kids,
he's always so serious.
But when it's just him and me,
he's shameless.
He'll say anything.
Mom,
That's dad sweet-talking you.
Dad's spoiled you rotten.
That's right.
I'm so blessed.
That's what love is.
Come on, mom, have a drink.
I want to be just like grandma,
and let love come crashing in on its own.
By the time Xiaofang's baby is born,
the new prickly pear wine will be ready to drink.
Flowers bloom, leaves fall,
and the little puppy grows up.
That's when you realize how fast time flies.
But love is different when it comes.
You just know, right away.
Mom.
Do you still miss Dad?
Hasn't he always been with me?
No, no, no.
Leaving isn't the end.
Being forgotten is.
The memories of your dad in my heart,
there are just so many.
Do you think these river lanterns we set out,
will they receive them?
They will.
It's not scary when someone passes away.
Being completely forgotten,
that's when they're truly gone.
What's your name?
I'm Yang Shu.
Shu, as in a big tree.
And you?
Qu Manxia.
Man, as in stretching out.
Xia, as in rosy clouds.
Mom.
Cheer up.
Don't cry, don't cry.
Be happy.
It's okay, be happy.
Turns out love
isn't rushing to pair up,
nor is it what others say is a good match.
It's like Grandpa and Grandma,
walking slowly,
loving deeply.
Be gentle, gentle, gentle.
Don't push so hard, okay?
You'll squeeze the baby out.
I didn't.
I'm just listening for movement.
Why are you talking nonsense?
Look how rough you are.
How am I rough?
Doctor.
Is this...
Looks like a boy, doesn't it?
The baby in her belly
is your leverage.
Once you have him,
you won't feel insecure.
I only have one wish now.
The Yang family bloodline
can't end with me.
It just can't be cut off.
Xiaofang.
Eat more.
You're the big hero here.
Xiaofang is so young.
She'll definitely remarry someday.
But having a kid is such a hassle.
Ever thought about giving the kid up?
This Shu guy is definitely shady.