(Previously)
I have something to give you, Hia.
You've given me so many things already.
It's time I give you something in return.
How thoughtful of you.
Tonight is our last night.
Wanna play Maruko?
(Thai slang for having sex)
Hia...
Wanna shower together?
Sure.
Hey, baby.
Don't call me 'baby'.
It makes me feel so awkward.
If I'm a little mouse... (Baby in Thai
is "Noo" which also mean a mouse)
How big is a buffalo?
As big as...
This!
Hey!
I'm sorry.
I don't like that at all.
Try calling me 'baby' again.
Baby.
Again.
Louder.
Baby!
Hey!
Remember this.
Don't raise your voice at me again.
You have no right.
Can you call me 'baby' again?
Just one more time, please?
My boyfriend is a bit weird.
But he's cute.
Hia.
I'm hungry.
Let's go eat.
Yeah.
I'm sleepy, but I'm also hungry.
Wait a second.
Go put some clothes on.
Or I won't be able to control myself.
When did you buy these matching shirts?
Whenever I wanted because I have money.
Right.
I'm kidding.
I bought them when you went to buy shoes.
I knew they'd look good on you.
What should we eat tonight?
A beachside beer garden.
Speaking of beer, it reminds me of our bar.
We should be able to open next week, right?
Who said we're opening next week?
We need to find an auspicious date first.
Opening a business requires good timing.
And we need a housewarming blessing.
(Buddhist tradition before opening a shop)
So we won't run into any more bad luck.
Okay.
Since we're looking for a
date for opening the bar...
Should we look for a wedding date too?
But we're already married.
Since when?
Since you put this ring on my finger.
Then let's go to the district office.
Let's register our marriage.
Don't skip steps.
You have to ask my dad for my hand first.
Sure.
We can go as soon as we're free.
How serious are you? [Famous Thai lyrics]
How serious do you want
me to be? [Famous Thai lyrics]
You're so adorable.
"ChermChey"
(Episode 10)
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Hello, Dad.
Hello.
Is there anything I can help with?
Take a look inside.
Hey there.
Where is everyone else?
They should be here soon.
Oh, congratulations, by the way.
Thanks.
Has anyone else arrived yet?
Just P'Lit and Nine.
Oh gosh.
P' Ton overslept.
We almost didn't make it.
As usual.
Yeah.
Let's go help inside.
Hia.
How is it over there? Is it done?
It's done.
Has the master arrived yet?
He should be here soon.
Where are your friends?
Just Ton and Aiyaret left.
Oh.
Hey, I'm here, my friend!
I'm here!
In.
The master is here.
Hurry, everyone!
Go wait inside.
Erng and I will welcome the master.
Okay.
Let's go, Erng.
The shop looks beautiful.
I'm glad to perform the
opening ceremony today.
By the way, what's the name of the shop?
It's ChermChey, Master.
ChermChey.
Where does that name come from?
It's a combination of my
name and my boyfriend's.
Your boyfriend is quite cute.
Where should we start?
Upstairs, Master.
Ah.
Let's begin then.
Yes, sir.
Oh! Master!
Master!
It was just a joke.
Oh.
Sathu.
Erng.
I'm so hot.
Are you possessed?
May your business prosper
and be highly successful.
Thank you, Master.
See?
That wasn't so hard.
Wow.
I'm completely drenched in sweat.
Well, everything is done.
I shall take my leave.
Sathu.
Master!
You forgot your bag.
Thank you.
It's good to get some rest.
You barely slept last night.
And you've been running
around since morning.
No need to rush or compete.
Just being together is enough.
Hey!
How did you get in? I locked the door!
You're not fast enough for me.
Hia!
You little rascal.
I'm not letting you go.
You won't let go?
Is this how you want to play?
Is this what you want?
Yeah.
You want to do this?
Today is Sunday the 18th.
An even day.
As agreed,
you do even days,
and I do odd days.
Today is an even day.
So it's your turn.
Really?
Did I get the days mixed up?
I'm sorry.
Then come here and let me bite you.
May all sentient beings,
partners in suffering...
Please save me!
Are you praying for mercy,
or do you want me to punish you?
Please have mercy on me!
Hia!
Why is my bedsheet stained?
I didn't mean to.
Shut up!
We can wash it tomorrow, Erng.
Go wash it right now.
I'll wash it tomorrow.
I already changed it for you.
Go wash it.
We can just use the black one for now.
It's the same thing.
I want to use the pink one.
I don't care.
Goodnight.
I'm sleeping.
I'm not getting up.
You're not getting up?
I'm going to sleep.
Get up.
Are you going to wash it or not?
Not now. I'm sleepy.
Suddenly feel sleepy huh?
Go wash it right now!
I'm already asleep.
Oh, wow.
Leave me alone.
I guess you're not afraid
of your wife anymore.
Hey.
Get up.
Go do the laundry.
Wait.
Go wash it.
Hia, go do the laundry right now.
I'll do it tomorrow.
I want it done today.
Tomorrow is fine, Erng.
If you don't wash it, what
am I going to sleep on?
I already put a new black one on for you.
Isn't it the same?
I want the pink one. I like pink.
I'm going to sleep.
You've gotten so stubborn lately.
Hey, what are you doing?
I'm not going.
Ouch!
Erng!
Wash it!
Erng, I'm not playing.
You want a piece of me, Erng?
You're the one who wants it, huh?
You want a piece?
You want to go? Get up!
Get up!
Go wash the sheets.
Go wash the sheets!
Hia!
You want more?
I told you to wash the sheets!
You really want to mess with me, Erng?
You're not going to wash them?
You want some of this?
Are you going to wash the sheets?
Are you going to wash them?
Fine, fine! I'll go!
Hurry up!
Move it!
I'm going!
Hurry up!
Can I at least put on my shoes?
Hey!
Geez.
Wash them quick. I like pink.
Mirror, mirror on the wall...
Who is the fairest of them all?
It's Erng, of course!
What? I didn't say anything.
Then who said it?
Is this really your house?
Of course.
It's so spacious.
This is my dad's house.
My house is around here, close by.
Not too far.
Do I look presentable?
Any more presentable and
you'd be wearing monk robes.
I really want to smack your mouth.
You're always so brave about hitting me.
You've gotten so bold.
Erng.
When we grow old...
Can we be Uncle In and Aunt Erng...
living here together?
Sure.
Do you want me to?
If you haven't left me by then...
I'd love for you to live with me.
I'm blushing.
Erng Erng just asked me to
spend the rest of my life with her.
Huh?
You're the one who started it, Hia.
Hello, Father.
Hey there.
Dad, what is there to eat?
I'm starving.
Wow, you just got here and
you're already asking for food.
Go get him some water first.
Fine, I'm going to the restroom first.
I really need to go.
Do whatever you want.
But I really have to go, Dad!
Whoa.
Huh?
Ouch, that hurts!
Go, go. Go wherever you want.
Hey, In.
I'll get you some water.
Wait here for a bit.
Yes, sir.
I bet...
Erng Erng's dad...
decorated the house like a
princess, just like Erng Erng.
Holy crap.
Whoa.
You must be In, right?
Hello, Mother.
Hello.
You're much handsomer
in person than in the photos.
Thank you. You're very
beautiful too, Mother.
Thank you.
I brought some fruit for you.
I hope you enjoy it.
Thank you, dear.
Have a seat.
Thank you.
Oh, dear!
Sit on the chair, sweetie.
Up there.
Oh, right.
I'm sorry.
I'm just a bit nervous.
That's a bit hard to swallow.
It wasn't me.
It was me, dear.
Aren't you embarrassed?
And where did Khem go, Dad?
Why did he leave In all alone?
Khem went to the restroom.
In, dear, Khem told me...
that you like your
food on the spicier side.
So I made a few spicy dishes for you.
But I'm not sure if you'll like them.
I can eat anything, really.
Except for vegetables.
Ah, that's good.
The princess is here!
Dad, I told you to change the sofa.
Do you think my legs are tiny?
Isn't this sofa too small, Dad?
You should buy a new one next time.
Right.
I look so tiny right now.
Did Dad talk behind my back to Hia?
Oh, who would talk behind your back?
Is there anything good to say about you?
Wow.
Plenty, Dad.
I'm pretty, right, Hia?
Right, Hia?
Erng Erng is pretty, right?
Yes, you are, N'Khem.
Who taught you to call me that?
Oh.
Sorry, I was just following
your parents' lead.
Just so you know, Khem.
Your husband has already
been bought by Mom and Dad.
Who wants to be a millionaire?
I do!
He's all mine now.
Stop.
I'm not playing anymore.
Dad.
I'm hungry. Let's go eat.
Mom.
When you can't get your way
with Dad, you turn to Mom.
Well, Mom's cooking is the best.
Dad's cooking is just mediocre.
Then go eat that mediocre food, kiddo.
Should I let you starve instead?
Go on.
Hey!
Go, go eat.
Go.
Go eat.
Come on.
Hey.
Let's eat.
Yes, Father.
If you say yes, then get up.
Going right now, sir.
If I marry Erng...
will I get all of this?
Wait until I die first.
I'll leave it all to you, son-in-law.
I'm definitely marrying her then.
Good, good.
I'm not marrying him.
What?
Why not?
I'm afraid of black magic.
Nonsense.
If you're not sleeping yet, stay here.
I'm going to bed.
Make sure to bring the
clothes down from the car.
Khem is just sulking, son-in-law.
You can check on these tomorrow.
Yes, Father-in-law.
I'll go make it up to him now.
Go ahead, son-in-law.
Geez.
What's with this father-in-law
and son-in-law stuff?
I can't stand this.
And just so you know, I'm not sulking.
Hey, Dad.
Who's Khem? I'm Erng
Erng, the prettiest girl.
I'll excuse myself now.
Go ahead, son.
Erng.
Erng, dear.
I've been looking at these
amulets until my eyes are blurry.
Isn't that how it should be?
But why call each other
father-in-law and son-in-law?
Well...
Because your dad is my father-in-law.
Whatever makes you happy.
I'm just glad to see you two getting along.
Erng.
Are you showered and ready for bed?
When did you take a shower?
While you were busy examining your amulets.
Was I...
examining them until this late?
Yes.
If it weren't this late, I
wouldn't have called you.
Taking a shower now,
the water must be freezing.
Don't worry, my house has a water heater.
Whoa!
I...
I I'm frightened.
Why did you jump like that?
I'm scared of ghosts.
Oh my god, you scared me too.
Can I...
rest my head on your lap?
Hmm?
Sure.
You're the sweetest.
Seems like we need to
buy a new sofa next time.
This one is so small.
Should we turn it off?
And go to bed properly?
No, I still want to watch.
I want to see how it ends.
Okay.
Then just lie on my lap.
Erng.
Yes?
When I said I wanted to marry you...
I wasn't joking.
You're not proposing during
a horror movie, are you?
No.
I won't propose right now.
But when the time actually comes...
please don't say no.
I'll be waiting for that day.
You're the sweetest.
And you're the best in the world.
I love you.
I love you too.
Saying "I love you" during a horror movie.
Want to make our own movie, Erng?
I'll show you how.
And who are you playing with? Tell me.
Whoever's lap I'm lying on.
A change of scenery would be nice.
We have to wake up early to
make merit with Dad tomorrow.
In the morning.
I'll definitely be able to get up.
Then you'll have to drag me along.
Let's go do it then.
Ow!
Right now?
Well, you won't get up.
If we're going to do it,
let's go somewhere better.
P'Nai and N' Erng.
Do you think our husbands
will survive grocery shopping?
I think my husband, In, is good at it.
Hmm.
Aiyaret is just as good at it,
you know.
Sis, can you not try to outdo me for once?
I don't give In any credit.
Even if he is my best friend.
Hey, Erng, let me ask you something.
How did you two meet?
That monk friend of mine told
me a story so confusing, I'm lost.
Can you tell us, or is it a secret?
He really did make a mess of the story.
Saying they met here and
there, it's all over the place.
But it's not a secret.
Then spill the beans, sweetie.
Oh sis, calling me "sweetie"
just because you want to gossip.
We met on a temple trip,
had a one-night stand...
and then he confessed he liked me...
before disappearing to
host a Kathina ceremony.
A Kathina ceremony?
Yeah, a Kathina ceremony.
At first, I thought it was
just a one-night stand.
But I didn't expect him to come back and make
my dream of having a real husband come true.
What about you guys?
How did everyone meet?
Hmm...
I don't really remember.
But as far back as I can remember,
P'Tonhon has always been in my life.
Our houses were right next to each other.
Yeah, his family claimed him
while he was still in his mother's womb.
Wow.
As for me, we were friends.
Then you got drunk, and
Ai ended up devouring you.
Right at the sofa in condo.
But how do you know so much, Nine?
That night, I passed out drunk.
But I know everything.
Every single detail of what happened.
And how did you find out?
Nai told me everything.
It's like he was proud of being devoured.
And you...
you and Lit.
You kept it so quiet, you jerk.
By the time we found
out, you were drunk with In.
Drinking beer until you were wasted.
I heard you threw a shoe
at your dad too, right?
That's a private matter.
But we're friends!
Spill the tea.
It was nothing.
Out of nowhere, Lit came up to talk to me.
Just making casual conversation.
Next thing I knew...
how did I end up with such a hot guy?
Wow.
Oh, please.
Whoa.
As for the day I went with In...
there was a little misunderstanding.
So I had to mark my territory.
He's mine.
Everybody hands off.
Wow.
Hmm.
Nine is definitely the wildest one here.
Are any of my friends actually normal?
Seriously.
But P'Ton is normal.
Oh, please.
I think he's the worst of them all.
Everyone!
Okay, one, two, three, cheers!
(One year later)
Erng, it's time to fulfill our vow.
You're just looking
for an excuse to travel.
Look.
The essentials.
So we have everything.
Let's see what's in here.
You already know.
That's enough. Why so many kisses?
Or...
do you want me to kiss you somewhere else?
Just try it.
Come on.
I'm leaving.
Where are you going?
Erng.
Matching shirts.
What do you think?
Let's buy them to wear together.
Sure.
But isn't it too much? We're
only going for a few days.
Better to buy and not wear
than to want and not buy.
I'm too tired to argue.
Take it.
I'll take them then.
We'll take these two.
No bag, please. I'll put
them in my shoulder bag.
Are you sure you're not
checking other people out?
I haven't even looked at anyone.
I don't look at anyone else...
since I got a fierce wife.
Am I fierce?
Very fierce.
You beat me up without mercy.
I think eight of my ribs are broken.
Oh, please. You're the
one who's fierce with me.
I'm calling the cops.
You're crazy. I'm not talking to you.
My wife is so cute.
Look.
There are seashells too.
I'll buy them for you.
Thanks.
Let's keep shopping.
Look.
If I wear this hair clip to the market,
will I get beaten up?
If anyone dares to touch you,
I'll protect you.
I feel so small and safe with you.
That's a good thing.
Then I'll wear this
clip to fulfill our vow.
I feel so lucky to have you.
Saying "lucky" a million
times wouldn't be enough.
I'm lucky to have you too.
Aww.
Last time I came here, I was so clueless.
But this time, you have me.
Your personal temple boy.
Wait for me here.
I'll be right back.
Where did you go?
Go buy one of these for yourselves.
This one makes your
husband love you like crazy.
This one makes him totally obsessed.
And this one makes him super handsome.
I knew it. He totally scammed me.
Let's take some picture.
That's enough.
I didn't mean to show off my husband.
(Noknoinarak: My friend got a
husband and won't stop showing him off)
But everyone still accuses
me of showing you off.
Where are we going after this?
Where do you want to go?
A nice restaurant...
Or street food?
The latter sounds good.
Then...
Sausage and grilled clams.
Dirty-minded!
What's dirty about it?
You're the one with the dirty
mind. Sausage is just sausage.
And grilled clams are
just scallops on a skewer.
I can't with you.
Always so dirty-minded.
Hey!
Erng.
You always pick on me.
Go eat your sausage and
clams somewhere else.
Don't talk to me anymore.
Erng.
If you pull away again...
You won't get any sleep tonight.
When we were praying earlier...
I wished for us to be happy forever.
I made a wish too.
But I think...
This temple is really powerful.
Why?
Because I'm already happy now.
I just made the wish,
and I'm already happy.
Still as cheeky as ever.
And do you like it?
I love it.
I think the world is strange.
I don't even know how we ended up together.
Yeah.
Do you still believe in destiny?
No.
I think finding someone
you like isn't hard.
Making it last is the hard part.
Then you have to feed it with sausage.
It feels like we're not
even on the same page.
Let's go.