Do you recognize
what this is?
Changqing!
Guards,
- Prince Xin is unwell.
- Changqing!
- Escort him back to his palace.
- Your Highness!
Calm down.
- Restrain him!
- Tell me now!
- Your Highness!
Changqing!
Who are you?
- Your Highness!
- Changqing!
Who are you?
Changqing!
Tell me, who are you?
=Blossoms of Power=
(Adapted from the novel, After My
Bloom, All Flowers Wither by Jin Huang)
=Episode 10=
Your Majesty,
I was shocked to realize
that Commandery Princess Zhaoning
and my late wife
share many similarities.
Changqing, watch your words.
Commandery Princess Zhaoning
is exceptionally intelligent.
What's difficult about making incense?
Are you suggesting
that in the entire world,
only your wife was an incense master?
Ladies from noble families
conduct themselves with grace.
Tapping one's fingers while in thought
is just a common mannerism
among young women.
It's hardly unique to your wife.
As for the talk of two moons in the sky
and the star gate opening,
even the Observatory Official
can't explain the reason behind it.
For you to use
such a mystical and unprovable event
as evidence
is far too forced.
Changqing,
your wife
passed away three years ago.
Could it be
that in your deep longing for your wife,
your mind has become unsettled?
I would like to ask
the Commandery Princess
to clear my doubts herself.
You have long resided in northwest.
How did you know
about that secret mountain path?
Your Majesty.
It seems at this point,
I can no longer hide it.
I admit
that Prince Xin's Consort and I
were close friends who had never met.
What?
Close friends?
Allow me to explain, Your Majesty.
The year I came of age,
my brother, Shen Yun'an,
was ordered to the capital.
Seeing how much I missed my brother,
my father gave me a carrier pigeon
so I could correspond with him.
Unexpectedly, the pigeon was injured
and fell into the home
of a young lady in the imperial capital.
After she nursed the pigeon
back to health,
she had it send a message back to me.
I wrote back to thank her.
Through this exchange,
we became close friends
who communicated only by letter.
That young lady
was Prince Xin's Consort.
Indeed.
Impossible.
I've never heard of this.
Qingzhi told me stories
of the imperial capital,
and I told her about life in northwest.
We both had a passion
for blending incense.
The secret mountain path and the
method for making Jati flower incense
were things Qingzhi told me about
in her letters.
After she married
into Prince Xin's Manor,
our correspondence gradually lessened.
It was only later that I learned
of her unfortunate passing.
I was deeply grieved.
Changqing,
do you have anything else to say?
Zhaoning,
this has all been a misunderstanding.
Please don't take it to heart.
Prince Xin did not harm me.
I am willing to let the matter rest.
Now that everything
has been cleared up today,
I hope Prince Xin
will abandon that incredible delusion
and stop chasing shadows.
Do you know
that even if the person hidden deep
in your heart
changes their appearance,
they will eventually be recognized?
Your deep love for your wife
is admirable.
But if this longing
has turned into an illness,
perhaps it would be better
to live in seclusion
to recuperate and cultivate your mind.
so as not to disturb others again.
Changqing,
if there is any more
improper conduct,
I...
will surely punish you severely.
Please forgive me, Commandery Princess.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Your Highness.
There is one thing I don't understand.
I'd like to ask you about it.
What is it?
Qingzhi had a proud and aloof nature.
She rarely socialized with anyone.
Why was it
that she was only close to you?
I don't want to say.
Fine.
Then I won't ask again.
Let's go to my temporary palace.
I had Tian Yuan
prepare some wild game dishes.
Please have a taste.
You're not going to ask anymore?
If you don't wish to say,
then I have no right to pry.
Everyone has their own secrets.
We aren't even engaged yet.
Even if we were,
I couldn't interfere
in your private affairs.
And I certainly have no right
to question you.
Your way of thinking
is quite different from other men
in the world.
A marriage contract
gives a husband
the privilege of helping his wife
with her troubles,
not the right to interfere
with her thoughts.
Whether it's an engagement
or a future marriage,
it should not become a restraint
on a lady.
After you.
Xihe, how are you?
Are you hurt? I've been searching
for you all night with my guards.
I'm fine.
Completely unharmed.
I was the one
who took you horseback riding.
And I failed to look after you.
If anything had really happened to you,
I would've regretted it
for the rest of my life.
Young Master Bu,
don't listen to Her Highness
making it sound so trivial.
You have no idea how dangerous it was.
It was all thanks
to the Crown Prince's help.
The Crown Prince?
With how frail he is?
I don't believe it.
What's wrong with being frail?
Being strong and robust
is useless if one is unwilling
to protect his wife.
Although Crown Prince
is physically weak,
he risked his life to help Her Highness.
He is a true gentleman.
How is the search for the live bees
I asked you to find?
You only care about requesting live bees
to treat Crown Prince's eye ailment.
It seems
this marriage is settled.
Your Highness,
this matter of the star gate
may sound mysterious,
but Prince Xin has always been
cautious and prudent.
How could he lose his composure
over such a legend?
Besides,
this concerns the Commandery Princess's
true identity.
Since you intend
for her to be the Crown Princess
of the East Palace,
shouldn't you
investigate this thoroughly?
When I first met her,
she was Shen Xihe.
Regardless of
whether the star gate exists,
since my heart belongs to her,
if she doesn't want to talk about it,
I will not pry.
Think carefully again.
Did your elder sister
and Commandery Princess Zhaoning
have any sort of friendship?
Brother-in-law,
my sister never treated me,
the daughter of a concubine,
as a real sister.
She always ignored me.
I know very little about her.
Are you sure you never saw
her receive letters from northwest?
I never saw any.
How could you mistake
Commandery Princess for Gu Qingzhi?
How insolent.
Do not address your fifth sister-in-law
by her given name.
I know.
You're trying to find out if your wife
and Commandery Princess
really corresponded by letter.
Do you really think
Commandery Princess is your wife?
What?
Are you trying to stop me?
I have to stop you.
What are you going to do?
Then you'll have to kill me.
Have you gone mad?
I thought you were drowning
in sorrow over your wife's death
and hadn't moved on.
But now it seems
you clearly want to lock yourself away
for the rest of your life!
I have lost my mind.
The woman I loved most has left me,
but everyone around me
is forcing me to act
as if nothing happened.
They say,
"A man lost in love is useless
for greater things."
They say,
"A great man need not worry
about finding a wife."
"Just find another suitable woman."
But has anyone
ever understood my pain?
I know your pain.
But Commandery Princess
is not your wife.
Your obsession is just an illusion.
I'm begging you, let yourself go.
Please?
I will never give up.
- It's Crown Prince.
- Changqing.
Your Highness.
Greetings, Changqing,
Changying.
Why are you here, Your Highness?
This place is hidden in a bustling city,
a quiet and peaceful corner.
It's a perfect place to hide a mistress.
Secretly hiding the descendant
of a convicted official.
Changqing, you truly are audacious.
Father has always held you
in high regard.
Over the years,
you've learned a great deal
about the art of ruling.
Coupled with your exceptional
intelligence since childhood,
in the eyes of the court officials,
you are the candidate for Crown Prince
that Father has groomed
for over a decade.
If Gu Qingshu were to be exposed,
tell me,
wouldn't the noble families
and officials backing the other princes
all rise up and attack you?
What?
You want to get rid of me?
I don't want your life.
I just want you to stop
bothering
Commandery Princess Zhaoning.
This is just a small request.
I hope you'll consider it seriously.
How could Crown Prince know
about Gu Qingshu's existence?
I was careless.
However, through this,
I've seen his true colors.
It's not a total loss.
Are you saying
he's faking his illness?
I don't think he's faking it.
But he must have his own sources
of intelligence in the court.
Our every move
is under his control.
I had considered that the Crown Prince
might be someone
who hides his true abilities.
But I never expected that
while he was alone
and away from the capital,
he could weave
such a large and intricate web.
Then, Changqing,
what do you plan to do?
The Crown Prince may be powerful enough
to stir up storms,
but he cannot threaten
me, Xiao Changqing.
I switched out the descendant
of a convicted official.
My crime is unforgivable.
I ask for your severe punishment,
Father.
It's been so long.
You're only just now remembering
to confess to me?
Shu...
has reached marriageable age.
If I were to keep her hidden
for her entire life,
I'm afraid Qingzhi would resent me
for not taking good care of her sister.
Today, I've dared to bring her
before you, Father.
For all my crimes,
I am willing to bear the consequences.
Changqing,
I know that you are grieving the loss
of your beloved wife
and your heart is still heavy.
Since you dared
to save Second Young Lady Gu,
it is my will
to bestow her upon you.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
- Father,
- I...
Shu is my wife's younger sister.
I have always regarded her
as my own sister.
Qingzhi passed away not long ago.
I am not yet willing to remarry
or take a concubine.
Fine.
Then I won't force you.
Thank you, Father.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
(Prince Xin's Manor)
This is the second time
you've saved my life.
I truly don't know
how to repay you.
It was His Majesty who pardoned you.
Besides,
I didn't do this for you,
nor do I need to be repaid.
No, Brother-in-law.
Since childhood, I have never
been doted on by my elders.
After the Gu family's downfall,
it was under your protection
that I was lucky enough to survive.
If you wouldn't mind,
I am willing to serve you
in my sister's place.
I look after you
because you are Qingzhi's
only living relative.
There is no other reason.
Also,
you must remember this.
There is no one in this world
who can replace Qingzhi.
I'll have someone escort you back.
No one can replace her?
What about Commandery Princess Zhaoning?
(East Palace)
Your Highness, how are
your eyes feeling?
Although I still can't
distinguish colors,
the stinging and dryness
have improved a lot.
Since we are now allies,
I won't be a stranger.
Thank you for your trouble.
♪If not for the chirping
of a few insects♪
♪In the warm days, a gentle breeze
blows open the blossoms on a tree♪
♪How else would I think of someone?♪
♪A faint taste of longing on my lips♪
♪Like a thousand twists and turns♪
♪Gone forever,
yet I savor the memory again and again♪
I wonder if you've heard
that in the Imperial Study today,
Changqing met with His Majesty
and admitted that three years ago,
in prison,
he secretly swapped out the descendant
of a convicted official.
Who was it?
The second daughter of the Gu family,
Gu Qingshu.
Not only did Father not blame her,
but he even returned some
of the Gu family's assets to her.
He also granted her the title
of County Princess Liyang.
What are you thinking about?
I'm thinking
about how these ladies
from prominent families
can fall from grace overnight,
reduced to dust,
and just as quickly,
they can be restored to glory.
If a lady doesn't take control
of her own destiny,
she will be like a rootless duckweed.
Never mind the second Gu daughter.
Even the eldest,
Gu Qingzhi,
the paragon of ladies in the capital,
the foremost among noblewomen,
didn't want to marry Changqing,
but she had no choice.
In the end, she met a tragic fate.
But I think
Gu Qingzhi
never bowed to fate.
When her family was destroyed,
she still held her destiny
firmly in her own hands.
What do you mean by that?
With Gu Qingzhi's intelligence
and resourcefulness,
if she had wanted to,
she could have found a thousand ways
to avoid marrying into the royal family.
But a lady
with upbringing and responsibility
etched into her very being
would not, for her own selfish reasons,
abandon the mission
her family entrusted to her.
Marrying Changqing
was an all-or-nothing gamble.
She knew long ago
that the struggle between noble families
would inevitably lead to bloodshed.
So, as Prince Xin's Consort,
she guarded the Gu family
and protected her clan.
Although the Gu family
was ultimately defeated,
I believe
that Gu Qingzhi's heart was free
of regret and guilt.
They were a family.
They supported each other.
working together.
She had no choice
but to take responsibility.
She did everything she could.
And she used her own life to set a trap
and avenge the Gu family.
Why are you looking at me like that?
It's nothing.
I'm just a little surprised.
This must be the Songyue Blade,
which can slice through iron like mud.
Just the agate on it...
A single stone is worth a fortune.
I see you have good taste.
My best friend is celebrating
a happy occasion.
So I'm hosting a drinking contest here.
Whoever can beat me,
this precious blade
will be theirs.
Young Master Bu,
I'll take you on.
Young Master Hu.
- Nice!
- Awesome!
Please.
- Young Master Bu.
- Young Master Hu.
Stop drinking.
Stop drinking. How much have they had?
Jin Shan.
Yes.
Fill it up for me!
Young Master,
maybe you shouldn't drink anymore.
Fill it up.
- Vice Minister Cui.
Stone Cui.
Pour the liquor.
You two are evenly matched.
If you keep drinking,
I'm afraid you'll harm yourselves.
Why don't we call it a draw?
The blade will still belong
to Young Master Bu.
Young Master Hu,
I'll give you a fine blade
some other day.
All right, then.
Let's go.
I'll take you home.
Who are you to me?
What gives you the right
to make decisions for me?
Jin Shan, bring the blade.
Yes.
Young Master Hu.
Quickly.
Go get a bowl of sobering soup.
Yes.
Jin Shan, pour the liquor.
Drink.
Drink him to death.
This is completely improper.
Vice Minister Cui.
You're very handsome.
Your words and actions are outrageous.
You're drunk out of your mind.
Where did he go?
He's gone...
(Clarity and Serenity)
Your Highness,
I asked Young Master Bu
to find some live bees.
Physician Xie can use
the stingers of wild bees
to stimulate your acupoints
and treat your eye condition.
Thank you for your concern.
It's just a small matter.
To you,
it may be a small matter.
But to me,
it is precious.
Physician Xie, you may begin.
Could you
stay here with me?
All right.
I'll wait here.
Physician Xie said
these stings will heal
in three to five days.
You just need to rest and recover.
Your Highness,
it's time for your medicine.
There's nothing wrong with your hands.
Yet you insist on being served.
I'm...
too weak to take care of myself.
In half a month,
after my coming-of-age ceremony,
I will ask my father
to arrange our marriage. How about that?
We've already agreed.
This is a mutually
beneficial arrangement.
It's best not to get
too emotionally involved.
I don't want a future
where you expect all your efforts
to be reciprocated.
When you can't get what you want,
you'll grow resentful.
All right.
Then in the future,
no matter how I treat you,
I do it of my own free will.
You don't have to feel indebted to me.
With a response like that,
are you satisfied?
I am.
Your Highness,
from what Commandery Princess said,
it seems she's willing to marry you.
But she was so blunt
about her lack of feelings.
As long as she's willing to marry me,
that's enough.
First, I'll secure the marriage.
Then, I'll win her heart.
If she isn't devoted to me,
it just means I haven't been
good enough to her.
(Jade Terrace and Auspicious Dew)
Who is Bian Xianyi close with
in the palace?
Is there any new information?
She doesn't like
to draw attention to herself.
When she doesn't have
to attend palace banquets,
she keeps to herself
and rarely goes out.
Move!
I didn't mean to offend you.
Please forgive me, Your Highness.
It's fine.
Don't worry about it.
Princess Pingling ordered me to...
Did the fall knock you senseless?
If you're still breathing,
then climb back up there
and get it for me.
Mo Yu.
Shen Xihe.
You see me,
and you don't even come forward
to greet me?
I heard
that because of the cliff incident,
His Majesty punished you by making
you copy the Heart Sutra 100 times.
It seems
that copying scriptures
has failed to improve your character.
You...
How dare you mock me?
I...
- Your Highness.
Your Highness.
Shen Xihe,
you're becoming more
and more insolent!
I have no grudge against you.
Why did you deliberately cause me
to fall off the cliff?
I only whipped your horse.
Who knew it would run toward a cliff?
What does that have to do with me?
So you did it, but you won't admit it.
Forget it.
I can't be bothered to argue with you.
But let me give you a word of warning.
If there's a next time,
it won't be as simple as
just breaking your nose.
How dare you threaten Her Highness
with such insubordination?
You failed to serve Her Highness well.
Her Highness doesn't have the heart
to blame you,
so I taught you a lesson on her behalf.
I'm sure you won't blame me
for overstepping my bounds, right?
It's getting late.
We have plenty of time.
I will come
visit you again another day.
- Your Highness.
- It hurts so much.
What are you standing around for?
Go to the Imperial Medical Office!
Your Highness, are you just going
to let her off the hook?
She's spoiled and arrogant.
All she knows is how to be condescending
and provocative.
She's no threat.
However, the one
who sent assassins after me
and threatened Bian Xianyi
into poisoning me
is the real venomous snake
hiding by my side.
We must investigate this thoroughly.
- Yes.
(Cultivate Virtue
and Practice Righteousness)
Your Highness,
this bronze sachet was found
in Bian Xianyi's room.
There's still some incense residue
on it.
First, take this item
to Commandery Princess's Residence.
Then, find out which types
of incense are used in each palace.
Yes.
This fragrance is
Three Balanced Elements Incense.
It's an incense made
from borneol, musk powder,
and the finest agarwood.
The formula is exquisite
and the ingredients are expensive.
Ordinary people wouldn't use it.
Palace maids and attendants
certainly couldn't afford
this kind of incense.
Your Highness,
Crown Prince sent over this report
on incense usage.
(Monthly Incense Usage Report)
This Three Balanced Elements Incense
is only used in three places.
Princess Pingling's chambers,
the Empress Dowager's
Buddhist prayer hall,
and Consort Liang's chambers.
I've noticed that silk sachets
are more common in the palace.
Bronze incense holders are rarely used.
This pattern is unique to northwest.
Your Highness, look.
The flowers are so beautiful this year.
Greetings, Your Highness.
There's no need for such formalities.
I am a bit tired.
Please, feel free to stay.
Your Highness,
I have something
I'd like to return to you.
Who says this belongs to me?
I don't recognize this item.
This was found in Bian Xianyi's room.
Your Highness,
do you wish to argue this
before His Majesty?
I have so many sachets.
Who can be bothered
to remember every single one?
That Bian Xianyi was a good dancer.
Perhaps I gifted it to her before.
Or maybe she stole it.
How would I remember?
But I must advise you.
It's best to watch what you say.
I am His Majesty's consort.
How dare you slander me
with baseless accusations?
Tell Mo Yuan
to gather evidence of her crimes.
Present it all to His Majesty.
She has intentionally plotted murder.
She has several lives on her hands.
She cannot be spared.
Yes.
Your Highness, if Commandery Princess
Zhaoning refuses to let this go,
what should we do?
What is there to fear?
I am the Emperor's consort.
No matter how arrogant she is,
she is merely the daughter
of a subject.
What could she possibly do to me?
Yes.
Throw out all the sachets
in my chambers.
Yes.
Go.
Your Highness.
I'll go get the imperial physician
right away.
It's nothing.
The wound isn't deep.
Bai Fu is usually so gentle.
It's always been closest
to you, Your Highness.
Why did it suddenly go wild?
An animal is just an animal.
Xiao Changyu.
Look at you, half-dead.
When will you ever avenge your uncle?
That useless Bian Xianyi.
She failed
to poison Commandery Princess Zhaoning
and ended up poisoning herself to death.
Because of Shen Xihe,
your uncle, Ye Qi,
was exiled a thousand miles away
and died in a land of pestilence.
Those wretches in the palace,
knowing I have no family to support me,
humiliate me as they please.
You must get rid of Shen Xihe
for my sake.
Xianyi is gone.
My heart
is gone with her.
Nonsense.
You think Bian Xianyi
was deeply in love with you?
The truth...
The truth is,
she was using me all along.
She used me for protection,
to fend off her unwanted suitors.
In reality, she loved someone else.
I knew all of it.
You knew?
Then why did you
still protect that wench?
How much longer
will you let a dead person
haunt your heart?
If that sickly Crown Prince
marries Shen Xihe
and gains the support of northwest,
his position on the throne
will be secured.
What chance will you have then?
Mother,
I have never wanted to fight for it.
I have disappointed you.
Useless.
Useless!
Physician Huang,
what's wrong with Her Highness?
It seems to be an external affliction
from pathogenic wind.
Her Highness's qi and blood
were already somewhat deficient.
I will first prescribe a formula
to dispel wind and relieve the exterior.
You must ensure Her Highness takes it
on schedule.
She should recover in a few days.
Li Yanhui, you don't
still think you're a princess, do you?
If it weren't
for His Majesty's arranged marriage,
do you think you would have survived?
County Princess Liyang used me
to provoke Prince Ding's Consort
and cause trouble.
If I had been cut
by these porcelain shards,
would that have been what you wanted?
♪I've hidden so many words♪
♪Too reluctant to tell you♪
♪So never uncover♪
♪The sand that slips away
with one grasp♪
♪The flower that withers
after one bloom♪
♪Silently buried deep inside my heart♪
♪Every answer I gave♪
♪Was both bittersweet and absurd♪
♪Hiding my tear-filled eyes
when I hurt you♪
♪How hard it truly was?♪
♪The wounds that healed
with just a little comfort♪
♪The lies made whole
with a single embrace♪
♪Pretending to be brave
as if I'd never been hurt♪
♪It's a shame I never could♪
♪Give you a moon in return♪
♪With the same open heart you loved me♪
♪I've crossed the wasteland of memories♪
♪Never knowing I was lost♪
♪Why don't you take me away?♪
♪Lead me out of this endless game
of hide-and-seek♪
♪You'll never♪
♪Know how much I long to, long to♪
(No animals were harmed
in the making of this film)