[Live and learn]
Hello, everyone.
I'm Zhang Junjia.
Actually,
I was so happy
to see you again
when school started.
Besides, I remember you used to
cry a lot back then,
and you were chubby.
The sound of heartbeats
is like music,
sometimes fast,
and sometimes slow.
When it loses its rhythm, one would
be uneasy.
Just like the tenth fret of a guitar,
which is hard to play at first.
But once you find the right position,
you can play the clearest chord.
[Smile After Tears]
[Tenth Fret: The Chord of Heartbeat]
Junjia.
Do you need help?
No need.
Go take a seat.
Here.
There.
Are you sure you don't need my help?
Yes.
Sit down.
Okay.
Are you sure you don't need help?
I told you to sit down.
Okay.
I've sat down.
Wait for me a moment.
Tell me if you need any help.
No need.
I did my best.
I work every day to make money,
so I just eat something to fill me up.
I eat takeout almost every meal.
So,
I've never cooked myself.
From now on,
just leave this stuff to me.
Aren't you still injured?
Take care of yourself first.
We can talk about the rest
later.
Okay.
Has
the team training been going well?
My fingers are used to it now.
They don't hurt as much.
What about you?
What about the basketball game?
I'm going for
a follow-up appointment today.
The bandage can be removed today.
Don't worry.
Wait.
I feel like something's wrong.
Let's try again.
I still feel like something's wrong.
One more time.
What's wrong?
Junjia,
there is not much time left before
the submission deadline for the demo.
What exactly is wrong?
Well,
how about we take a break first?
[Live and learn]
Are you okay?
You seem a little bit off today.
Can I ask you a question?
Back then,
why did He like music?
He was trained to
learn all kinds of instruments
since he was a kid.
Later, he liked composing songs.
From then on, he began to love music.
He felt happy when he sang.
Is it really just because of the joy?
I really want to finish He's song.
But I always feel that the current song
is just a finished product.
There is no emotion behind it.
You mean
the current song sounds
like you're doing it just to get it done,
not because you really enjoy it?
Don't rush to find the answer.
Music is not an exam anyway.
It will tell you
on its own
when your mind is most relaxed.
This is what my brother told me.
Sounds like something he would say.
Diaoqin, are you okay?
I'm fine.
Do you want to take a break?
No, it's okay.
I can do it.
Let's practice layups.
Jiateng, ball.
Junjia.
You're in such a hurry to play basketball.
Didn't the doctor say to take it slow?
I'm just warming up.
Don't worry.
I'm almost done.
Let's go home together later.
Junjia.
Can you get me a towel?
Don't move.
Let me help you.
I can do it myself.
Is your shoulder okay?
What if
it affects
the game?
If it really affects it,
there's nothing I can do.
Sometimes,
accidents happen.
We have no choice but to accept them.
But
accidents
are always scary.
You know what?
My fish have been replaced several times.
Before,
some fish would jump out
and die.
So I added a lid.
Unexpectedly,
it was not ventilated,
and the water temperature rose.
Then, the fish died again.
No matter how you prevent it,
accidents will still happen.
But
I still don't want to give up.
One day,
I will definitely find a way
to let them live well.
Find a way.
Recently, during team training,
I always felt something was wrong.
It feels like I missed something.
If
you need my help,
I can be your audience.
I don't understand music,
but
I can tell you
how I feel when I listen.
What was this song
[Watching you drown in sorrow]
originally about?
♪ Watching you drown in sorrow ♪
In this song,
♪ In your tears ♪
He tried to talk about a sweet couple
deeply in love.
♪ I wonder what love is ♪
♪ It's when you're alone,
someone is by your side ♪
I really want to finish it,
not just because
it's He's last work.
But
♪ It's when you're lost,
someone points out the right direction ♪
the more I sing, the more it feels wrong.
♪ Though you have nothing,
you won't turn around ♪
♪ But you are in midsummer ♪
♪ In spring flowers ♪
Why
♪ In the aurora full of stars ♪
can't I get that feeling?
♪ I can only wait for you ♪
Is it because your singing
♪ I can't be afraid of you getting hurt ♪
lacks sweetness?
♪ It reminds us that
freedom is also a cage ♪
If you want,
♪ Between us ♪
I'll help you find it.
♪ Repeating ♪
♪ After you turn around,
I'll wipe your tears ♪
♪ Hugging and hovering, only in dreams ♪
♪ After you turn around,
I'll wipe your tears ♪
It's said that
fish have a memory of only seven seconds.
♪ Hugging and spinning,
in the room that doesn't exist♪
Maybe their love
only lasts seven seconds, too.
It's short,
♪ Hope, hope again ♪
fading quickly.
♪ You have no tears ♪
But the seven seconds
♪ I'll smile from afar, goodbye ♪
are precious enough.
Why?
Because love
is love.
Even if it only lasts seven seconds,
it's real.
Even if it's short,
it's worth remembering.
In the ending,
after searching all day,
I still couldn't find the answer.
Maybe I
can never finish this song.
Don't give up.
I once lost five or six
basketball games
and couldn't figure out why.
But I kept trying,
practiced hard,
and realized that
even though I failed to get an answer,
I could still win once.
What if you had kept losing?
Then,
I would think I was unlucky.
Is it really okay to think that way?
You have to.
Maybe
you don't have to find answers.
When the time comes,
they will reveal themselves.
[Diaoqin]
I noticed you weren't home this morning,
and you didn't come to school.
What happened?
Excuse me,
have you seen Zheng Diaoqin?
He went to the hospital
for a follow-up appointment today.
The hospital?
His shoulder ligament is severely torn.
He can't participate in
the National Youth Inter-School Cup.
Let's go.
Let's practice.
[Diaoqin]
The number you dialed is not answering.
Your call is being transferred
to voicemail.
Junjia,
why are you here?
Where did you go?
Why didn't you answer your phone?
Why did you go to the hospital
without telling me?
I heard
you can't participate in the game.
Your injury is so severe.
Why didn't you tell me?
It's fine.
Just miss one game.
It's no big deal.
But
if it weren't for me,
you wouldn't have gotten injured.
Don't say so much right now.
Let's talk when we get home,
okay?
Let's go.
Thanks.
Junjia.
Do you remember
what I told you before?
Some fish
jumped out.
Later, I added a lid,
but the water temperature got too high.
Then, I added a thermostat.
In the end,
the water temperature
fluctuated drastically,
and the fish
might still die.
So,
accidents are just like that.
They aren't caused by just one thing,
but a combination of events.
I had
an old injury here long ago.
I couldn't lift heavy anyway.
It just so happened that the hit
accelerated what was bound to happen.
But...
Junjia.
I lost
several competitions
and only won once.
But I never gave up.
Do you know why?
If I keep telling myself
that I've lost,
then wouldn't I be too
afraid to do anything?
Though I missed this time's game,
I can still participate in the next one.
If we miss one opportunity,
there will still be new ones.
The most important thing is
that you're still here,
and you can start again.
What the heck?
Don't you think it's scary?
Not really.
It's pretty ordinary.
Besides, aren't they ghosts to begin with?
Can we stop watching it?
No.
If we don't finish watching it,
how can we know if you
can get any inspiration from that or not?
Fine.
Here it is.
Why did you scare me?
How is it?
Any inspiration?
No.
Don't scare me again.
Okay.
Horror movies
can get your heart racing.
Sometimes when you get scared,
you accidentally get closer to each other.
Or
try rollerblading.
How's it?
I don't know how to skate.
Come on.
Give me your hands.
I'll help you.
Take it easy.
It's unsteady at first.
You need someone to hold your hand.
I think I've got it.
I'm letting go.
Okay.
When you fall,
someone will help you up.
Finally,
go see the night view together.
Looking down from here,
you'll find the whole city
looks smaller,
like blocks.
I think
I've found the answer.
What's the answer?
I was afraid of
admitting it before.
After losing He,
I felt
completely lost.
[Senior He]
Good morning.
Why did you do that?
He gave it to me.
What are you doing?
- No, no.
- You can't take that apart.
Later,
I thought I found my direction.
But
I was just going in circles.
Is it like dribbling the ball in place?
Pretty much.
Except
no one is going to steal my ball.
I'm the one
who doesn't want to let go of the ball.
What about now?
Do you know that
no matter how dark it gets,
there will always be light?
I know.
But no matter how bright it gets,
it will get dark, too.
Athletes
usually rely on rest
to recover their stamina.
The sun needs rest too.
If it's always bright,
the plants
would wither and die.
The rivers
would dry up too.
When I'm with you,
I feel recharged.
Then,
do you want to take this chance
to write down this feeling?
Here?
The most real feeling is right now.
This time,
what I want to write
is not what I lost,
but
what else I can give.
Our demo passed.
[Preview of the Next Episode]
We advanced.
Welcome.
Is this
where Junjia works?
Are you Diaoqin?
I am.
Are you with Junjia?
He hasn't arrived backstage yet.