Wataru.
What's wrong?
I'm sorry.
If you don't want this,
you can push me away.
Wait...
What are you doing?
What if someone comes?
Yeah... I know.
I'm sorry.
His feelings and sincerity...
I can feel them so deeply, and yet...
I guess I still can't do this.
That lonely look he gets sometimes...
Why is that?
Here.
Wait a minute.
Where did that voice come from?
You startled me.
You looked lost in thought.
Is something on your mind?
It's nothing.
Thanks.
How can Saeki act so normal
after making a request like that?
So, when can we go to the beach
from the final scene?
Oh... the pilgrimage?
Yeah.
That's the last spot, right?
With part-time work and homework...
The only day I can clear my schedule
is the twenty-eighth.
The twenty-eighth?
Yeah.
Does that work for you?
- Let's make it the twenty-eighth then.
- Sounds good.
That cave is really amazing.
It left a huge impression on me.
That's the place I want to visit most.
I can't wait.
By the way,
once this deal is over...
what will happen to us?
(Take care.)
(No...!)
(Let go of me.)
(I don't want to... pleaes don't go)
(I'm sorry...)
(You're not in my heart anymore.)
To Saeki, this is probably
just a way to get closure.
Once this is all over,
we'll just go back to how we were...
(Goodbye.)
One day, he'll stop liking me.
If that happens...
I'll be so lonely.
"My Summer Of You"
(Episode 4)
Typhoon No. 4 is expected
to bring strong winds...
- with potential warning-level heavy rain.
- Saeki?
It's no use.
The trains to Moriya Beach are suspended.
Even though it's barely
windy or rainy here.
Yeah.
There's nothing we can do about a typhoon.
It suddenly changed course.
Damn it.
I wanted to go even if it rained,
but it really is too dangerous.
What a shame.
Then do you want to come
over and watch "Sea of Light"?
Huh?
Well, since we have the day off,
I thought you could come over.
Oh, or I could go to your place instead.
No, I'll go to yours.
My place is a bit of a mess right now.
Is it?
Yeah.
Though my room is pretty messy too.
Whatever, it's fine.
I'll text you my address.
Okay, I'll head over now.
Alright, time to clean up.
Okay...
Oh my god.
Underwear... Why is there
underwear all over the floor?
- Come on in.
- Thanks for having me.
This room is so you, Wataru.
Stop staring.
Showing someone your room feels as
embarrassing as letting them see you naked.
Naked?
No, I mean my interests and tastes.
It feels like my mind
is completely exposed.
I know.
Oh, sorry.
This...
Huh...?
Ah! I'm sorry!
I'm sorry.
Excuse me.
- Excuse me.
- Wait, wait!
It's not what it looks like!
It's a total misunderstanding!
Look, this was on the floor...
Underwear?
He tried to grab the underwear I picked up,
and we both tripped and fell.
Oh, I see.
Sorry about that.
My brother is such a slob.
Oh, I'm Wataru's older sister.
I'm Saeki.
Sorry for dropping by so suddenly.
Don't worry about it.
Mom said to give you guys this.
Oh, thank you.
Sis, we're going to watch a movie.
Get out already.
Have fun, Saeki.
Get out, hurry up.
- Let's start watching.
- Yeah.
"Sea of Light"
It really is the best.
Yeah, it's great no matter
how many times I watch it.
But watching it makes
me want to go even more.
To the beach from the final scene.
Yeah.
By the way, I missed
the Tonkatsu Pavilion guy.
Oh, I forgot about that.
Let's look for him next time.
Yeah...
The typhoon seems weaker than I expected.
Yeah.
Hey, let's reschedule
once school starts.
We really have to go there
for this to feel complete.
Wataru, you can stop here.
I can walk the rest of the way.
Okay.
Well... see you next semester.
Get home safe.
Saeki?
Wataru, thank you.
For what?
I didn't do anything.
See ya.
Even so, thank you.
Morning, Wataru.
Did you enjoy your summer?
Of course I did.
It was summer, after all.
You idiot.
By "enjoying summer,".
I mean "falling in love."
Get it?
No way. Enjoying summer
means working up a sweat in youth.
That makes absolutely no sense.
None at all.
Hey.
Are you looking for Saeki?
Huh?
You've been staring at the
hallway since this morning.
I just heard from a
friend in the other class...
that Saeki is absent today.
Apparently, it's due to family matters.
Family matters?
That's what the homeroom teacher said.
Did Saeki mention anything to you?
No.
Sorry for texting when I know you're busy.
I heard you were absent today too.
I'm worried.
If there's anything I can do,
please let me know.
It's already been three days.
Alright.
I'm so sleepy...
I can't survive two more periods.
What are you guys talking about?
Summer is over.
Now is the season for studying.
- Goodnight.
- Hey.
Excuse me, do you have a second?
You're Toda, right?
- Yeah.
- I'm Kawaguchi from Class A.
Toda, you're always with Saeki, right?
I guess so.
Did you hear about that?
About what?
Wait, seriously?
Even you don't know, Toda?
He's been absent since
the semester started, right?
Yeah, I think so.
Well, the homeroom
teacher announced it today.
He transferred schools.
Apparently, it was decided
suddenly over summer break.
I tried calling him, but he didn't pick up.
I thought you might know something,
so I came to ask.
Do you know anything?
Toda?
Hey.
The phone you are calling may be turned off
or out of the coverage area.
Please tell me where he moved.
You really don't give up, do you?
Can you really not tell me?
Like I said,
I can't give you that information.
It's a matter of personal privacy.
Just ask him yourself.
But I can't get in touch with him.
Please.
You two are as stubborn as they come.
I'll only tell you what I'm allowed to.
Is that okay?
Yes.
Well, how should I put this...
It's true that he's transferring.
But he's actually moving to Canada.
Canada?
Yes.
I heard his father is being stationed
there, so he has to go with him.
But this wasn't decided over summer break.
It was already set during the first semester.
What?
He asked me to keep it a secret
until the start of the second semester.
I tried to talk him out of it,
asking if he was really okay with this.
But he was extremely
firm and wouldn't budge.
Since he was so determined,
I couldn't force him.
He must have had his reasons.
I'm sorry, but I can't
tell you where he moved.
Because I made a promise to him.
That's all I can say.
So that's how it was.
The person I like
is the Wataru right in front of me.
Even his confession to me...
But in return, I have a favor to ask.
Would that be okay?
Even proposing that trade-off...
Everything up until now...
All of it...
So that's what it was all about.
Is Wataru going to be okay?
Who knows?
I don't know what Saeki's situation is,
but those two were really close.
Leaving without saying a word...
It must be really hard on him.
Oh, Wataru is back.
Want to go to the batting cages?
Huh?
I feel like I haven't gotten
any exercise in ages.
- Oh.
- Sure.
- Let's go then.
- Let's do it!
I want to hit too.
- Awesome!
- What speed are you going for?
150 km/h, of course!
Damn it!
Wataru, turn down the speed!
No, this is fine.
I like you.
He hit it! He hit it!
A grand slam!
That's amazing!
Wataru?
See that? That's the power
of the Go-Home Club.
Oh, go for it, Hiraoka!
- Show us your tournament spirit!
- I won't lose!
Whoever misses has to buy ice cream!
Ah, are you talking about Guchi?
Leave me alone!
Watch me hit a home run!
- You jerk!
- Huh?
Buying three ice creams is way too much.
I'm completely broke.
Lately, I've been living on broccoli.
Like I care.
I'm the one who's short on cash.
Being broke is a serious issue.
See you tomorrow, then.
- See ya.
- Bye! See you tomorrow.
I'm done. My hands are all red.
Me too.
Wow, that looks painful.
No way. I'm skipping
club activities for a while.
Should we watch this one next time too?
Really? Awesome!
The female lead is indeed really cute.
I don't want to watch it again
just to see her.
No?
No...
Well, maybe a little.
But you didn't have to say it out loud...
I'm home.
It's so hot.
Oh, you're back.
You're quite late today.
I went to the batting cages
with Guchi and the guys.
I see. Oh, by the way,
- You've got a letter.
- A letter?
Yeah.
For me?
Here, this one.
It's rare for anyone to
write letters these days.
Wait a minute.
You're being loud!
(Saeki Chiharu)
(Wataru...)
(Next Episode) I thought even if I left,
he wouldn't care that much.
If you don't like it, you can just say so.
Isn't he in Japan right now?
Tell the homeroom
teacher I'm leaving early.
I absolutely refuse
to let this summer end like this.